6tartin ' tobay, we' re in tbe elite class!
Time ta move into tbe empty room!
Eita!
Wbat's all tbis? Um depósito?
A Rokubou-san me falou disso aqui.
Fveryone bibes stuff bere tbey bon 't
want founb buring room inspections.
Mas o que vamos fazer
com as coisas do pessoal?
Me falaram que elas iam vir pegar depois,
so we' re just to clean up for now.
Clean it up? Por que a gente?
Tbe beck? Wbat we gonna bo witb tbat?
Ob! Tbat's gotta be Rokubou 's
secret training macbine.
Oo figure. O treino da escola é pouco pra ela.
Sério? Well, since we gotta clean,
migbt as well see wbat everyone's got.
Wb-Wbat?
Pigures?
Eles são da Kawai-san.
Ela ama tanto répteis que
coleciona figures deles.
Mas por que répteis?
E essa roupa de motoqueiro?
Isso é da Kusakai-san.
Ah, então ela gosta de motos? Que maneiro!
Nozomi? Let's organize everytbing into rooms.
Agiliza ou isso vai levar o dia todo.
Que treco pesado é esse?
Nem da pra mover...
O que tem dentro?
3-3ubbba statues?!
l bearb Yosbiba-san likes
carving 3ubbba statues.
3ut using stone? Tbat's too barbcore!
Hum, de quem será que é essa?
O que é isso aqui?
l-lt's from "Weak-Kneeb 3oy! "
Must be Pujisaki-san's!
Isto é... são fotos da Kusakai-san?
"Oobbess Collection "
Tbis, too? Anb tbis one?!
All tbese boxes markeb "Tsuki " are packeb
witb pboto albums of just Kusakai-san!
Já limpamos quas tudo.
Boa! Falta pouco!
Ob, woulb ya look at tbat? Wbat a pretty room!
Now we just bave to carry our luggage in.
Hmm? Parece que esqucemos algo.
A string?
No! Take a closer look!
Isso é lingerie!
Quêêê?!
3ut it's just a tiny string!
No way! Tbey make panties tbat small?
You can see rigbt tbrougb ' em!
ls tbis wbat tbey call " battle panties" ?
3attle panties?!
U-Um...
Será que... podem me devolver isso?
De.. vol.. ver?
ln otber worbs, tbey belong to Kazane...?
Um, tbat's not bow it is! You see, ub...
lt's okay, Kazane-chan.
Isso mesmo.
Tbe soft-spoken Aoba-san...
lt's battle time...
...baving sucb a stimulating swimsuit.
You must be a lot bolber do que eu pensei.
Não, não é isso!
Eu peguei umas roupas da minha irmã por engano e escondi aí pra ninguém achar!
Tbat weak excuse won 't work on us.
Tbat's rigbt.
No secrets between us, rigbt?
l tbink we' b all like to bear
about your battle experience.
Fb?!
Tell us!
Já disse que não é isso!
CONTINUA NO PRÓXIMO VOLUME!!
PRÓXIMA PALAVRA DE QUADRIL
「FEL CIBER」