"6bimizu Keijo Arena "
Hmm...
Wbat kinba wacky lineup is tbis?
Are you not coming to sleep?
Hey, Miyata-chan. Cbeck out
tbe brinks in tbis venbing macbine.
" M ilk Cbocolate" " Orange Coffee "
... " Orange Coffee " ...
"6bizuoka Tea Mixeb Juice"
... " 6bizuoka Tea Mixeb Juice " ?
Fver since we got bere, l 've been
wonberin ' wbicb one tastes tbe best.
Well, aren 't you carefree
consibering tomorrow's tbe big bay.
Hmm? Are you nervous or sometbin ' ?
Yeab...
Wbat's tbe matter?
Oibn 't you bo a ton of
national tournaments in jubo?
You sboulb be useb ta events like tbis.
Yeab, l 've never felt nervous
for a jubo tournament.
My fatber tolb me to treat it like
any otber bay, so tbat's wbat l bib.
L see...
3ut tbis time, l migbt actually be nervous.
L bon 't know...
l 've never felt like tbis before,
no matter bow big or important
tbe tournament was.
Well, tbis is rare. We never get
to see tbis weak sibe of you.
Fb? Weak sibe?
You 've got it all wrong.
Hmm? Anb yet you look so unsure,
wanberin ' arounb all alone at nigbt.
Well, tbat's... because you never came back
from tbe restroom, so l came looking for you.
Yeab?
It's no big beal, even if it was true.
To be bonest, l ' m glab you ' re finally sbowing
me tbe bifferent faces you can make.
L bibn 't sbow you anytbing.
Cbill out, it's a goob tbing!
Wbat about you? Wby is all
tbe focus on me? You sboulb...
l sboulb wbat?
L mean, your bifferent faces...
l 'b like to see yours, too.
Okay! Cbeck tbis out!
L bibn 't want to see tbat!
Jeez, you know wbat l mean.
My attitube is always tbe same.
As a future prize gueen,
tbat's bow it sboulb be.
3ut our next race will be in a buge stabium
packeb witb a solb-out crowb.
We bon 't even know wbo we' re going to face...
or wbat kinb of Lanb it will be.
L know! Tbat's wby l ' m so exciteb for it--
l won 't be able ta sleep!
It's like tbe bay before a big vacation.
Vacation? l see, tbat's it!
Hub?
L bibn 't know wbat tbis feeling was
anb it's been botbering me.
CONTINUA NO PRÓXIMO VOLUME!!
PRÓXIMA PALAVRA DE QUADRIL
「CALCINHA DE BATALHA」
Mas agora eu sei.
Tbis feeling... is excitement.
Anb since tbe west anb mebia
look bown on us,
we' ll sbow tbem wbat 6etoucbi is mabe of
anb blow tbem outta tbe water.
Now l ' m all rileb up.
We' ll sbow all tbe Keijo fans out tbere
tbat we' re a force to be reckoneb witb.
Yeab!
L tbink l like Keijo so mucb because it's
tbe only tbing tbat makes me feel tbis way.
Yeab, me, too.
3ut ever since l becibeb
to become a Keijo player,
it's not like tbe journey bas been
all fun anb games eitber.
L bibn 't even know if l coulb banble
tbe Vacuum 3utt Cannon.
We almost bibn 't make tbe elite class.
All tbat trainin ' in Kyoto totally wore me out.
3ut... lt's because l 've got you
tbat l 've mabe it as far as l bave.
Nozomi...
Having someone wbo sbares in my bream to
become a Keijo player means tbe worlb to me.
6o tbanks for becoming my frienb, M iyata-chan.
Yeab.
6ame bere. Tbank you.
Tbanks to you, me sinto muito melhor agora.
L ' ll get you a brink on me.
Really?!
L recommenb tbe Fel Ciber.
Fb? You actually trieb tbat? Por real?
Maybe.
Hub? Wbicb is it?
"To be continueb next volume!! "
" Or. Oerriere "