Bonus anime:
Number 5
Seraph of the Endless!
Can't you even do something that simple?!
What'd you say?!
You go ahead and do it, then!
Now now, both of you...
Alright, why not? Unlike you, I can pull it off no problem!
What did you say?!
Come on, you two. Have a little self-control—!
And to think they'll be in the same unit together...
I wish they'd get along a least a little better.
You seem a little down, Yoichi-san.
Well, because...
If you really want to,
I know of a way that we can make those two get along.
Shall we give it a try?
If I remember correctly, it should be around here...
Here it is!
It's a discontinued book of secrets.
A-A book of secrets?!
Impressive! You drank those right down!
What the hell is this disgusting drink, anyway?
It's seriously bitter.
I'm fine with bitter stuff, though!
Oh, shut up.
Now now, you two.
This is a magical remedy to make Yoichi-san's wish about the two of you come true!
What the hell?
I just drank it, but that sounds shady as hell.
It's not harmful to their health, is it...?
It's a military secret, so it's probably fine.
"Probably"?!
This is a truth serum variation which brings out the honesty in people.
Oh?
Wh-What's happened to you two?
I think this is...
Woof!
Woof! Woof!
H-Hey!
One of the side effects listed is a chance to make the user
behave like an animal should the remedy be too effective.
Tell me that sooner!
"Like an animal"?! They've completely turned into dogs!
H-Hey!
Sit!
Oh?
Paw!
Well, this is cute.
Don't you think it turned out alright?
I-I don't really think so.
I mean, they're not getting along like this.
You think so?
I do! Turn them back to normal, please.
I guess I've got no choice.
This should be the antidote!
Are you saying that remedy was a poison?
I wonder...
Oh, they've finally turned back.
Looks like it worked this time.
How dare you do that to us, Shinoa?!
Come on, now...
You too, Yoichi!
Making us drink that suspicious—
What?
What's going on, you two...?
What?!
Yoichi.
Wh-What's going on, Yuu-kun?
I never noticed before, but when I look at you up close...
Come again?!
Umm... I... Umm...
K-Kimizuki-kun?
Yoichi...
You too?!
H-Hey, Kimizuki...!
Oh? Could this be a side effect of the antidote?
It seems to act like a love potion.
Why?! And how does that even work?!
Wouldn't I need to have taken it too?
And why have there been nothing but side effects?!
Yoichi...
Idiot! Can't you see Yoichi's troubled?
You're the one who's troubling him!
What'd you say?! You wanna go, huh?!
N-No fighting!
Kimizuki...
Your glasses...
Your hair...
I think it's kinda nice.
Oh! I think the antidote was much too effective.
It must be because you wanted them to get along so much, Yoichi-san.
Th-This is my fault?!
Now that it's come to this, there's only one way to solve the problem.
Here we go!
One, two...
Bash!
All I wanted... was for them to get along with each other.
Let me know whenever you want to borrow my secret power!
I'm not borrowing that ever again!