Na
go
ya
Arc
You're right, she is in this blade.
But I'm the one in control.
Oh hello there, Shinoa.
Long time no see.
How've you been?
I can clearly see my sister's the one in control.
I'm not possessed.
No, you're 100% possessed!
Or rather, you're being controlled!
You're haunted!
I'm not—
Oh, right, Guren.
We're having curry tonight,
so make sure to stop by the store and get some onions while they're on sale.
I'm... not...
Onions!
Th-This must be the power of the demon weapons...
No, wait, this just is a typical housewife!
You can and you will.
Fine.
I'll tell you why I let you live.
Why I need the Seraph of the End.
What?
Sorry, I didn't quite catch that.
Like I said...
Uh, sorry, I know you said you would tell me but
I'm pretty sure you're just making whispering sounds.
Please, can't you just tell me—
The truth is that Yuuichirou is—
Oh, my.
What's going on here?
We were testing your loyalties.
Now then, let's begin the debriefing.
Who the hell are you?
Lieutenant General of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army, Hiiragi Kureto.
Your interviewer!
Let's get started.
What do you hope to achieve by applying to the Imperial Demon Army?
What do I hope to achieve?
That's obvious! I just want to exterminate the vampires!
He's an idiot.
He is.
He's got the look of one, too.
A walking bundle of stupidity.
Indeed.
Next question.
How did you spend your time in school?
I did 1,000 practice swings a day with my sword!
Also, I slept through my classes
and ate lunch when I wanted!
Yep, he's an idiot.
Truly.
He's completely lacking.
In every way.
One last question.
Give us a display of your artistic ability.
You may not use your demon gear.
Wait, hold on. What do you mean?
Too late!
Lightning!
Hyakuya Yuuichirou,
you failed!