This bug report is just too sudden.
Bad news comes without warning.
At this rate, we may have to
postpone the activation indefinitely.
Why do you think we keep engineers around?
Indeed. Correction of bugs,
manipulation of information for vendors,
and project operation must
be adequate and prompt.
We are diligently tending to the matter.
I'm sick of hearing that answer.
Server expansion, arranging supplemental
personnel, and various expenses...
This could fell a whole company!
People, time, money...
How much of these things do we need
before this new system is complete?
At any rate, the UNI System's
activation date has been announced
at the general meeting of the shareholders.
Maybe we should outsource this job?
Naturally, we'll have you take full responsibility.
Please wait!
Please let us, the HackaDolls,
handle this matter.
Can you do that?
That's what HackaDolls are for.
"That's What HackaDolls Are For"
Episode 3
Five years and a thousand people have gone into
the development of this new AI system, UNI.
We're so close to its activation,
but now this unknown bug has popped up,
and we're at a total loss...
Bunny Ears - 2
Kitty Ears - 1
Doggy Ears - 3
Here is the report.
Report
18th mid-term report
DONE
I see... Leave this to us.
That's what HackaDolls are for.
You just like saying that, don't you?
I'm not sure what exactly we should do, though.
What?!
If only Yama-san,
the legendary genius programmer who
created the basic design for this
UNI System, would help us,
then this problem could be resolved.
I don't follow, but this
Yama-san sounds pretty great!
But then, one day,
he suddenly lost his motivation.
Yama-san!
If that's the case, then...
If we encourage him with a little free service,
he's sure to be motivated to work again!
I see...
Server Room
Yama-san has been shut in here
for over half a year now.
Here we are...
That's him?
Yama-san, please!
Please fix the bug in the UNI System!
Leave me alone.
That's Yama-san?
Leave this to me.
Yama-san, please work for us.
We'll reward you plenty for it.
Stop it!
That's not going to work.
My heart just isn't in it anymore.
Now that the anime with the
cute maid girls is over,
there's a gaping hole in my heart.
There's no reason left for me to live.
Can I take your orbear, sir?
Wait, what are you making me do?!
That's very, very close!
But I'm only interested in
the two-dimensional world!
Sorry!
What's this?
What are you doing?!
How can this be?!
Commence Hacking
It's the autonomous hacking
program I made when I got mad!
Hacking?!
Warning: An unknown program
has hacked into UNI.
Oh, no!
Damn! What's it trying to do
by taking over the UNI System?
A new bear ear system has been
set up inside the UNI System.
Currently sending mass data on bunny
ears, kitty ears, and doggy ears...
Load increasing... Load increasing...
Oh, my God!
It's going to overload the
system and burn out our server!
Huh?! Does that mean...
If the power surge is strong enough
to burn out the UNI System,
it'll blow up this entire building!
Girls, help me!
Okay!
Order it to cancel!
Count.
Ready.
3, 2, 1, Control!
Alt!
Delete!
Uh-oh... We failed!
The load is still growing!
Load
Bear ear system,
initiating self-destruct program.
Jeez, it's so fast!
This pop-up speed is incredible...
Bear ear system self-destruct
program has been installed.
Pull out the LAN cables!
Roger!
This'll buy us a little more time,
if only minutes at best.
Yama-san, why did you do such a thing?
I created UNI System as an autonomous
distributed system using bunny-ear,
kitty-ear, and puppy-ear girl AI.
But then I discovered bear ears,
and they stole my heart.
I wanted to add bear ears too,
but it wasn't allowed.
So I locked myself in here
and made it on my own.
Yama-san...
Can't anything be done?
There is a way.
Yama-san!
We'll do an anti-bear ear
reverse-hack on the UNI System.
Luckily, there's still
a bug in the UNI System.
We'll use this bug as our
back door to reprogram UNI.
In other words, it's a counter attack!
Yama-san!
Whoa! It's started!
The bear ears have initiated the
UNI System's self-destruct program.
We'll reprogram UNI right now!
Due to excessive data recovery, the
server has burnt out and will detonate.
Yama-san, will we make it on time?
Not if we do it the normal way!
The detonation radius will
encompass the entire building.
We're deviating!
But we're not supposed to deviate!
Shut up! I'm in charge
of the specifications now!
Amazing! Yama-san is writing
directly in machine language!
Twenty seconds until explosion.
Yama-san, hurry!
Ah! The bunny ear system is down!
Bunny ear system is overheating.
Oh, no! Kitty ears are down, too!
Kitty ear system is overheating.
H-Hurry!
Seconds until explosion: 10... 9...
Yama-san!
Don't worry. We have a 300-millisecond buffer.
8... 7... 6...
Milliseconds?!
It's not zero or negative.
5... 4...
Okay, girls!
Yes!
3... 2...
Push it!
1... 0.
Self-destruct program aborted.
Yes!
It's a miracle!
We did it!
That's what HackaDolls are for!
Phew, what a relief... Hm?
*Don't push me
Oh, maybe now it's actually a game?
Remaining time