Episode 8: "Kind of Main Heroine-ish"
I'd better call for help...
"Help"
"Come right away"
"Cute girl"
The Personal Entertainment AI
that syncs up to you: HackaDoll!
Ah!
Oh, dear.
This is done for.
And I was trying to call for help...
I'm sorry!
Oh, but what an unusual outfit you're wearing!
Are you a foreigner?
Nice to meet you desu!
I am HackaDoll!
I don't care who you are, just please,
take me someplace high!
Um...
I don't know what she's saying.
I wonder what country she's from.
That's right! My translating device was broken!
Um...
Me. High. Place.
Take. Go. Please!
Please!
What's she saying?
I could make out "please."
We might be able to communicate.
High.
Place. Go.
My
planet's
mothership.
I will call for help.
Uh-huh...
"I haven't had a bowel movement in a week,
so please give me an enema." Right?
Very well!
That's completely wrong!
Looks like you were wrong.
Since she's not from here,
maybe she wants to go sightseeing?
Oh! Good idea!
Huh?
You can count on us!
We'll help you make progress
with your sightseeing!
First, let's go shopping!
Wah!
They just don't understand me!
Oh, what is this place?
Fashion Center
Shimaran
Ta-da! The pinnacle of fashion: Shimaran!
What do you think of this?
It's both cute and tough. It's cu-tough!
Huh?
That's not surprising.
Do you like those better?
They are cute.
Seems very heroine-ish.
Then let's make ourselves main heroines, too.
Yeah!
I need to contact the
mothership immediately!
Now, let's all go to some trendy spot together!
Where should we go?
Argh! I don't have time for this!
Yeah, good question...
But...
They don't seem like bad people...
C'mon, let's go!
Let's go, let's go.
I could stay with them for just a bit...
We'll advance you!
Well, where shall we go next?
I'm starving.
Want to go to a trendy café?
Leave it to us!
Chashumen      Beansprout      Pork Bone          Salt           Soy Sauce           Miso
.                              Ramen            Ramen           Ramen          Ramen             Ramen
Now for our next story.
Yesterday, at the International Armadillo
Lovers Society's convention in Tokyo,
What do you think?
Trendy, isn't it?
Yes, indeed.
Master! Four of the usual!
about 500 armadillo enthusiasts from
around Japan had passionate discussions
You got it.
Huh?
It looks surprisingly good.
Let's dig in.
about armadillos in their rounded form.
The Armadillo Lovers Society
was formed 25 years ago when...
This flavor!
These wavy noodles...
They hold the distinct flavor of wheat!
What is this?!
Of course it's delicious.
It seems to be meat, but it's
so tender, it melts in my mouth...
And this broth...
The soy sauce flavor isn't overpowering.
It's perfectly balanced...
This aroma that fills my nostrils...
It's fermented dried bonito.
Amazing!
Pops! Seconds, please!
You got it.
Okay!
I am presently at the tallest broadcasting
tower in the world: Tokyo Skytree!
Oh! That place would work!
I can call for help from there!
The Skytree's height is 634 meters,
a play on words with "Musashi."
The world's tallest broadcasting tower!
What scenery can one see from it?
Do you want to go there?
Yes!
We're so high up!
It's kind of romantic.
Wow...
The people look like specks of dust.
The tour ends here!
Hand her over, now!
#4-chan?
What has this girl done?
She is an alien that we at
NASSA have been tracking.
"Hand her over peacefully,"
is what I'd like to say, but...
I'll give you a three minute headstart.
Nailed it.
I always wanted to say that at least once!
After them! After them!
A UFO?!
Thank you for helping me.
I am Princess Kirara of the planet Dena.
While I was on a tour of Earth,
I got separated from my tour group.
Miss HackaDoll...
This is a sign of good will on my planet.
I wish I could stay with you longer,
but I must go home now.
You're going home?
Yes. But I will never forget
my time with all of you.
Thank you.
Princess...
Well, this is goodbye!
Oh!
She's an animal!
I'm sorry for deceiving you.
This is my true form.
Princess...
Even if you are some kind of ham-star...
We're still BFFs!
Thank you.
HackaDolls...
Farewell.
Wait, damn it!
Wait— What?
What?!
Farewell!