Ouch!
And yet...
HackaDoll #1!
HackaDoll #1
HackaDoll #2
#2!
HackaDoll #3
#3!
HackaDoll #0
Episode 1: "Personal Entertainment AI! HackaDoll!"
You three were created to be
Personal Entertainment AI.
Our previously dispatched sisters
HackaDoll production
9 million produced!
Downloaded around the clock!
have been producing great results
for their respective masters.
And yet, you...
Since you're later models,
you do look like them,
but it seems there was a
drop in quality, because...
To put it bluntly,
you're junk.
Keep this up, and you can forget
about Personal Entertainment AI.
You'll be in the scrap heap.
What? No way!
Oh, dear...
But there must be something
that even you three can do.
Now that you've been created as HackaDolls,
it's time you earned your keep.
Yippee! I'm making my debut!
Now, now...
Huh? What are we supposed to do?
You three will be sent down to Earth,
where you will put your bodies on
the line to help humanity advance.
Our bodies?
I'll do it!
I'll work hard and become a proper HackaDoll!
Wh-What do we have to do, specifically?
Anything goes.
As long as it isn't morally offensive,
you will do any task, great or small.
Any task?
That's your cue.
Go forth, HackaDolls!
Go advance humanity!
Yes! I shall go forth and advance them!
Good luck!
Fight on.
That includes you two!
Rats.
Should've known!
Personal Entertainment... Whoa.
So this is a "HackaDoll"?
Oh. Looks like it's installed.
HackaDoll: Syncing to you.
News App
Open
Introducing a news app that syncs up
to you! News on anime, gaming, manga...
The Personal Entertainment
AI that syncs up to you...
HackaDolls!
Huh?
Nice to meet you!
I am HackaDoll #1!
Glad to be of service!
I'm #2.
#3.
So...
Yes?
Wait, huh?
Introducing a news app that syncs up to you!
News on anime, gaming, manga, voice actors,
light novels, tokusatsu... We bring you the
news you care about most! With HackaDolls,
your life experience will advance!
Check out all the
latest anime news!
We'll help you advance in anything!
Check now!
You just pop out like that?
Now, without further ado...
Wait, what were we supposed to do, again?
How to Be a HackaDoll
1: Perform a component analysis.
A component analysis is...
Oh, that's right!
Component analysis!
Ah! Wait!
Too bright! What's going on?!
A component analysis is
a HackaDoll skill that determines
her master's likes instantaneously.
I will explain.
A component analysis is...
M-My eyes...
Someone else read it.
How long does this last?!
A-A component analysis is
Too long! This is too long!
a HackaDoll skill that determines
her master's likes instantaneously.
Done!
I'll recommend all kinds of things
you might like, based on this!
Wh-What are you saying?
Let's see...
Are you guys insane?
Hey! Don't just...
Saiyuki Reload Blast
If you like this,
then you're sure to like this, too!
Hitorijime
Boyfriend
Huh?! Uh, that's not really...
And if you have these clothes...
Then this will look great on you!
What is this?!
I tried it on you.
Stop it!
Don't take my picture!
Recommending things that would
suit you perfectly, just like these,
is what we HackaDolls d— Ow!
Wait! Not that!
What is this?
Th-This is...
So my recommendations were spot-on after all!
Why are these people even here?
We came here to advance you!
How is this "advancing" me?
For starters, why not enter this in Comiket?
Absolutely not!
Where did you even get that idea?!
You're not making sense!
It's obvious you like it.
Well, yeah, I do like it...
But I suck at drawing.
I'm just a bandwagoner. Other people
draw much more intense stuff...
But what about...
What about the promise you made that day?
Was that a lie?
I don't think I can do it just yet.
But I swear I'll go to Comiket someday.
This is all I've got, after all!
Good luck.
Good luck!
Let's promise.
What about your promise?
I didn't promise that!
Seriously... What are you people?
We came here to advance you!
Were we useful to you?
Not in the least!
No! Don't say that!
At the rate we're going, we'll never
become full-fledged HackaDolls!
You're not even full-fledged yet?!
Please start advancing!
Rumble
All oden items are 70 yen
Welc'me!
She is quite a challenging case.
I can't make any recommendations!
She just isn't advancing at all.
How 'bout it?
I don't even care how.
I just wish she'd advance already.
All oden items are 70 yen!
Want some?
That's it!
Okamu Ippon
Jeez... Who were those girls anyway?
We have returned!
It's them again!
Ta-da!
Wh-What's that?!
It's oden!
Someone recommended it to us,
at the convenience store!
Here! Say "ah"...
Hey, don't...
Ouch! Ouch! That's hot!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! It's hot! It's hot!
Oh! But you ate it!
You've advanced!
You think that...
would advance me?!
Huh?!
Very well! I'll start over with
another component analys—
Just leave!
Please advance somehow!
Advance!
Overall Rating