Episode 13: "HackaDolls Can Handle Anything, Even Comiket"
You're getting married?
Yep!
C-Congratulations.
Thanks.
I hope you find someone soon, too, Aya-chan!
Yeah...
Oh, that's right.
I decided to go for it and make a
doujinshi for this year's Comiket.
Are you going as a guest or...
Aya-chan, you're still into that?
I quit being an otaku ages ago.
Oh... I see...
But you could still attend as a fan...
Aya-chan...
Just move on already.
Yuri-chan...
You're not young anymore.
You need to start thinking
about your future, your career.
Well...
You need to face reality.
No peeking, you pervert!
What's happening?
All oden items were 70 yen!
We are, as always...
Your Personal Entertainment AI, HackaDolls!
What is it this time?
Ahem!
Due to our stupendous efforts,
you reclaimed your otaku status
and began drawing doujinshi for Comiket.
Which is almost here!
So we came to see how your
manuscript is coming—
Huh?
Please leave.
What has happened?!
After all we did to advance you!
What in the world happened?
Hey, where's the rest of this?
Just stop it, please!
My manuscript is in there!
What?
Why?
Why? Because I realized something.
It's time to stop being an otaku and face reality.
Don't say that! Let's go to Comi—
I'm not going!
Ayame-san...
Please leave.
HackaDolls? More like "hacks"!
All you do is force me to do what you want.
Don't ever come here again!
HackaDoll
Uninstalled
#3-chan...
Yeah.
You, too!
You look so happy.
Ayame-san, you look so happy!
You were having so much fun.
How can you suddenly hate it now?
Stop lying to yourself!
I don't hate it...
I just think I'm too old for it.
I can't keep running from reality...
You can't run from your feelings
and call it "running from reality"!
It's okay to like what you like!
Age has nothing to do with it!
I will advance you, Ayame-san!
I'll chase you to the ends of Hell
to advance you if I have to!
That is our duty as your Personal
Entertainment AI, HackaDolls!
I think!
You're crazy...
I'll make you crazy!
What?!
Er... I mean, I'll advance you like crazy!
Oh, fine!
All right already.
But I have to start from scratch,
since I crumbled it up.
And there's no time.
Can you help me with my manuscript?
Yes!
Okay, time for some serious advancing!
I've gotta recharge first...
Hey! Don't fall asleep already!
I don't like this pairing...
Please don't say that.
Are we really going to get this done?
I am Chief Comiket!
My name is Comi-shima Ket-nosuke!
Please clear the way!
We're attending Comiket—
Little ones, you are nowhere
near ready for Comiket.
Behold the other attendees!
Gimme five copies of the new book!
What a lovely day!
Can I look at this?
Yes.
Y-You mustn't run at Comiket!
#3-chan, watch out!
#3-chan!
Why did this happen?
Okay, that's enough.
Zero-nee?
If you can't even advance someone at this level,
it's time you were scrapped!
Not at Comiket!
#1-chan!
#2? #3?
You're next, #1.
How dare you turn my
best friends into dust?!
Well, shall we begin?
Z-Zero-nee!
#4-chan!
#1... If we don't do something,
#0 will destroy this convention
center and everyone in it.
#4...
Please protect my beloved
convention center and otaku...
Stay out of this, you useless failure.
Y-You transformed?
Impossible! I can't be...
#2... #3... #4... You guys...
#1-chan!
#1!
#1...
I'm not sure how, but you did it!
You guys... Yes.
I did it! I advanced!
#1-chan. #1-chan.
I advanced...
You were fast asleep, #1-chan.
We did pull an all-nighter.
Huh? It was a dream? No way!
Um, did we do a good job advancing your work?
It really was crazy.
But...
It was fun, and we did finish the doujinshi.
So I guess you did advance my work.
Thank you so much!
I'd like that in writing.
Ditto.
Well, since you've advanced me plenty,
you should go advance lots of other people.
I'm sure they're waiting for you.
Good morning.
Day 1 of Comic Market 89 will now commence.
Well, let's get going!
We need to keep advancing people.
Yes! Personal Entertainment AI,
HackaDolls, can handle anything,
even Comiket!