Episode 2: "Please Let Us Be Idols!"
What...
is this?
Triple booking? No...
Fourth booking?
The correct phrase is "quadruple booking."
Guess I screwed up...
But!
Solving messes like this is
what makes a great producer!
What's three or four events?
I can fill this schedule...
No, I couldn't!
Damn it!
I just can't fill this last slot!
If only there were an agency that could
introduce me to an idol who's free...
What you need is...
The Personal Entertainment AI
that syncs to you: HackaDoll!
H-HackaDoll?!
The AI that can advance
any part of a person's life?!
Now that we're here, you can rest at ease!
We will be in the event that has an opening!
Huh? You weren't going to
introduce me to an idol?
We don't need to do that!
Look!
Look at what we can do!
Isn't that CG?
Shh!
We're going to be idols?
We'll wear cute costumes, sing, dance,
make everyone go "squee!" for us...
It's every girl's dream!
I think you just want to do this.
I appreciate the offer, but...
Please!
I promise we'll advance your company,
so please let us be idols!
But I don't want to trouble the sponsor—
Please let us be idols!
But this is a very important event—
Let us be idols!
There are a few days left until the event.
If you'd just give us a chance
and let us prove ourselves...
Yeah, but—
Let us!
Fine!
We'll start you off with some lessons.
Okay!
IWS
Idol Agency
We're ready to start!
And so, our days of taking lessons began.
Running...
Hopping...
Hand-shaking practice...
Photo sessions...
This...
Ikebukuro Girls CD Shop                  HackaDolls                  Autograph Signing
might just work.
At last, the big day is here!
What a huge audience.
I'm nervous...
Today's event is very special.
Special?
Yes. The winner of today's event
gets to release a debut CD
from a major record label.
What?! D-Debut?
Only if you win.
Oh, right! No problem!
It's almost time. Get ready!
18:00~18:30         HackaDolls
Bathroom!
Now I'm really nervous...
Did you hear? There's a
last-minute replacement today.
Oh, you mean the group that
claims they can "advance" people?
They're making a mockery of idols.
They're probably nothing special.
Yeah, I don't really get them.
I'm sure they won't get great results.
But we worked really hard for this!
I know we can do it!
But maybe the audience
won't be satisfied with us...
I want to be an idol,
but if the audience doesn't get excited,
then I can't advance the producer's career...
But I wonder if anyone will even watch us.
Girls...
Producer...
All idols struggle with that insecurity.
And it's the miracle of overcoming
that insecurity to stand on the stage
that the audience is here to see.
I'm already excited to see what kind
of miracles you girls will perform.
Remember how badly you wanted to be an idol?
And you want to advance my career, right?
Don't worry!
I'm sure there'll be people watching you.
Now, go make miracles!
Okay!
We're still in the girls' bathroom...
Who's next?
HackaDolls?
Last-minute filler?
Oh, I know them.
The ones who can "advance" anything.
Oh, them?
So they can be idols, too?
Awesome!
Nice to meet you all! We are...
HackaDolls!
We practiced lots to become idols today!
Please listen to our song,
"Cabbage Testing"!
Cabbage Testing
Lyrics: Ikuo Geso
Composition: Daisuke Horita
These vibrations...
The building itself is resonating!
Did I mess up?
Not at all!
#1-chan, you were great!
Your soul reached me!
It was the best!
Thank you so much!