Whenever you're in trouble,
you can count on Mobami-chan!
Hey, #1.
Do you like anime?
I love it! Especially Mobami-chan.
It's the greatest!
That's perfect for me.
The company that makes that anime is
understaffed and having all kinds of problems.
Go help advance them.
Huh?!
Awesome! On my way!
In the anime production studio...
The men spending nights
sleeping at their desks
are about to meet a HackaDoll.
Episode 7: "KUROBAKO"
Excuse me...
Are you that HackaDoll they say
can help advance anything?
Y-Yes, I am!
I am a Personal Entertainment AI
that syncs up to you: a HackaDoll!
Oh, you can skip that stuff.
Okay.
Mobami-chan
#07
"KUROBAKO"
I'm going to have you help with
the anime Mobami-chan's
seventh episode, "KUROBAKO."
What? Awesome!
You can count on me! I'll do anything!
Am I a key animator?
An animation director?
You're doing the same task
as me: production assistant.
Huh? What's that?
Production has the crappy task
of coordinating all departments,
including key animation,
inbetweens, filming, and editing.
Huh? I love anime, though,
so I'll give it my all!
Is that so?
Don't try to escape.
30 Days Until Airing
Um, I'm calling about the
key frames for Mobami-chan...
Oh, you can't do it this month?
Then what about next month?
You can't predict your schedule?
You can't stand the director anyway?
This is crap... Crap... Crap...
O-Okay... Goodbye.
I'll use you for a character design.
All fifty turned me down,
one after another.
Stop crying and keep working.
Ack!
20 Days Until Airing
Y-Yes?
We're going to collect the key frames.
Go. Hop to it.
O-Okay...
Excuse me! I've come for the key frames.
Hello!
Seems like they're inside.
Um...
Here it is!
Give them a second
touch-up, please.
Huh?
What does this mean?
You have to start over again from the layout.
14 Days Until Airing
You've gotta be kidding me!
Huh? I didn't realize #4-chan was also here.
No way can we have this all done in two days.
B-But Hagiyama-san has put together 100 cuts.
The art and filming departments
say they can't wait any longer.
You think I care?
Making things meet the deadline is your job.
The post-process doesn't concern you.
I'm going to work down to the last second.
Sheesh, what a useless production assistant.
I can't take it anymore!
Okay, take over where she left off.
Huh?!
7 Days Until Airing
Y-Yes?
TIme for the after-recording.
Huh?
Awesome! I get to meet voice actors!
Oh, maybe I'll get some autographs.
I didn't get to meet the voice actors.
It doesn't even feel like we're
working on the same project.
They live in a completely different world.
Okay, let's go collect key frames.
I-I'm so bummed!
6 Days Until Airing
#1-chan?
Y-Yes? Is the inbetweening done?
I brought this for you.
Have you been sleeping okay?
Ah... Y-Yeah.
Oh, sorry! Wait just a minute.
I'm back.
Huh? #1-chan, did you go take a shower?
Yeah... I washed my hair in the bathroom.
I haven't bathed in a week.
#1-chan...
It was nothing like what I imagined.
Everyone is so strained, and irrational...
I wanna go home!
Oh, dear.
But you can't. You need to
stick it out until the end.
If you run away,
all the fans looking forward to
the anime will be disappointed.
But...
Come on, we'll help you.
Right?
We'll help.
Let's work hard together.
O-Okay!
Let's all work hard together!
Key Frames: 540 cuts
Number of Drawings: 12,800
Number of Runaways: 1 (HackaDoll #4)
Revenue: In the red
HackaDoll #3
Healthy
HackaDoll #2... Healthy
HackaDoll #1... Healthy
Day of Airing
Whenever you're in trouble, you can count on—
Well... I guess that'll do.
Good work, Director.
Once we take this disc to the
station in Osaka, we're done...
But we won't make it in time.
Ugh... We totally dropped the ball on this one.
Hey...
A recap episode, eh?
And the third one this cour.
A miracle
didn't happen.
You're wrong!
A miracle will happen.
I'll make it happen!
#1?
HackaDolls can do it!
The three of us will go together to Osaka!
Advancing this company is our mission!
We made the delivery!
You girls...
Good work.
Th-Thanks!
I look forward to working
with you on episode 8!
Now I know that anime is best enjoyed at home!