You're the reason I my cherry opponent
My name is Tomoe
Good, including the love road bought by Hey
Hey because are disabled even if the game without between the sum it is Tarunada of Stop referee
That's right of Fussaｰ
Gentleman thief Heuristic of the wilderness again a 10% decline in after the in
Request is simple
Do Taurus Anta of the entire fortune to me
Kohler Anta also bid and Negai
Yes desire to be a beginner just one
Reverse
Ten thousand underlying motive Kudasaima-chan
Oh Oh
Ah
Moe Chan It Hey's Dameru wishes after
The winner of the Queen's Blade than able to grant any wish
I'd have is alleged the man underlying motive
So I do it not I grant You're wish
You okay Queen's Blade final winner is possible any wish
Chau short
understood
In the Heuristic of
I Can not Please clean the entrance of the arena you buy
clean up
Somthing not Do it well of the sound guy
Come to someone I'd seen the weight that occurred Municipal rice
Fight the model all did their easy Tsukai heel Shiryoku Prince
Was'm Queen's Blade
Inclusive but amateur 0
Said Did you cause the results are in
[musics]
earena
Eeeeee
Oh
There is no after another
Atomurai's is more of you
Ah ah ah
Eeeeee
Tsu I'm sorry
Tsu did not Mairi is to mean that disconnect one
I mean there
Wish street of losing her Dariwa here
It ruled Italy
Nja bad yo ni
Rusha Yoshikinkoe
It is interesting Yoshitoshi
Which was
No I do not want to in the if me up around here
Yes Welcome Well
ladies and gentlemen
Hahhahha'
It is one generation, but I'm not Kudasara to accept
Not carry in this state 's also heavy luggage
The regular enter good thing it is something that I give to you
It is not that going stole from me
Keep remember well the place of there
erina's
Not ride in tone
I slow
Sue
Sumuno' in yoriko wait
My name is Mara kingdom of the princess Menace today
[musics]
Say please and at all fell down
I'm coming with riding pony
It does not bring to the end of the next but forgive
Just had bored
Thank you I was wondering whether enjoyable journey can be if it is possible to be talking about something
not
I did you need a Pontsu follow Child-like
This kind of older sister sharp as
That's right he will put up Seriously
Even the floating wow really
It comes with
Yes, please put the irie luggage
Hmm
Menace's Thanks
I think Why are you know a cup of everyone so there is also a
Hey increasing please sell me was in this
I do not go to why
Not return
Show the way
We would have seen you staring
What things
I Toka Menace Kkeu
please
High woman revealing say your army is white or the favorite
First, such a thing is's a ministry of persons who control also to an attractive appearance Well
I also fell a little more
Which was
I think that everyone's enough attractive as it stands
Han'
Naa Ja Attarimae
We are accustomed to hear
Sorry to keep you waiting
slow
We do have to ensure the best inn in good with street town Une
I burn
Not be taken in my day
So we have a formidable Yoshitoshi in the continent
Ikena is the thing
When you prepare the idea to
Well
And seemed queen aldolase like is set to visit us in town
Where is also Kind regards tossed Nasty
Nice to meet you
Edge of even something became the warrior priestess will light Tomoe thus the same room
Thank you very much
Ha ha ha
Ne it is the bottom of the hunting
Even without taking yuina is fine, but Urso Mikosama I
I wonder a little put out a total of to my slave
It can not be overlooked as a ministry of ruling party
We rude
Help the weak pay magic
It is a warrior shaman teacher
I leave immediately
Yes
Michelle How to Uo'
Meet, etc.
that
I wonder if such think that
It regards the child you were a child today is to help the weak pay Well
U'u Please wait
Well you
Excuse me something
I have heard the strongest forces of Hinomoto Speaking warrior priestess
'S supposed to be dependable than the poor Knights amulet
There is more of
He who also dominate the know that in other countries
And I did not even feel like dabble in children
There Yoshitoshi in the city of arena
I received
Gentleman thief location of wilderness
Naa's face that can not be seen
b pitcher I Erinu
2 Tsuna
Good to may not come up before the angels come to decide the appropriate two names
a is better to put the favorite on their own
Open the seat 9 net
Fought your previous
One day I want to ask you about that time
Remember one by one
Tsu that of Allah losing opponent
Have
Iiii courage
Always it is said
Ah ah ah
play
Is just two people had left the house
Pressure to very much
[musics]
Rice
Entered Michelle's
Are you sure you want to talk a little
Yes
Do I what kind of your relationship with that selfish personage
Winter
You if ride to the consultation if you are badly treated as slaves
That kind of you
Is that so
It was a little outgoing
I'm friendly
Tomoe's Queen's Blade 2 for what
I'd like to cure a person of illness
Elixir Man underlying motive've heard that there is in this continent
If we continue to win the Queen's Blade should be able to get
I think of
Used without hesitation When you have that there is a means to save the others to their own
Use and Queen's Blade is the means for me
Thank you for that
The reason for fight
We can confirm again
It is likely to overlook the battle without Yuruko thanks
Thank asked in response to the call
Nanaeru
Give me to thank Ha Oh Oh Oh
What I'm also'm pretty busy the US requirements
Simply strong I think you try to open a sight game
Only only beautiful appearance early tricks
Such Queen's Blade Haa is he was already Miaki
Naa's selfish
Will those things is the Queen
Yes summons but Yoshitoshi
There is one person decided another
It Tomoe
I saw cherry blossoms
The problem is the opponent
Well Cow us to introduce If there are interesting Yoshitoshi
Hmm
Have one person that a small number of games to have raised appointed to select local
Hey I just say do not run away if the sight game
Busy because this side Den
I no longer
Thing I want you to be a Yoshitoshi with 8 beat force
a-N-A
Return of her husband like 8 Usa house smell rice
[musics]
Hey, I wonder not it terrible What smell a girl
A little wet
eh
Hmm
Ah ah ah
I wonder if looking at the trends
It went by me anywhere
Hahhahha'
Relax please Huh
I went a little Anataa
Hey, would not or attacked No way To before
Some of that Do Myochikirin costumes
It was atmosphere that concealed a wayward body without me
I prefer to say Oh would not why
Hey, I wonder if you like black-inclusive
I think it was a rice eggplant of black hair Speaking
I do not even know well that of Tomoe's'm Sonnanja Neyo
[musics]
eh
Gan'
I wonder also cool hangovers When you wipe this
Ah
Rough up
Naa Ja like a yo and fairly, then stop to motivate
Yomeane Oh so much Seyome-chan
a-N-A
Also a gonna say no good
O'o'
It is natural
A place like this at up to lawmakers of love, such as
Outrageous is N forward
But I'm was just playing a little above
Welcome
Thus the request dissatisfied Koshiro is
Lie told us position
Behold with the current dimensions think that it is above its
Man
I think you good sound is not put out
Ah
There are some knowledge
[musics]
More Kuchiko 4 Mr. Nakya
Ah ah Aan
Ischl 3
I'll be sure to help
Huh
here
Refuse
9 wonder if not it is better to Doi or because I do not sleep Nante invitation from the mine
I only became Yoshitoshi in the course of events I do not know somehow or 's your game
Not a have time to participate in such a thing
Since I gait of gay older sister was finally grasp
Naa so there is a clue to get to the rough Marks
Or Rena and chopsticks also to the
Kin'no chocolate
Huh enter that warrior priestess is
Oh I take it by the early in the morning soon
goo
Though provided him in the directions song notes of up to origin of a fire
Elina like in that was after the Kyubei
I had better refrain little because be a vicious drinker I'm bad
Absolute position I see
I think it is better to 嘗胆 was received respectfully to Dan' Tara sight game
em N
Numbness I'm healed
All right
You indeed I fight
Hmm
You have to like the kind of thing I
Hey Airi's
me
I 5
Yes
John aldolase like Ow
[musics]
Oma
It was Joe and acquaintance
Warrior is mana Miko Tomoe
The sound of the ultra-aldolase say 9 will those who stand here
Well like I'll resistance want vile in western six-party us to
Let's give tell us firsthand the what a justice
Hey, that was me saying well with resistance vile
Not to say that the forgotten dream of it
Toshiha unexpected squid also boy address that such a crisis after 10
Said two people I mine or the attempt to treat what, It 's my belongings
So there Maderun
Order in the name of Queen aldolase
While good thy collar of r in Yoshitoshi
Use all-held
Oh warrior priestess and the fight
Han'
2 Toga was decided
If not closed Nanaeru-like Chan
Wow I'll put that kind of two names
It falls short of that of a prima facie Nee Well Nyamimyi
ChaErina the flowers come with a Zekkage
Haga those that prevent tracking and juice of the blade
day
Tomoe
Emergency vulgaris the game
Chopper
Depiction request of the room
What if I was to win
I wonder what about if the person is doing slave advanced goods
Well to say that since there should cry
My request is the think you say that to your slaves
It made 8 shoes
day
Over where the request was together
We summer of spares all-held the have fighters showed a good fight
me
[musics]
so
Eeeeee
san
[musics]
wh
Ne 's do
Welcome to
[musics]
me
I put both support point of view
Results could be even if Mote
Hey Rina like is I wonder if I think that abandonment is a bother to the slaves
Do I worry
Was I there is a mission that must be fulfilled in that person
Oh Oh
ni
Ah ah ah
[musics]
This article
wh
car
Oh Nante eupa Taka
Write Which of seeing taste Zillah is
so
Exit this match,
I wonder do is
Tracking of vehicles of Saint Zekkage
Ah
Owwa
Sorry, angel-like
Tomoe is not likely fulfill the served
Well I think I you know is what happens more than I was also victory
Ah
Order to Tomoe as a trading company
Take took us to Hinomoto
Dot
Because me
So're saying please and insect who guides the
Ai'
Yes
This my guide who s the ugly Nante's naked
Milton
Show me a professor of Yoshitoshi of force
Good equipment receive but
Oh
It is word 剱
Is to help any time of the journey as long as it is a queen if there
not
This this is that whistle
Over try blowing
Do you even want
Not only healed
me
also
It does Mase Ottoe
Tsu scary
But
Tired Toka kind of Panay in Toka easing pain
That is to Michel whistle there is a strange effect to heal wounds and disease
I So I numbness of the arm were gone before the match
It may fulfill also the purpose of Tomoe's if there is this force
True the crust the crust the crust the crust the crust
I wanted to teach early
Hey, since immediate edition b-kun Bikun and it was not far from it anymore violently
Thank you
Ah ah ah
It is a fee of departure to the original
Wow chase Ino spirits like