What a bad luck for you to be my opponent.
Warrior Priestess Tomoe, presents herself.
Hizan!
All right, let's see who the winner will be!
Even if you play the game without the light of the referee's angel Nanael.
Is that true?
Yes.
Then, let me declare the start of the match!
Right.
Wilderness Bandit Risty.
My request is simple.
You will give me your entire fortune.
Come on, decide your wish too.
Y-Yes.
Warrior Priestess Tomoe, my wish is only one.
Please give me your pussy tape.
Pus-sy tape?
Huh?
Uh, Tomoe-chan, that's not a good wish.
Huh? Shouldn't the Queen's Blade
winner have any wish granted?
I don't have that pussy tape you say.
So you can't fulfill your wish.
But no problem, the Queen's Blade final winner will make any wish come true.
Premonition of parting
Understood.
Then Risty-san,
If I win,
would you like to clean the entrance to the arena?
Clean up?
You are an ordinary one.
I don't care.
Right, give us a good fight, Bitoushis!
Since you make use of all your strength, this should provide us a good battle.
Fight for Queen's Blade!
Here I go!
Be cautelous, lady in white!
This was just a first warning.
I don't want to give you scars.
Let's see how long can you endure that pose of yours.
You have nowhere to run.
It's you who don't have where to run!
Please forgive me, but I wasn't intending to loose.
I admit lost, that sucks.
So, the winner is the Warrior Priestess Tomoe!
The loser Risty must fulfill Tomoe's wish, so take it well.
You cannot recuse you know,
or there will be a punished.
Warrior Priestess Tomoe, what an interesting Bitoushi.
If you come to that area I don't care
You are right, welcome, Airi.
Yes, Elina-sama.
Depending on
You won't take it
At this rate, I can't carry heavy luggage anymore.
That's a good thing, Airi.
I will give you my vital energy here.
It's not something I'll take away from me.
Remember the octopus well that moment.
Elina-sama.
Don't get too excited!
It's taking too long.
Noriko it's the same.
Hello there.
I am Menace, the Princess of the Amara Kingdom.
Please let me take you to Pico.
O-kay.
There are a lot of customers, you know.
I would do it gladly, but the next city is not so close.
I was just a little bored,
and nothing interesting was going to happen.
I was wondering what kind of funny adventure could be waiting for me.
Thank you, but...
Ora ora.
It seems like your companion came.
Elina-sama, this kind lady is saying
she will take us to the next town.
Uow, it's really floating.
Yes, I've arrived here with it.
Airi, help me put the stuff.
Ok.
It's all yours.
Thank you very much, Menace-sama.
Airi-san, how do you know her name?
Hey, this carpet, sell it for me.
That's something I can't do.
Speaking of which Michel,
you was taking a good luck.
What are you talking about?
Menace tits.
Huh?
Please let me take you to Pico.
Do you like women with a high degree of exposure?
T-That's not true at all.
Well, to have an attractive appearance Dominating Start working.
Me too
Elina-sama, you are not
being yourself right now.
I think it's attractive.
That's obvious.
I'm used to listening
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Take too long.
I guess you have secured the best inn in the town.
About it...
I still can't get numb.
There are tough Bitoushi on the continent.
I cant, no at a moment like this.
Airi to bring me here, pure joke.
It seems like the Queen Aldra-sama is in the town.
All the places here are full.
Nice to meet you.
Warrior Priestess Tomoe, presents herself.
Gaske verb also has something to do with
Thank you very much
Stop right there you, I know you from!
It's fine for me but something,
Warrior Priestess-sama, I...
If you dare to handle my slave.
As a ruler, I will not forgive you.
I'm sorry for my behaviour.
As a Mao duty to Help the weak
That's what a Warrior Priestess is taught to do.
I'll be out soon.
Ok.
What are you going to do?
Eh? I-I dont know...
Well...
I wonder what Tomoe is goingo to do.
After all, if a grace that helps weaknesses is available,
I'm leaving the boy with your hands.
Huh? W-What?
Are you sure, Elina-sama?
I'm sorry for this.
It's fine.
Speaking of a Warrior Priestess,
I heard about Hinomoto’s strongest force.
t should be a talisman that can be relied upon by a poor Knights
You are detailed
Knowing about other countries,
it's the basics for domination.
Besides, I didn't feel like touching my child.
Bitoushi that dominate people in the arena.
I found you.
Wilderness Bandit Risty!
I don't recognize your face, are you a Bitoushi?
I'm Elina.
Elina, so?
It's just you two?
I think that is plenty enough.
A angel told me she was bringing two women to me.
It seems like you found me first.
Here it is.
Oh, that's convenient.
You fought before, I want to ask about Bitoushi.
I remember each one.
Is that so? Then what about the one you lose?
It’s a good courage.
Come anytime you want!
Only two people turned me around.
Tomoe and...
Leina.
Leina onee-sama?
Hey, Elina-sama!
Michel-san?
Yes?
Can we talk a little?
Yes.
That selfish person, what kind
of relationship do you have?
Well...
If you're being treated so badly as to be taken off, I'll take a consultation.
There's no need of it.
If you are saying.
This relieved me a little.
You are so gentle.
Tomoe-san, why are you fighting in Queen's Blade?
I want to cure one's illness.
100 I heard that there is Mantan on this continent
You can get the Queen's Blade if you keep winning
Tomoe-san?
Yes?
If you have a way to save others,
would you use it without hesitation?
I would use.
For me, Queens Blade is the means to make it possible.
Hum...
Thank you.
I could confirm the reason for fighting again.
Thanks to this, I can understand what it takes to fight.
Thank you for accepting the call, Nanael.
Right, right, keep your gratitude.
Then, what's the matter? I'm very busy you know.
I think I'll open a match.
Just strong, only the technique is fast, that looks beautiful,
I'm tired of seeing that Queen's Blade.
This is a little selfish don't you think?
That's what being a Queen is all about.
Yes, yes.
I' laready decided likely to empathize One.
The Warrior Priestess Tomoe.
Oh, that girl.
The question is who will be the opponent.
If there are interesting Bitoushi, can you introduce me?
I have not appointed a beautiful fighter, but one person with few strong numbers.
I can't escape in the morning and it's just right
Ops, I need to hurry or it will be bad.
Wish's Devil, The death of someone with the power to defeat what I want.
Give to your master a harm welcome!
You smell like beer.
Dont you think it's rude say a girl has bad smell?
Wait, huh?!
Wonder where are you looking.
W-Where, you say?
take your time
Hey, you.
Y-Yes?
Dont tell me,
I wouldn't have been attacked by Tomoe
Huh?
That woman, In the life of Myochi Kirin
It was a ridiculously selfish atmospher e.
That's not true.
I like that. I wonder if I also like black hair.
Now that I remember, Menace's hair was black too.
It's not like that.
You know nothing about Tomoe-san.
If I blow this, I wonder if my sickness will cool down.
Ora, I don't think I'm very motivated
Don't do it.
If you do it that way, I will...
You say no but you really do like.
No, I said no!
Such as vulgar acts in such plac es?
Ora, I just played a little more, but...
Vulgar?
By chance Am I frustrated?
That's obviously a lie!
If you think it's a lie, see it by yourself.
Well, I don't think you can
make a good sound anyway.
You are wrong, if it's Tomoe...
I have some knowledge.
You need to include more in your mouth.
Michel-san,
I will save you, it's a promisse.
I refuse.
I rarely invite myself, you never know when there will be another chance.
I don't know what is a exhibition
match, but I was just a prospect.
I have no time to participate in such things.
After all, I need to follow the footsteps of Leina onee-sama.
I've finally served, so there seems to be a clue to how to get to Maramax.
Leina was heading to Hinomoto.
Hinomoto.
Airi, where is that Warrior Priestess?
Who knows, she left early this morning.
Damn, I was planning to ask
her to guide us to Hinomoto.
Was sloppy last night because drink too much.
Elina-sama, drinking too much is very bad.
You should refrain a little.
Shut up!
So, that's how it is.
In this case I think it's better to
have it at home in the morning.
My wounds got healed.
It's all right.
I will fight.
So, that's how it is.
It's you?
That's what it seems.
Hey, Airi-san.
Is that...
Who I'm thinking?
Yes, that's Queen Aldra-sama.
Menace-san!
So she is friend of the Queen.
I am the Warrior Priestess Tomoe.
, the price of Queen Aldora, Yuuki
I want you to go into vulgarity, and I want all those to be whipped out.
I want to finish showing what justice is.
You used to say that the quality is poor, last night.
I will not forgot what I saw.
A boy's address that is too old
How do you handle those two because they belong to me
It's my self Touhou
That's enough talk for you two.
In the name of Queen Aldra,
Elina, now that you are officialy a
Bitoushi, show us your strength.
Fight with the Warrior Priestess.
Do you two already decided?
If not decided, me, Nanael-sama, will decide myself!
Let me see, hum...
What about meow-meow ears?
That's not going to happen.
I am the Pursuer of Solitude, Elina!
Those who block the enemy are fated to disappear with the dew of the blade!
Warrior Priestess Tomoe!
Let's set this duel!
All right, let's start it!
If I win, you will release the slave!
Wonder who is the person
you are calling a slave.
Well, fine.
I won't lose anyway.
My request is Tomoe,
you will become my slave.
I-Is that allowed?
Very well, we are gathered here for a reason.
Now, show us a great battle!
Bitoushis, show all your strength and bring us fun.
With this Queen's Blade battle!
I have no choice.
This is bad!
Get ready!
Oh, nothing bad.
I say the same.
It doesn't matter who's gonna win, please support both.
T-That's obvious.
Tell me, was Elina-sama serious about turning Tomoe-san into her slave?
Are you worried for her?
Yes, she has a mission to fulfill
Thats news to me.
It's decided!
I wont allow it.
The victory is mine!
What is this?
Don't let your guard down!
You are stubborn.
But I don't have even a scratch!
I declare the end of the match, with this.
And the winner is...
The Pursuer of Solitude, Elina!
I'm so sorry, angel-sama.
I don't think I will be able to be a good servant.
Now, with my uncontestable victory,
you know what's going to happen.
As the winner, I demand the Warrior Priestess Tomoe...
All of us, you will take to Hinomoto.
T-That's why you make me your slave.
That's right.
So you have nothing to worry
with me being your master.
Airi!
Right.
It’s not that bad to be naked.
Elina, congratulations.
You showed me the strength of a gracious Bitoushi.
Good to receive
That is my testimony.
The Queen's influence has no limits,
it will help in your journey.
Tomoe-san, take it.
This is that flute.
Try it.
But, are you sure?
Be kind, please?
After all, the sound doesn't come out.
No, but...
Tired, feeling pain or anything.
Now that you say...
Michel's flute Cures wounds and illness, Has a nice effect
So before the match...
It was becoming
With this power, maybe Tomoe-san's purpose could be fulfilled.
I really wanted to tell you sooner but,
I coudn't.
Drop this chicken act,
that's not a behaviour I can forgive.
Thank you, Michel-san.
I'm very grateful.
Very well!
Let's departure to Hinomoto!
Leina onee-sama is waiting for us!