That's why you are my partner
Warrior Priestess Tomoe.
Even if you play the game without the light of the referee's angel Nanael,
That's right
Then, let me declare the start of the match!
Right.
Wilderness Bandit Risty.
My request is simple.
You will give me your entire fortune.
Cola
You also aim for Nazoid
Yes
Warrior Miko Tomoe There is only one hope
Please **
Huh?
Ah, Tomoe-chan, that's not a good wish.
Shouldn't have the qb chellenger May any wish be granted
I have that kind of guy
So you can't fulfill your wish
But no problem, Queen's Blade The final winner will make any wish come true
Premonition of parting
understood
Then Risty-san,
If i win
Would you like to clean the entrance to the arena?
clean up
Hey motivated guy
I don't care
Right, give us a good fight, Bitoushis!
How to make use of all motels
Are you tired
How long can i endure
You have nowhere to run
You don't have an ATM
I didn't like my neck
I admit lost, that sucks
So, the winner is the Musha Miko Tomoe!
Don't sleep with your phone closed
Warrior Miko Tomoe, what an interesting Bitoushi.
If you come to that area
I don't care
You are right, welcome, Airi.
Yes, Elina-sama.
Depending on
You won't take it
I can't carry heavy luggage anymore
Good thing Airi
Genitals
I give you
It's not something I'll take away from me
Remember the octopus well
Elina-sama.
I don't feel well
It's taking too long.
Noriko
it's the same
Manicure
I am Menas, the Princess of the Born Kingdom
Please lie down on Pico
There are many others, but next month
I'm just bored
Thank you,
Ora ora.
Your companion came
Elina-sama,
It seems that this kind lady will take us to the town.
Uow, it's really floating.
I've arrived
Airi, help me put the stuff.
Thank you very much, Menas-sama.
Why do you know your name
Hey you
This carpet, sell it to me, that's not the case
Speaking of which Michel,
you was taking a good luck.
What are you talking about?
Woman strike
Huh?
Let people decide
you Are you Do you like women with a high degree of exposure?
no way
To have an attractive appearance Dominating Start working
Me too
Erina-sama Yes, just as it is
I think it's attractive
Not obvious
I'm used to listening
Sorry to keep you waiting
Take too long.
I guess I've secured the best inn in the town
that is
I still can't get numb
There are tough pits on the continent.
In such a thing
The Queen Aldra It looks like you're in the town
Everywhere is full
Nice to meet you
My name is Tomoe.
Gaske verb also has something to do with
Thank you very much
Stop right there you, I know you from
Fine but something
musha miko-sama I
If I dare to handle my slave, as a ruler
I will make you regret.
excuse me
As a Mao duty to Help the weak
Thats a musha miko mo kyouji
I'll be out soon
Yes
What you going to do?
Eh? I-I dont know...
Well...
I wonde r if I said Tomoe
Well
It ’s grace that helps weaknesses. is available
I'm leaving the boy with your hands.
huh?
Are you sure, Elina-sama?
Something
I'm sorry
It's fine.
Speaking of a warrior shrine maiden
Kinomoto ’s strongest force I'm listening one two Three
t should be a talisman that can be relied upon by a poor Knights
You are detailed
Knowing about other countries, Dominate
Besides, I didn't feel like touching my child
Dominate  people in the arena
I found it
Wilderness bandit Risty
The face I don't see B dentistry
I'm Erina
Erina, so?
It's just you two?
I can't t hink of  a good one before the electron decides on two suitable names
You should put the one you like
Here it is.
Oh, thats great.
You fought before
I want to ask about Albi investment
I remember each one
Then what about the oponnet you lose for?
It ’s a good courage
Come anytime you want
Only two people turned around
Tomoe and...
Reina
Reina-oneesama?
Hey, Elina-sama!
Michel-san...
Yes?
Can we talk a little?
Yes.
That selfish person, what kind of relationship do you have?
Well...
If you're being treated so badly as to be taken off
I'll take a consultation
There's no need of it.
Is that so
This relieved me a little.
You are so gentle.
Tomoe-san, why are you fighting in qb?
I want to cure one's illness
100 I heard that there is Mantan on this continent
You can get the Queen's Blade if you keep winning
Tomoe-san?
Yes?
If you have a way to save others
would you use it without hesitation?
I would use.
For me, Queens Blade is the means is what makes it possible.
Hum...
Thank you.
I can confirm the reason for fighting again
Thanks to me
Thank you for accepting the call, Nanael.
Right, right, keep your gratitude.
Then, what's the matter? I'm very busy you know.
I think I'll open a match
Just strong
Only the technique is fast
It looks beautiful
I'm tired of seeing what Queen's Blade
Well, I'm selfish
That's what being a queen is all about
Yes yes
I'm likely to empathize One has already decided
This is Tomoe
Oh, that girl.
The question is who the opponent is
If there are interesting Bitoushi, can you introduce me?
I have not appointed a beautiful fighter, but one person with few strong numbers
I can't escape in the morning and it's just right
From Niihama
The death of someone with the power to defeat what I want
Give to your master a harm welcome.
You smell like beer.
Dont you think its rude say a girl has bad smell?
Wait, huh?!
Where are y ou looking
Where training
take your time
Hey you
Dont tell me,
I wouldn't have been attacked by Tomoe
Huh?
That woman, In the life of Myochi Kirin
It was a ridiculously selfish atmospher e.
That's not true
I like that. I wonder if I also like black hair.
Now that I remember, It was Meros' black hair
It's not like that
Don't even know about you
If you blow this
I wonder if my sickness will cool down
Ora, I don't think I'm very motivated
Stop please.
If you do it that way, I will...
You say you cant but you are feeling good
Such as vulgar acts in such plac es
I just played a little more, but
By chance Am I frustrated?
If you think it's a lie
Well, I don't think you can make a good sound anyway.
If it is Tomoe, I have some knowledge.
You need to include more in my mouth
Michel-san,
I will save you, its a promisse.
I refuse
I'm rarely invited by friends, so maybe I should change it
I don't know if it's a match before you, but I was just a prospect
I have no time to participate in such things
The footsteps of your wonderful sister
I've finally served, so there seems to be a clue to how to get to Marks.
Headed to Mino Washi
Hinomoto.
Airi, where is the bitch miko?
Who knows, Even for early morning
I was think ing of asking him for directions to Hinomoto
I'm sloppy last night because I have a bad drinking habit
Elina-sama, drink too much is very bad
You should refrain a little. Noisy
So thats how it is
So I think it's better to have it at home in the morning
Numbness has healed
Its all right
I will fight
Interesting.
What do you   mean of me
That's what it seems.
Hey, Airi-san.
Is that...
Who im thinking?
Yes, that's Queen Aldra.
Menas-san!
So she is friend of the Queen.
I am the shrine maiden Tomoe
, the price of Queen Aldora, Yuuki
I want you to go into vulgarity, and I want all those who use this radio to finish looking at what justice is.
You used to say that the quality is poor. Last night
I will not forgot what I saw.
A boy's address that is too old
How do you handle those two because they belong to me
It's my self Touhou
In the name of Queen Aldra,
Model fighting
Do you two already decided?
If not decided, seven-colored eggs
Let me see, hum...
What about meow meow ears
Nao conte com isso.
I am the warriow of tempest, Elina!
Those who block the enemy disappear with the dew of the blade Chadame Warrior Miko Tomoe
Disappear for the blade
I'm always fighting Rei-chan YouTube
If I win, you will release the slave
What if I'm willing to be a slave  The person
Well, fine.
I wont lose anyway.
My request is Tomonkai
Make you a slave
Where the larvae have gathered
Now, show us a great battle!
We have all the Hitachi blad es
With this Queen's Blade battle!
Essa não!
Oh, nothing bad.
I say the same.
Please support both
Thats obvious.
Tell me, Was Elina-sama serious about turning Tomo-san into her slave?
Are you worried for her?
Yes, she has a mission to fulfill
Thats news to me.
pede arrego
I wont allow it.
The victory is mine!
Wtf is this
Shirane
This is the end of the match
An the winner is...
Zetsuen no tsuisekisha, Elina!
Im so sorry, tenshi-sama.
It ’s unlikely that I ’ll  be able to serve as Ayaniwa.
I also won
You know what's going to happen
As an advantage
Named Samurai Miko Tomoe
You will take us Take me to the bottom hinomoto.
That's right if you make me a slave, so my husband
And my guide
It ’s not that bad to be naked
Elina
Niigata
He showed me the grace of a continental gladiator
Good to receive
That is my testimony
As long as Maru is information, it will help your journey.
Tomoe-san, take it.
This is that flute
Try it
But are you sure?
Be kind
After all, the soundIt do esn't come out
But
Tired
Hitomi or
Ivalide
by the way
Michel's flute has
Cures wounds and illness
Has a nice effect
So before the match
It was becoming
With this power
Maybe Tomoe's purpose could be fulfilled
I really wanted to teach you sooner
Bikun Bikun and that were so fierce and far from that
Thank you, Michel-san
Im very grateful
Now Good departure from Kinomoto station\ After all sound