Bonus anime:
Seraph of the Endless!
Number 6
Stay combat-ready, everyone.
Make sure you're prepared for whatever comes our way.
After we turn the next corner,
Shinjuku's defensive perimeter should be right ahead.
This is...
...Ueno, isn't it?
I... I seem to have taken a wrong turn.
But we need to get to Shinjuku...
Shinjuku's that way. Let's go!
Right!
After we turn the next corner,
Shinjuku's defensive perimeter should be right ahead.
This is...
...Shibuya, isn't it?
I... I took another wrong turn.
We're getting closer, though!
Yeah!
After we turn the next corner,
Shinjuku's defensive perimeter should be right ahead.
The Statue... of Liberty.
We're in Odaiba, right?
Kimizuki-kun, are you by chance...
...lost?
Yeah...