Something, please stop.
Again on twitter? You really like it, huh.
But is so funny!
Hey, it ’s almost time for delivery, right?
Today is 3's turn, right?
note: Nanamin is the 3-chan's V.A.
Ah, Nanamin...
You are the best.
Hum? Ahn?
What are you doing? From this Chichibu!
3-chan, someone has to present the report...
I totally forgot.
Absolutely dont forget or will be bad
toukyu man de wa nai tamo
Shit, just 30 seconds left!
Leave it to me! 20代 男性 そういう人には とりあえず1000円
Pera, tudo isso?
A 20 years old girl!
Then a good game with sexy strong man is the obvious choice!
Esse é o seu perfil...
eeee jikan ja
This is the last moment!
Nanamin!
Ah, just ten left!
This week it will be a super deployment
Hey, if you give up then it all ends here!
Nanamin...
Acorda pra vida!
Ora, ora.
Nanamin....
typo
This time was a total failure but...
Actually, I will send you hot news.
Not just for you,
From now on we also distribute things that you may like
By the way,  I also analyze what kind of atmosphere you like.
For example, something that looks like an official
チョロン ぽいもの
Or maybe something like a summary.
From now on, you can count with your news app, Hacka Doll.