We are now preparing to fight
life forms known as Demons.
So, through a magic called "science,"
humans have evolved themselves, then?
That may be a scenario prepared
to bring on the end
that mankind has invited.
Armageddon?
Huh? Army what?
The High-Teen Numbers are waiting.
We can't stumble now, not here.
Right.
You are all such bothers,
so be reasonable and die!
Everyone, let's go!
Okay!
Think it would be that easy, little boy?
Nicely roasted.
003! Guidance, please!
Understood. Sending data via brain waves.
Locked on!
Data received. Firing!
007!
Saving a lady is a job for a gentleman.
What's the enemy's stronghold like?
The energy reaction has grown stronger.
It's on that island.
Set...
I've made a deal with a demon, too,
so that you may one day wake again.
0015.
I have secured Miki Makimura.
All this must mean a lot to you.
Since Set is your real brother.
He can't be expected
to recover via normal treatment,
and now this is the only way left.
By bringing Miki Makimura here,
the Devilman, Akira Fudo,
will certainly come too.
That is what Atun desires.
Set will really wake up, right?
That he will.
What is it?
But after the battle of the demons?
What's important is my research.
I don't care what happens after that.
I'm going to create the strongest cyborg.
And when you lot thrash
those proto-cyborgs,
my revenge will be complete.
Oh, Atun is reacting!
Akira Fudo, or rather, Devilman
is approaching.
Let's add the finishing touches.
Set...
So, this is the right way?
Yeah. I can sense where Miki is.
I somehow felt something was wrong,
but it didn't' feel like
Miki was in any danger.
Is she a cyborg, too?
Maybe.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Miki's been kidnapped.
Is there a worse feeling than that?
What's important is
their goal in kidnapping her.
The reason this forest has grown dangerous
seems to be related as well.
If Black Ghost,
who produces battle cyborgs,
are in league with a demon,
then quite an enemy is waiting for us.
Yeah.
What's wrong, boy?
You want your mommy?
Activate Accelerator!
You think you can run from me?
What's wrong, boy?
You're trying your best to run...
but it's a waste of time!
He's not there!
You dare show me an illusion...
They somehow battled through.
Now we're talking.
It would've been boring if that
had taken them out.
Set!
Eva...
Now the moment has come.
Atun!
Take charge of this vessel
and descend to our world!
That's it. Just a little more.
It's mine... It's finally mine!
Set?
Now I can really take him on!
Take him on?
I've done it!
My cybernetic demon is complete!
What?
Miki's over there. I'll go ahead.
Be careful!
Wh-- What do you think, Set?
Or is it best to call you Atun?
-Set.
-Hm?
-That was a stupid question...
-Ah...
You're no longer Set or Atun.
How about putting it this way.
You're a new being,
a reborn fusion of both.
Set's weak personality
has been consumed by Atun.
Not even a small piece of him remains.
Professor!
You've served your purpose.
What?
I like this new body.
I'll thank you for that, and that alone.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
You will prove yourself
to be the strongest in existence,
and that I am...
the greatest cyborg researcher...
So what?
You damned demon!
Set...
Are you also going to give me orders?
Is there nothing left of Set?
I wonder...
But whether or not he's in me matters not.
This form, this existence
is something new, born just now.
If that's the case,
I'll never forgive you
for meddling with Set's body.
Impertinent for a mechanized doll.
Set...
He's coming!
Time to settle things
with my nemesis Amon.
I'll destroy you
and become the strongest demon.
And you will be the sacrifice
to fill the world with sorrow!
Who's that?
Who's calling me?
What in the world...
Nothing for you to worry about.
You're the High-Teen Numbers!
It's just two demons
trying to face each other.
001.
You guys have made a big mistake.
If you mean forging a contract
with a demon, that was no mistake.
Our calculations were perfect.
Now you're all here.
We're still missing 15 and 18, but...
Well, we should be enough.
I wouldn't count on it.
In order to prove that
my father's and my cyborg research
really was the best,
you're all going to die here.
-What was that?
-You've already met him.
The demon human, Devilman!
Well then, Proto-Numbers, shall we begin?
009!
Boom!
You get beaten too fast!
Hot! Hot! It burns!
What the hell? That little kid
needs to learn some manners!
We can't keep up...
What unbelievable stamina.
I feel Miki's presence.
It was you!
What have you done with Miki?
A mere human with the powers of a demon.
You'd stand against me
without even knowing that power.
Who the hell are you?
Have you forgotten, Amon?
The heroic Atun, one of the best warriors
of the demon tribe!
Amon? Atun? Quit with the gibberish.
Where is Miki?
You have degraded, Amon.
This speed...
You've merged with another
and gained new powers, I see.
Interesting!
Miki...
Please at least let Miki be okay...
Miki.
Set, the boy we both grieved over...
I've turned him into a monster...
You're Eva... I heard from Akira.
There's still something I must do.
Please look after Miki.
Boom!
An ice cage!
Well this should be no prob--
Whoa!
What are you playing at, 007?
My fire is perfect for times like this!
Not so fast!
Well, that's no good.
How about this then!
They really are useless!
Hey!
It burns! What's going on?
Here comes your spanking!
Wha--!
The mole tactics actually worked!
Is that the best you can do?
How was Amon taken over
by someone like you?
The hell if I know!
All I want is to protect Miki
and the world she lives in.
Edward, Cain, Abel?
Eva?
What is it?
Atun killed the Professor.
It can't be! My father?
Why'd they stop fighting?
They'd had enough?
No, they don't know
the meaning of fatigue.
There's no more point in fighting.
Dr. Adams was the one
who wanted the 009 Cyborgs dead
and he's gone now.
What's more...
Set didn't regain consciousness.
The only thing
inside that cybernetic demon
is a completely different, evil being
fused from Atun and Set.
Well, if that's how it is...
then I will continue my father's research.
Now is the time for us to show
the strength of the High-Teen Numbers!
Right.
If that's not Set,
then let's take him down
along with the proto-cyborgs.
No, Edward.
What worth is there now
in proving the brilliance
of Dr. Adams' research?
Even if you prove that,
we are nothing but weapons.
The professor will still be dead
and Set won't come back.
If you continue fighting,
our sorrow will simply increase.
Eva, only victors have a future.
I have no intention
of giving up this battle.
Eva, don't waste your time.
It's a shame but we'll have to
put your plan in motion.
001, what do you mean?
What are you rambling on about?
Stop it!
009!
005!
007!
You owe me!
It was 0015 Eva who woke me.
Just like me, she has psychic powers.
She foresaw this possibility.
Akira!
-You?
-Oh, it's you.
So, even with the power of a demon...
in the end, you're just a human.
The mechanized dolls are all lined up.
Don't get cocky.
After we deal with the proto-cyborgs,
we'll take you on properly.
A demon-cyborg fusion...
009.
You deal with him.
But...
0015 Eva will cooperate.
15?
There's only one way to do it.
Leave the other High-Teen Numbers to us.
Understood. Activate Accelerator!
-I won't let you!
-Whoa!
You're forgetting that
we're your opponents.
008 to the Dolphin.
Roger that.
You won't get far!
Got this!
What incredible recuperative power!
001, I'll begin.
I see. That's how it is.
Their special self-reproducing cells
that Eva told us about
were created by unique charged fusion
when they were brought into being.
In other words, if the cells are exposed
to anti-energy,
the fusion process will be reversed
and their cells will become unstable.
They won't be able to regenerate.
That would require
a massive power generator
and facilities to convert it
into anti-energy.
Eva can activate the power generator.
I see.
The sonar-radar on the Dolphin
can act as the conversion facility.
But since Eva is also
a High-Teen Number,
she won't be safe either...
There is no other way.
Hm...
Everyone,
move to the coordinates I sent you.
I'm in position.
Barrage on Point 3 Sector 1
for three seconds.
Understood.
006, now!
Okay.
003!
-Now!
-Okay!
007!
Here I go!
002!
I'm on it.
How can you be faster!
You don't have the specs!
Just the result of data collection
and action prediction.
Oh, and our teamwork, too.
Pathetic.
That's right. We're not going to die.
The self-repair function...
What kind of scheme is this?
Even if I look like a demon,
I'm still a human.
There's someone I must protect.
Someone to protect...
Preparations completed.
Radome bay deployed.
Energy conversion system standing by.
Roger that. System reboot complete.
Eva!
Set.
This is the only thing
I can do for you now.
Focusing energy.
No way!
Anti-energy conversion confirmed.
Starting irradiation.
They got us...
My self-repair function...
Set...
You're not Atun. Where's he gone!
Set... Set, is that you?
Atun? Set?
I am far beyond such terms.
What... what is this?
I can't analyze it either.
He's somehow tenuously balancing
between demon and machine.
Everyone, be careful.
My repair function...
Ouch... Damn you!
Abel, no!
Take this!
Abel!
Cain!
Huh?
Witless fool. Do you really think
a mechanical doll like you can fight me?
Well, then.
If you're what my father was aiming for,
then I'll surpass you with my own hands!
006!
This is the end.
I can't believe
we, the High-Teen Numbers
can be defeated like this...
We may have faced the same fate.
That's why it's always hard
even if we survive.
What trite words.
Don't you understand?
When we became cyborgs
and realized we had powers
beyond that of any human,
I thought I was human no more.
I thought that demons wearing human skin
had made me into a demon as well.
But I was wrong.
It's not about power or appearance,
but whether or not you can
continue to be human.
You can choose yourself.
So even having gained powers,
you're still just a being
with a weak, human heart.
You just don't get it.
-Let's go!
-Activate Accelerator!
However fast you move,
you cannot reach the speed of light.
It's because I'm human that I can fight!
Longing for hope to ease the heart's pain,
and wishing to protect someone.
Human's weakness is their strength!
009!
Damn!
Can't you do something, 001?
Demons' abilities are
above my level of understanding.
001...
001, give your power to me.
Set, you're in there, aren't you?
Please, show yourself. For me.
St... stop it!
Don't touch me!
What the hell is this?
Set, you can rid yourself
of this demon possessing you.
Come back to me. To your sister.
Get off me!
Eva?
Set...
Eva...
001!
I'm finally free from that spell.
Amon, let's fight!
I keep telling you, I'm not Amon!
There!
Without your recuperation powers
you're nothing but a puny demon.
You wish.
Blood is what we demons seek.
Yes, excellent!
Let us enjoy this festival of blood!
Activate Accelerator!
What's wrong? The festival isn't over yet.
009!
That'll do.
See you.
Yeah.
He reminded me of something important.
What's that?
That we are human, too.
Because we have something
we dearly wish to protect.
Huh...
Hey, Akira.
I feel a little strange.
Miki, it's best that you don't know.
Well I guess it was a bit too soon
to pick a fight with us.
A savior in the form of a demon...
Savior?
Well, maybe you're right.
I'm glad he wasn't an enemy.
Yeah.
Means there's demons of all sorts
out there, huh?
Your eyes are open, 001.
What's going on?
Warning. Warning. Evil spirit approaching.