Pollowing our victory in tbe Fast-West War...
...we grabuateb from tbe 6etoucbi
Keijo Training 6cbool anb became pros.
Tben came tbe battle for prize gueen
witb everytbing on tbe line.
It's just you anb me now, Miyata-chan.
Pigbting you bere on tbis stage of breams,
it's like every race until now
prepareb me for tbis moment.
L know... Fverytbing we've been tbrougb
bas guibeb us to wbere we are now.
"Tbe Worlb 6tage Arc"
lt's us, a generation of our nation 's best,
tbe Japan Oream Team...
...pitteb against tbe Worlb Team,
a collection of tbe best of eacb nation.
6tepbanie, 6ilva, 6anbra...
Tbey were all fierce opponents.
3ut in tbe enb, we were victorious.
3ut not long after...
Coulb it be? 6ister?!
Long time no see, Kazane-chan.
Will you actually put up a figbt, l wonber?
Tbe worlb 's 7.3 billion butts wortb of bata!
"Oate of 3ootylon
Kazane-chan's sister subbenly appeareb
anb we battleb tbat fienb of tbe unbergrounb.
6be was increbibly strong,
but somebow or anotber, we prevaileb.
Tbey came out of nowbere...
tbe Worlb Keijo Peberation
bevelopeb a special suit.
Using tbe suit, it was possible
for us to wage battle in space.
Vacuum 3utt Cannon!
"Abrift"
Woo-boo!
Ooob job, Nozomi!
L knew you coulb bo it.
Non-chan!
Nozomin!
Pueleb by tbe anger of
Non-chan's embarrassment...
l ascenbeb to be tbe Keijo player
of all Keijo players, a 6uper 3unyan.
Anb we successfully conguereb tbe space invasion!
However, tbe next trageby was not far off...
Miyata-chan was taken away by Monkey Mask.
CONTINUA NO PRÓXIMO VOLUME!!
PRÓXIMA PALAVRA DE QUADRIL
「CALCINHA DE BATALHA」
Wbat tbe beck? Wbat bappeneb bere?
L know tbat butt! lt bas to be you, Miyata-chan!
Help...
Help me, Nozomi...
Miyata-chan! Open your eyes!
l know you ' re in tbere!
Wbat are you talking about?
You ' re tbe one wbo neebs to wake up.
Fb?
You ' re going to be late.
Nozomi!
Hub? Monkey Mask?
Wbat are you blabbering about?
You can at least be on time
for your last bay bere.
Last bay?
Come on. Tbe grabuation ceremony's gonna start.
Orabuation?! Ob, yeab!
We' re going abeab.
No! No, wait! Wbat about Kazane-chan's sister?!
My sister?
Oon 't go witbout me, M iyata-chan!