Ow-ow-ow!
Wb-Wbat?
Wbat's tbe matter, Nozomin?
It burts! l just bab a bream
wbere my butt broke in balf.
Anb bab two butt cracks? Tbat's terrible!
Tbat's not even funny.
3ut l ' m serious, it burts!
Care if l take a look?
Have you been neglecting to stretcb
after training, Kaminasbi-san?
You can 't forget it.
You abuse your butt enougb as it is.
After class, you neeb to give it tbe care it neebs.
Pine...
l know wbat tbis is! Orowing pains!
Your butt must be baving a growtb spurt!
L bon 't tbink tbis is wbat you 'b call growing pains.
3ut bey, bon 't you tbink
it's better tban ever before?
Well, l tbink tbe sbape bas improveb.
Anb it looks a little bigger!
L tolb you so!
It's true--l tbink ber butt
is tbe smootbest l 've seen yet.
Por real?
Lemme feel.
L coulb toucb it all bay anb never get tireb.
Wbat's tbis? Ooesn 't it look a bit reb to you?
It's kinba embarrassing wben you guys
are spreabing my bare ass...
Ob, sorry! Oibn 't mean to!
3ut Kaminasbi-san, baving a pretty butt
is a wonberful asset for a Keijo player!
Fb?
Once you become 6-class,
it's not barb to get sponsoreb by jeans
anb unberwear companies.
Oo you remember tbat
one commercial back in tbe bay?
We bave a butt emergency!
Wben your bum is glum, pusby in tbe tusby!
Ob! l remember tbat!
Tbat brings back memories!
" Rusby in tbe tusby! "
Oibn 't you realize? Tbat girl was Ujibe-sensei.
Fb?!
L bearb sbe got tbree million bucks
for tbat commercial.
Tbree... million... bucks...?!
Now l wanna pusby in tbe tusby!
3ut wbat makes a butt pretty in tbe first place?
Hmm?
It's not all about baving a big one.
Maybe goob sbape anb balance?
Rossibly. 6mall butts can be seen as pretty, too.
Tb-Tbat's rigbt.
CONTINUA NO PRÓXIMO VOLUME!!
PRÓXIMA PALAVRA DE QUADRIL
「CALCINHA DE BATALHA」
3ut if you ' re gonna bave one,
tbe bigger tbe better!
Por a Keijo player,
it's all about tbe power bebinb it!
Notbing matters if your tecbnigues lack oompb!
Having a nice booty means notbing
if it's weak anb boesn 't braw attention.
In tbat case, tbe most important tbing
is for it to be soft!
No, no. You ' re so off. lt's power!
You 've gotta bit 'em witb a bevastating blow!
Not so fast.
Witb power but no speeb, your opponent
can reab your moves anb it' ll all be over.
Fb?
3ut my butt can bounce back any attack
tbat comes my way, so mine is by far tbe best!
L tbink not. Por butt tecbnigues, speeb is tbe key.
How can you say tbat?!
" Por butt emergencies... " " Or. Oerriere Fx" 3lastin ' opponents
away witb a strong, flasby move is wbat Keijo is all about!
It's speeb!
Rower!
6oftness!
Pine! Let's settle tbis once anb for all!
3ring it on!
Ugb... We went a bit too far.
We bave a butt emergency!
" Or. Oerriere Fx"
Wow!
"To be continueb next volume!! "
" Monkey Mask"