Na
go
ya
Arc
Hm, it's gotten pretty chilly since he fell asleep.
I hope Yuu-kun doesn't catch a cold.
Maybe we should've brought mufflers.
I guess so.
Then I'll go back and get some.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I mean, I'll be fine as long as I get closer to the fire.
And if this chump catches a cold, it'll take longer for us to get to my demon training.
Nobody said anything.
O-Oh, really?
Yeah.
Well, okay then.
What?
Come on now, aren't you cold?
Take my jacket.
Huh? What?
You're playing Yuu-chan.
Oh, Kimizuki-kun, I could never.
You're too kind.
I've always admired your tenderness.
I am amazing.
But I see right through you!
I mean, surely this is how you treat everyone?
No, Yuu!
I love you, and only you!
Yuu!
Kimizuki-kun!
To be continued.
The show's canceled!
Seriously though, that tenderness line was some good improv, Micchan.
What can I say? I'm just a natural.
I'm not surprised!
Yoichi, can I murder those two?
But you actually are really nice, Kimizuki-kun.
Oh, no!
Don't let him fool you, Yoichi-san!
He's a player, Yoichi!
What the hell is up with you two?
Well, we're bored.
Yep, that's pretty much it.
And it seems like it's still gonna be a while before Yuu wakes up.
Do something to entertain us.
Do it yourself!
Is that any way to talk to a superior?
What!?
Problem?
I don't want to hear that from you!
What's that supposed to mean?
What do you think you're doing!?