The year 2046
After the invention of a device called Neuro-Linker, most young people
spent most of their lifetime in a virtual world.
A boy named Haruyuki, suffering from his bad social situation,
received a strange program from the most popular girl of the school, Kuroyukihime.
I'll send you an application
for your Neuro-Linker.
A program that changes one's reality completely.
Accelerated?
A world that is speeded up?
The name of this application is "Brain Burst"
It accelerates the human brain by 1000 times.
Now, shout this: Burst Link!
Burst Link!
A second in the real world now consists of a thousand seconds for you.
Knowing the secret of the fast-paced world,
Haruyuki became the knight of Kuroyukihime to protect her.
Don't you want to be faster, boy?
This is the story of a young man yielding a great power.
I'll make you dance with my 'Poison Sound'!
Let's go!
The only way to get "Burst Points" is through duels.
If a player loses all "Burst" points,
the program "Brain Burst" will be uninstalled,
and can't be re-installed again.
And the player's memories regarding "Brain Burst" will be erased entirely.
If this world is so close to reality, he must have a weakness.
That's right!
Dance more!
Please move 'Silver Crow'.
Faster than him!
Even if I can't trust myself,
Your consciousness has created that body, if you don't trust yourself, who will?
Are you able to stop my "Monster Machine"?!
I will believe in her words!
It is almost time
That's it!
What?!
In order to keep accelerating
you must keep fighting and winning.
Again, congratulations on your first victory.
At this rate, you can quickly ascend to level 2.
T-Thank you
Currently I can't imagine leveling up...
In fact, it is an unimaginable long path...
Within thousands of Burst Linkers, only few reach level 4.
If you reach level 7 or 8, you can go on and enter a large group.
A Group?
In other online games it's called "Guild", but we call it "Legion".
Currently, Accel World is divided and ruled by 6 legions.
They are ruled by level 9 Burst Linkers which are,
Blue, Red, Yellow, Green, Purple and White.
They are the 6 Kings of pure color.
I never heard of any game where level 9 is the limit.
I never said that level 9 is the maximum level.
So, is there anyone who is level 10?
How many?
In Brain Burst 2039,
since its creation 7 years ago by a mysterious author,
no one has reached level 10
most likely due to the difficult conditions.
Is it because you need dozens of wins?
A million maybe?
Only 5 wins are needed.
But every opponent must be level 9.
And if he loses... he will run out of points.
Causing Brain Burst to be removed from the player.
One summer, 2 years ago ...
everyone of the present kings reached level 9 almost at the same time,
and due to a message of the system, they knew the difficult condition to gain level 10.
At one point a disastrous war arose because of that,
but up till now, the kings decided to abandon that goal.
They signed an agreement and established a society with laws.
It's a farce.
They must have defeated thousands of Linkers
to get to level 9.
So, your goal is to challenge those kings?
No, I already did.
The 6 kings, formerly 7 kings,
had a strong bond and were friends and rivals,
but the black king betrayed the other kings,
on that night two years ago.
The black king?
Yes, I am the seventh queen "Black Lotus".
I was against the non-aggression pact,
and I proposed that we should fight among the 7.
Since then, Kuroyukihime disappeared from Accel World.
But lately she has received challenges within the school network.
She was chased by a blue avatar,
called Cyan Pile.
She ended up asking Haruyuki for help.
And the suspect to be Cyan Pile was...
Kurashima Chiyuri,
the childhood friend of Haruyuki.
I-I am sorry.
However, he believed in the innocence of his friend.
So he went straight to see her.
And so, he found the trojan on her Neuro Linker.
That was...
Thats weird. It's slow...
Could this be...
..a back door!
Burst Link!
The boy who attacked Haruyuki,
Araya, attacked the two with a car.
At that moment, Kuroyukihime used the second,
to tell her feelings to Haruyuki.
This must be revenge.
I didn't try to understand the other people.
I played with the feelings of others up to this day.
But... but...
Do not make that face.
At least all of this has something good to it.
Good?
This time...
you will believe my words.
Haruyuki-kun, I love you.
This is a new feeling for me.
I can't control it, and I always feel confused.
I always think of you...
It fills me with joy,
and also sadness.
That's what they call love, right?
Be strong and become faster.
Show me you have the potential I saw.
No! No!
I can't let something happen to you!
I must protect you... but...!
I still... I haven't done anything for you.
Someday... we'll see each other again.
Senpai, don't do it ... Senpai!
Senpai!
Kuroyukihime saved Haruyuki,
and received a severe injury that left her unconscious.
If she receives a challenge from Cyan Pile while unconscious,
then I can't intervene and he wins.
I will protect you.
The next day, his best friend, Takumu, appeared at the hospital.
Taku, you're here.
Taku!
But what is his reason to be here?
Burst Link!
The reason is
Takumu is Cyan Pile!
You placed the virus in Chiyuri's Linker.
And you accessed her hard drive without permission, Taku!
That you are the one to see through her hard drive...
You're not even her boyfriend!
But you never truly know the girls you're with...
She seemed to be happier with you,
even when I held her hand.
Everything needs to end, Haru.
Spiral Gravity Driver!
The avatar of Takumu,
Cyan Pile, is level 4.
Silver Crow is only level 1, he stood no chance.
Even so, Crow tries to get up for Kuroyukihime.
Then...
Senpai...
True strength is not only to win...
Even if I look pathetic, I crashed into ground...
and being paralyzed...
I have to fight
and continue to long for the sky even if I am grounded...
That's it!
That is the sign of strength!
It was the awakening of his true ability.
Wings?
It's warm.
She is calling me...
Let's go!
It was the ability to fly, which had never been given before.
Fall off!
Lightning Cyan Spike!
Haru!
Taku!
Haruyuki-kun.
You will be recognized in the world as the fastest Linker.
And you will see the potential within our minds and hearts...
The great potential.
I can see! I can see it, Senpai!
Sorry!
You win, Haru!
In the real world, I can't beat you in anything,
but, in this world you can not beat me!
Now, we are on the same level.
That's why... That's why you'll be my ally.
Be my ally, Taku!
Just like me, you'll fight under the command of that person.
Why would you trust me?
I have betrayed the guidelines and my Legion,
I also betrayed my two only friends.
From now on we'll talk together...
about Brain Burst and what we fight for...
And also of the feelings that we kept hidden...
We will talk about everything...
I think we...
need to start there.
Senpa-
Senpai...
Senpai!
Good thing... I knew you would be safe...
You're injured.
Thank you, Haruyuki-kun.
No, Senpai...
You told me to trust you
So...
Your true appearance is beautiful.
My instinct wasn't wrong.
You are the person who will change the world.
The time has come, I must get out of my cocoon,
and fly to the sky.
Listen! Burst Linkers dominated by the 6 Legions!
My name is Black Lotus and
I challenge the 6 current kings.
My legion Nega Nebulous and I,
It's time to get out of our comfort zone and
defy the false peace.
The appearance of Silver Crow with the ability to fly,
and the announcement to restore Nega Nebulous
spread quickly through the fast-paced world.
Three months later.
The territory, the area, that is dominated by a legion, is
determined by the battle
that occurs every Saturday in the afternoon.
A battle with unrestricted levels and number of participants.
You must win over 50% of the battles.
We will take care of it, go.
I'm counting on you Haru, proceed as usual.
You can count on me.
Cyan Pile joined Nega Nebulous.
The three people are securing the territories around the Suginami school.
But, it was difficult to expand the territories further.
His ability to fly was useless against long distance shots.
He didn't advance to level 4.
Damn.
Did you think we would fall for the same thing twice?
Your flight ability, once you get used to it, you are an easy target.
But still...
Still, I...
I want to be strong.
Welcome, Onii-chan.
An angel?
A true angel...
When he returned home he was greeted by a girl who claimed to be his cousin.
Sorry, I used the kitchen without permission.
I thought you would be hungry when you got back.
Onii-chan.
Can I also come in?
I'll leave! I am sorry! Wait!
Don't worry, we're cousins.
No, sorry, I'm okay!
But, do not stare at me, please ...
Tomoko-chan...
Tell me, Onii-chan.
You're a Burst Linker, right?
The tan mark on your neck...
You are very observant if you realize those small details.
Anyway, I got tired.
I 'll make you obey!
You put Scarlet Rain in disgrace!
You will pay for that!
Be careful!
I'll kill you...
The identity of that Angel was Scarlet Rain, the Red King.
She had investigated Haruyuki's real life,
in order to enter his house.
Uh, are you really the Red King?
Rail Storm Domination!
Silver Crow, Lightning Kick!
I win, Onii-chan
So it seems...
So, will you listen to me?
Please.
I want to meet your leader...
In real life.
In person.
Why would you go to such lengths to meet Haruyuki?
Do you love him that much?
Obviously not!
I want his avatar, not him himself!
Silver Crow...
I want to borrow those wings on your back, your aviating ability, just once.
to destroy the Calamity Armor.
Calamity Armor?
VR movie.
It's memory footage, played directly from inside my brain.
The Disaster Armor, also called "Chrome Disaster".
Seven Years ago...
We tried to defend ourselves against it with everything we had...
but even higher level Linkers were defeated.
However, they could not destroy the armor.
It is able to possess a Burst Linker...
It takes control of one's mind
and turns him into a killing machine.
And...
This is the fourth armor.
His form and size are on a whole new level from the fifth one currently on the loose.
The armor changes its shape to fit its avatar host.
However, its crazed manner of attack never changes.
Two and a half years ago, thanks to the seven kings of pure color,
the curse of Chrome Disaster had been sealed, that's what we thought.
How do you explain what's happening now, then?
It's a fact that a fifth one appeared and is on the loose!
What's the name of the fifth one?
Which of the kings is it?
It's not a king.
The fifth one is my...
He's a member of the Red Legion, "Prominence".
Her original name is Cherry Rook.
He was a good guy.
He didn't have any flashy abilities, but he worked hard and got to level 6.
He had so much to look forward to.
Yet...
Damn it!
He still belongs to the Red Legion, but he goes around attacking the members of other Legions.
He's breaking the non-aggression pact.
So now I have to deal with him.
I see.
I finally know what you want.
Huh? What does she want?
Isn't it obvious, Onii-chan?
I want you to catch Chrome Disaster for me.
I can't possibly do that!
We move forward with the plan the following afternoon.
Kuroyukihime and Nico decided to stay at Haru's house until the plan is finished.
Don't stare at me like that.
This was the only color of stuff that would fit me.
Th-That's not it!
It really suits you! It's perfect! It's a critical hit!
Hey, did you know Silver Crow?
She looks nice now, but without her clothes she's actually r-
Is that the best you can do?
You will see, I'll crush you!
Normally, members of different Legions are enemies, but
the three of them laughed as if they were friends for a long time ...
Passing fun times.
There he is!
Cherry got on a train on the Seibu Ikebukuro line.
If he follows his usual pattern, he'll be hunting in Ikebukuro today.
Let's go!
The mission to slay the fifth Chrome Disaster starts now.
Unlimited Burst!
S-So this is the Unlimited Neutral Field.
That's right.
We used it before to hunt the Calamity Armor.
By the way, have you noticed anything else?
What do you mean?
There's no time limit!
That's right.
That's what makes it an unlimited field.
Once you're here, you can stay forever.
Of course, you have to be level 4 or above to enter.
Before they arrived at Ikebukuro,
The Yellow King, Yellow Radio, appeared.
I see. So it was you!
You planned all of this, Yellow Radio!
Open fire!
Let's go! Reinforced Exterior!
You punks are going to find out what it's like to...
face the wrath of the Red King!
It all turned out to be the yellow king's plan.
Silver Crow and the others fell into his trap, but...
the fierce battle,
ended up being a battle between level 9 Linkers.
I hated you from the first time we met!
Lotus!
Death by Piercing!
Fatal Fortune Wheel!
The Calamity Armor.
Chrome Disaster!
But how?
We should've still had a day's worth of time in this world!
Don't tell me...
He accelerated on the train?!
Deceit Firecracker!
Get devoured!
Get devoured and become my meat!
This isn't even a fight anymore!
Chrome Disaster suddenly appeared,
and the Yellow Legion retired.
What is this?
What's wrong with me?
Silver Crow seeing all the power that individual had...
lost the will to fight.
"A Burst Linker with no will to fight
can't operate their Duel Avatar".
You're afraid of defeat, because you believe it will negatively affect your value.
That's why you haven't been performing very well in the territory battles recently.
It's not a belief. It's the truth.
Because I...
Don't misjudge yourself!
I won't abandon you, no matter what happens.
Do you really think the bond between us...
is that weak?!
Thanks to the words of Black Lotus, with whom he has an almost familiar bond,
Silver Crow rose again.
Senpai!
Geez...
This is why i hate kids.
S-Senpa-
She didn't shoot?!
She's just sulking.
What?
That little girl wants to trust, more than anyone,
the final bond between Burst Linkers.
Yes, I can tell.
They're Parent and Child.
The Red King is Disaster's...
I mean, Cherry Rook's Child.
Well, what are you doing?
I'm fine.
Go and help Niko.
Our ally.
Okay!
Stop that!
So that edge at Sunshine City is the leave point.
If he's in the middle of a leap,
you can't dodge me!
What now? How do I stop him?
I know!
More!
I have to accelerate more!
I...
...want to be strong.
That's all.
I'm sure you understand, right?
Don't you want to be strong too?
You think that means you can be forgiven for everything you did?!
You're not the only one!
Who doesn't want the strength to face every hardship?!
You did it, Silver Crow.
I'll handle the rest.
It's a Transition.
The Unlimited Neutral Field is of the Chaos element.
And so, it changes at specific intervals.
They cleared their item storage of the Calamity Armor.
Then Silver Crow and the others returned to reality.
Is something wrong, Haru?
N-No, nothing's wrong!
Oh, and I'm sorry, but one of my colleague's kids is staying over at our place.
Well, good luck!
My prized collection again...
Welcome home, Onii-chan!
Scarlet Rain told the Kings that Chrome Disaster was taken care of.
Cherry Rook, lost her memories of being a Burst Linker,
but she had regained her common sense.
W-What's this?
Well, uh... um...
It's to thank you.
C-Can I...
Can I really have these?
What?! If you don't want 'em give them back!
No, I'll have them!
Thanks.
They're good, Nico.
Really good.
Wh-What the hell are you crying for, you idiot?!
You're so embarrassing!
What's with you, you stupid idiot?
Don't eat and cry at the same time!
The young man with silver wings,
begins to grow by facing several Burst Linkers.
I will also enter Nega Nebulous.
Kurashima Chiyuri, Lime Bell.
recommended by Scarlet Rain.
The right hand of the Red King,
Kakei Mihaya, Blood Leopard.
In this world there are fateful encounters...
and also strong bonds.
Kurasaki Fuuko, Sky Raker.
I'll show you everything about me...
to the last drop.
Himi Akira, Aqua Current.
And so Silver Crow began to head towards the top of the accelerated world with Black Lotus next to him...
through battles with more powerful enemies.
End of editing, timing and translation fixes by Knigh7s (borrowed subs from ??? for Chrome Disaster arch)
Frame Torrent!
Now.
Damn.
I won't let them take this point!
Today I will knock you out! You'll see!
Raker!
That damn...
Frame Torrent!
Hey!
Special Technique: Point Impact!
Using those legs is cheating...
You're stupidly obvious in your attacks, Ken-chan.
Onee!
Maiden!
How could you do that to my brother!
Wait...
They conquered the Meijijinguu temple.
We can't lose here!
The woman who has a tree avatar is recharging the energy of her allies.
That Decurion creates an army.
It's considered bad luck to use a Christmas tree in august.
It doesn't matter!
Damn! I can't summon my invincible fortress.
Rain, can you make a crater on the road?
It will take about 20 seconds.
What do we gain by doing that?
I have no time to explain.
Okay, cover me.
Shape Change.
10... 11...
18... 19...
That's enough.
Hey, there I go!
It's useless, you can't use that weapon against my shield.
That's cheating!
I hate the darkness.
In the basement there is a train tunnel.
You should have said that earlier!
Hey, hey, hey, you damn crow!
You have the guts to face me, Bitter Valley.
I already told you that isn't Shibuya.
It's Igaya!
Shut up!
Technique V!
Very careless, Silver Crow.
I'm sorry, Senpai.
The Green King, Green Grande!
Shibuya was part of our territory.
Give it back to me, Grande.
Don't look back to the past.
We won't leave this territory.
Isn't that right, Chief?
Come to me!
Good.
Wait, wait, wait!
If they fight between the kings it will be like 'Sudden Death'.
You see.
No, it's not that.
A field change?
It can't be.
The battlefield territory does not change.
W-What that?
That's a wind vortex?
We must go.
This is...
S-Senpai!
Don't come here.
S-Senpai, what was that?
No lo sé.
The network was never down before.
What happend?
That black tornado.
This effect is not possible with this wind speed.
The BB icon on the virtual desktop is weird.
It does not work.
Burst Link!
Rays...
W-We can not accelerate.
Hey! And now?
The social cameras in the city are out of order.
The area without service is expanding.
It's confirmed that Shijuko, Minato, Shinagawa and a part of Suginami,
are in the same state.
The police was sent to the affected areas.
They are now investigating the problem.
At this moment they are on alert.
Citizens in the affected area are careful.
Guys, I'm sorry I called you on vacation.
Let's start.
First, I want you to see this.
Leopard and Fuuko collected the information.
It is impossible to accelerate in this area.
It keeps expanding.
This is the area without service.
They concur.
It is not possible that it is a coincidence.
They must be some link.
The problem is...
It could be that we can't accelerate because the social cameras are malfunctioning,
or the Brain Burst program is affecting the social cameras.
Sure?
If it's the first, we can not do anything.
If it is the second, we can investigate in the accelerated world.
And what will we do?
But it's impossible to accelerate because the social cameras are off, right?
I got an idea, we could walk.
We can enter the limited field from Suginami.
But, Master.
I heard that Burst Linkers were disconnected when they were touched by the black cloud.
Don't you think we should discuss
that with the other legions as well?
Obviously, I've asked for a meeting of the 7 Kings.
But, because of the broken connection,
I got no answers from kings.
There is another problem.
Guessing by its speed of expansion,
this area will be devoured by the black cloud at 6 a.m.
It will isolate us from the accelerated world.
Very fast...
I plan to wait for the response of the kings until that time.
But, if they still don't respond...
We, the legion Nega Nebulous...
we will face that black cloud.
That's right.
So...
Tonight the members of our Legion will gather in one place.
It would be good for us to prepare.
Is there a suitable place?
My mother is traveling abroad for work, so if you insist...
Thank you, the truth that wanted to ask for this favor from the beginning.
So we'll meet at Haru's house.
I'll tell the others.
Ah, by the way, today is...
But they are not real, they are AR.
You'll never give up on her, don't you.
It's beautiful.
Yes.
I was thinking, if this was okay while the accelerated world is in trouble.
But, it was good.
Everyone enjoys it.
Haruyuki-kun, have you ever wondered what it would be like to stop being a Burst Linker?
Yes, but I can not imagine it very well.
I'm just scared.
I understand, I'm scared too.
Those who lose all their points, lose the memories of being a Burst Linker.
Besides I thought that one day this would be of help.
But if all social cameras in Tokyo are disabled,
we are no longer able to be Burst Linkers.
But we are keeping our memories.
I never imagined it to end this way.
It's good that everyone gathered here today.
Even if we may spent too much time playing around before the mission.
Fuuko, Utai and Nico as well.
They do not say it, but they are afraid,
that the bonds that we have disappear in an instant.
Everything will be fine.
We are stubborn, we won't abandon the accelerated that easy.
You also said it.
That if we don't withdraw that night we'll be feed to the dogs.
Even if we can no longer return to the accelerated world, we will remain to be Burst Linkers.
The link that unites you, us and others will not disappear.
Never.
I was lonely until I met you.
I thought I was alone.
Haruyuki-kun.
I wasn't interested in reality, I only cared about virtual world.
I was so pathetic, but...
Haruyuki-kun!
Yes?
N-N-No, It's not what you think!
It's not what you think!
I am sorry! I am sorry! I am sorry!
Haruyuki-kun, I...
What?
I had a futon.
Eh?! What... What are you even talking about?
I am so sorry.
Don't apologize!
I didn't receive any messages from the kings.
This is the first major mission we have since Prominence and Nega Nebulous work together.
But it won't be the last.
We will find out about the secret behind the black cloud.
This is a battle to keep moving forward.
We don't know which enemies await us, but nonetheless
we will defeat them and come back safe.
Unlimited Burst!
No doubt.
It's the same cloud I saw in the last territorial battle.
That is, if it devours us that thing will automatically disconnect us?
But what....
Damn!
What are you doing all of a sudden!
You know how my sister feels and you're still flirting with Lotus-sensei.
You fucking pervert!
Onii-san, you're wrong!
Stop!
We don't have time!
So we will proceed as planned.
Appear, invincible fortress!
Heat Blast Saturation!
Damn, the information was right.
But he does react.
I think we can get by while they attack that cloud.
With my machine it is easy-come and easy-go!
We don't think so.
Then, we must do it as we discussed.
So this or that way we have to enter.
Only we can do this.
Who are you?!
The green king, Green Grande?
He arrived on time.
Boss...
I remember that cloud
T-Tell us!
You know it, Grande?
It is the Dark Cloud of an old enemy, the Goddess Nukes.
Nukes?
But he was sealed.
But Nukes did not have the ability to disconnect Burst Linkers.
Nukes?
Sealed?
The situation is complicated, we need to know what's going on.
So, can you go through that cloud?
Parsek Wall.
A new technique?
That's great, Boss!
Seriously you're an old guy without grace.
We have no other option, we will have to trust him.
Change, Dreadnought!
Get up!
Here we go! Do not fall!
Note: (Talisman) Protection regarding traffic.
Thank you for using our transport service.
Our transport vehicle will destroy objects along the way,
to collect energy.
I hope you don't fall off.
A world were everyone protects himself.
This was a warning from the Scarlet Rain society for safe transport!
Almost there.
The cloud area begins in Opera City, there we will enter the Dark Cloud.
Now is your turn, Grande!
Parsek Wall.
Will we be all right, Grande-san?
We're 2 minutes away.
What?!
Is that the limit?
You should have told us earlier...
To all engines!
Ni-Rain, go on, go on!
The shield seems to be weakening.
Why are you counting?
Hurry up, Rain!
I'm already at it!
1!
Look!
What is that?
It's like an Olympic stadium?
I'll go there.
W-What is that?
These are subordinates of Nukes.
Nukes Core.
That place is like their base.
They're protecting the stadium.
So, the Goddess of Night, Nukes, was exempt from the seal,
is in there.
Don't hesitate, we'll commence the attack.
Rain, attack with everything.
The others follow Rain!
Hurry!
Too many.
I got this!
Eat shit!
Heat Blast Saturation!
He stopped!
What's happening?
They hit me.
Senpai, the Goddess Nukes.
She was the strongest enemy of the underground of Yoyogi.
But since she was very dangerous, she and that dungeon were sealed.
It was forgotten.
Very dangerous?
She is a legendary level enemy which we once fought.
She has a power greater than Shisei Metatron.
Why did she appear now?
Frame Torrent!
Here I go!
Now!
Maelstrom.
Freeze Trans.
Frame Torrent!
There is no end to it.
It is useless to just brute force.
This is bad.
Damn, they surrounded me.
Rain.
I can't use the missiles!
If they defeat us here...
they will continue forever.
Damn it! Shit!
Rain!
This technique...
You are Aster Vine and this is the purple king, Purple Thorn.
Why?
We did not come to help you.
We came because Grande asked for it.
Can't you help us more carefully?
Then I can't help you.
There they come again!
Chie-chan, stay behind!
I see you like to go solo, Black Lotus.
The blue king, Blue Knight.
How did they get here?
Thank Grande.
If he hadn't opened the road, we wouldn't have been able to pass.
Ah, that's why they look like this.
You and your companions.
What?
Regardless I think I'm better than you.
In addition, the true hero is late.
Right, Lotus?
I know you don't get along with others.
Do not you think this time it would be better to help us?
What do you say? Damn, since yesterday...
W-Wait, Senpai, calm down.
Bell, help the Kings recover.
Hello, excuse me, this way, this way.
Come closer.
That is good.
Here I go!
Citron Call!
So this is the recover ability.
I did not think I would get it.
Refresh, refresh.
That was it. Good job.
Lotus, you will make no progress if you keep fighting alone.
I-It's true.
These flying dragons are everyone's enemies.
We must strike with ranged attacks to make them fall.
What do you say?
All right.
Nega Nebulous.
Here we go!
Coronal Mass Ejecution!
Vorpal Strike!
Lightning Cyan Spike!
Superluminal Stroke!
Frontal Thunder!
Maelstrom.
Laser Javelin!
Keep moving, there only 2 left.
Chie-chan!
Taku!
Damn, damn, damn.
At this rate, Taku will be forever lost.
This is...
Do not tell me that...
Wow, wow, it's an ugly view.
It's ugly.
Yellow Radio.
I do not like to do these things, but
there's no problem with me helping you.
No problem!
You followed us without saying anything.
Don't act so mighty!
I do not know what you mean.
I do not know.
Great, all 6 Kings gathered here.
Yes, I never imagined to see that.
Silver Crow.
Yes!
We will take care of the enemy.
You'll fly with your queen.
Yes!
We will clear the sky.
Let's cooperate.
Yes!
It's time to fight back!
Hurry!
Set On!
Gale Thurster!
Take this!
Halistorm Domination!
Frame Torrent!
Maiden!
Yes!
Frame Vortex!
How are you, Crow?
Go and give that thing a good beating!
Where are we, Senpai?
Yes, this is the bottomless space.
Over there!
You are...
the one I saw...
Do not wake us up.
Are they the ones generating that black cloud?
That black cloud will cause eternal sleep in the fast-paced world.
Then nobody will fight, there will be no sadness and no one will suffer.
All Burst Linker will fall into a sweet dream and can live forever.
That would not be living.
Burst Linkers that do not accelerate, are no longer Burst Linker.
Then stay here forever too.
Keep accelerating until eternity in this garden.
What is this?
I feel something coming in...
This is.. her memory...
Unlimited Burst!
Your little, but very sad, cry
awakened me from my thousand years of sleep.
Why are you crying?
I failed...
Sure in the real world, I...
I was always afraid to fly.
But I trained in the accelerated world and worked hard.
Finally the people had accepted me.
If I can not fly, I'm no good.
Welcome...
How foolish! Is that why you're still in this unlimited field?
Yes, we will never return to the Lowest Level.
I will fall asleep for eternity.
That is your wish.
Laser Sword!
This is the wrong way.
We are not enemies, this isn't the world where we should live.
People who try to wake her up will be devoured at night.
Senpai!
This is...
So this is the true form of Nukes.
Wait!
If we go further, we will be caught.
I see.
Senpai, what about them?
I heard about them.
Nemesis and Tanatus.
The sons of Nukes are the powerful enemies.
Their damage is collateral.
Senpai!
Why do you take so long?
Metatron?
You saved us.
Shut up, immature being!
Damn, I can not keep watching, it's so silly.
Come closer, my subordinate Silver Crow.
It's true that with your current strength you can't defeat Nukes.
Useless, nonsense.
I am sorry.
But still.
The circuit that unites Nukes with those warriors,
is weaker than our bond.
You must separate the little white warriors until you can break that circuit.
But I do not have the strength to do so.
Pull yourself together!
It's not strength, use your heart and with your new energy source you should be able to do it.
You must defeat those two guardians and Nukes.
My subordinate Silver Crow,
use your wings!
Yes!
Senpai, help me.
Yes.
There they come.
Light Speed!
We got through!
Metatron Wing!
Laser Lance Vorpal Strike!
Why are you trying to wake me up?
We must return to the real world.
Beloved people are awaiting us.
I was always alone.
There is no one who waits for me in the real world.
Gymnastics was everything to me.
It was the only thing that connected me to people.
If I'm going to lose everything and suffer alone...
I'd rather fall asleep forever here.
I used to think the same way.
Once I thought I could never get up again after losing everything.
But he and my companions taught me that I was wrong.
If you stretch your out your hand you can reach anyone.
There must be someone waiting for you.
Waiting for you.
Look!
I'm coming back.
Yes.
Sorry and thanks, Nukes.
But that is for the best.
I will be watching over you at all times.
Forever.
Is it okay for us to come with so many people?
No problem, being hospitalized is mostly boring.
I don't see a problem if we are many.
I am speaking out of experience.
You should not say that.
Is she?
Wow, they're from Ume school, aren't they?
Do you know them?
Well, we're friends.
Translated into English by AMANWITHOUTLIFE.
Some editing by Anime-Knigh7s.