Following the fierce battle in Nagoya,
we escaped from both the Imperial Demon Army and the vampires,
and ended up in the world of Seraph of the Endless.
Na
go
ya
Arc
Celebration
Graduation
Ceremony
All right everyone, listen up.
Today is your graduation.
It's time to say goodbye to the memories you've made at this school.
What memories?
Hey, Yuu, are you listening?
Huh?
Why are you even here, Guren?
Heh, the reason I'm here...
It's because we've reached the end of the special.
What!?
Well, Kureto and his people are here too, but they won't appear.
By the way, I appeared a lot.
It must be because of how amazingly beautiful I am.
You shut up.
Oh, you're here too, Mitsuba?
I can't accept this!
Why do I have to—
Mitsuba!
That's exactly what Seraph of the Endless is!
Viva illicit relationships!
Anyway,
I'm going to give you a test to see if you actually deserve to graduate.
What kind of test?
Whatever it is, my grades are the best in here.
Naive, Kimizuki.
Don't underestimate the prestigious Sanguu family!
Yeah right,
I'm taking first place!
Hey now, aren't you brats getting a little overconfident?
During this test, no cheating will be tolerated.
You're also required to take it seriously.
Even still, you must succeed!
Do you understand?
We may not—
Teacher! We did that already.
Oh.
Yep.
It's a written examination.
You've got half an hour.
Now then—
Shinya-san!
Morning!
What are you doing here?
Or actually, how the hell did you even get in here?
Huh?
I thought you called me.
I didn't.
No but seriously, go home.
I'll be your TA.
No.
Then how about I—
No!
Come on, I want to be in this, too!
Aren't we buddies?
Fine, you can take the test along with the brats.
Huh?
All right, begin!
Let's see, first question...
"True or False: Ichinose Guren is basically a god."
Seriously!?
What the hell is up with this question!?
Hey, shut up, stupid Yuu.
Was I talking to you, dumbass Kimizuki?
You looking for a beatdown?
Maybe I am!
Bring it!
Guys!
This is the graduation exam!
Get your act together!
Just a bunch of punks, I swear...
Huh?
Oh?
Shii-chan, come on out.
Okay, so you're saying the answer to this question is...
"Mahiru-neesan."
Thanks, Shii-chan!
I see.
Come out, Gekkouin.
Okay, with this...
Got it!
Nice going, Yoichi!
Yeah!
Open the coffin on the count of nine, Kiseki-Ou!
Come, Tenjiryuu!
These are the answers!
See that?
Hey you guys, shut up!
Kiseki-Ou can't count properly with—
What do you think you're doing, Kiseki-Ou?
How in the world did you manage to set the answer sheet on fire!?
Heh, you guys are hopeless.
I'll show you how it's done.
Lend me your power, Ashuramaru.
Unfold,
Ashura-Kannon!
Huh?
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
"Try doing something yourself for once."
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
Try doing something yourself for once.
PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you ☆
yay
"PS. I multiplied the amount of questions for you"!?
You didn't have to do that!
Shit.
I guess this is my final option.
You guys are hilarious!
Christ, you guys are loud.
You guys...
You all failed!