It's all over!
No 18º andar...
Monstros apareceram repentinamente no Under Resort.
Bell e seus fellow adventurers lutaram lado a lado contra eles...
e finalmente venceram a batalha.
Vamos voltar, Bell-kun, para o nosso lar.
Let's get back to the sunshine.
If you're wondering why we're here in a hot spring, bem...
Is it wrong to try to pick up
hot springs in a dungeon?
That battle was quite a close one.
Honestly, I wanted to stick around the 18th floor a while longer,
mas é melhor para a Hestia e eu to head back now.
Indeed!
Besides, se ela não tivesse vindo,
Bell-sama and I could have had a very good time.
O que você está dizendo, Supporter-kun?
Bell definitely wants to go back with me as soon as possible.
While you don't know how to heal his exhausted body,
I can cure, comfort, and serve him in whatever ways he wants!
Quanta besteira!
Ele me ama tanto que jamais conseguiria viver sem mim!
Inimigos!
Hellhounds!
You got them!
There's more!
Those are... Haudarmados!
Não tema, minha Deusa!
Eu estou aqui para protegê-la!
Bell-kun!
Bell, you're awesome...
Você é incrível, Bell-sama!
Ei, Lili...
Swift move, Cranel-san!
You finished them before we had a chance!
Como esperado do nosso Little Rookie!
Não, que isso...
What a disgrace, falling to flattery so easily!
Wha... what?
Deusa!
O que é isso?
Um território inexplorado?
Inexplorado? You mean it's not on the map?
Sim.
Without a doubt.
As far as I can recall,
there isn't a cave like this one.
And it's not a tunnel pit either.
Então fizemos uma nova descoberta?
Você é incrível, Deusa.
Ah... yes... I'm always amazing...
Ei, o que você está fazendo?
Não pode ser!
Mikoto!
É perigoso ir na frente sozinha!
Uma fonte termal?
Isso aí!
I guarantee this is a hot spring!
Quando se trata de fontes termais, I'd never be wrong!
Não tem mais nada aqui.
Não sinto a presença de nenhum monstro.
Maybe it's a present from the dungeon.
Then we shall avail ourselves of its kindness.
C-Como está, Mikoto?
Tanto a temperatura como a concentração de minerais na água estão perfeitas!
I must take a bath!
Nós não fizemos nenhuma pausa since leaving the 18th floor.
Everyone! Let's take...
A bath in this wonderful hot spring!
What's wrong?
Não me diga que você esqueceu the last incident!
Oh, you mean the one in which Bell was the luckiest!
Bell the luckiest?
Ah no, uh...
What's that?
Anyway...
We can't take a bath com o Hermes aqui!
I really want to though.
No way...
Vocês podem usar trajes de banho.
Wear swimsuits, then you needn't worry anymore.
Great idea!
But where do I find a swimsuit?
Eu sabia que algo assim poderia acontecer.
I brought swimsuits for everyone!
What have you done?!
Every piece is a masterpiece, escolhida por mim.
And they're yours now.
When did you do that?!
Como ele sabe o tamanho ue usamos?
Never mind!
After all, we can take the bath now!
You can change clothes behind that rock.
As damas primeiro.
Would you keep a watch on him?
I'm not going to bathe with you.
So I planned to do so from the start.
Behave yourself, Hermes-sama!
Tá, já sei...
Bathing with Bell!
That Valen-seilaoq isn't here.
I must take this chance!
An ongoing feast is right behind that rock!
Lili is yet immature,
but her strength that has helped her survive this long
makes her little body graceful!
Despite Mikoto being serious all the time, she's really sexy hot.
And there's Chigusa, whose waist line is slim and delicate.
Surrounded by crystals, they look even more beautiful.
As for our Asfi, she was once a princess...
No, I shouldn't have said that.
Well, she's from a noble background.
I assure you.
And our final eye-catcher is Hestia,
whose boobs are incomparable among all the goddesses.
Just think about it!
They're all naked right behind that rock!
Damn you Hermes!
You must have given me this undersized one on purpose!
Two flossy fluffy fruits covered by her pale skin!
Can you stay calm with that image?
Got it!
Goddess, what's up?
Don't worry, Bell.
Some unexpected things happened.
Please wait a little bit longer.
Alright.
To think that...
This size is still too small for you?
So you messed up again.
It's not my fault!
So what should we do?
It's not like we have any spares.
I don't think a larger size even exists.
So all my plans of bathing with Bell will come to nothing?
It's too soon to give up, Divine Hestia.
Mr. Welf!
Would you lend us a hand? Mr. Welf.
Are you calling me?
Sorry guys, looks like I have to go.
Why him?
Welf, you're a huge help!
Whenever you gather your group, a swordsmith is always necessary!
I will bring word to Hephaestus in praise of your excellent craftsmanship.
Oh, thanks.
Why are you so depressed?
Leave me alone.
Bell, I'm coming!
Tell me, Bell. Does this suit me okay?
Yes, Goddess.
Sorry for causing you trouble!
Now let's get to the hot spring!
I assume everyone is decent now.
I have a feeling that mine is the most embarrassing...
Mine is also embarrassing!
I feel bashful, as well.
No no no! All of you look excellent!
However, Miss Mikoto...
Don't you like the swimsuit I chose for you?
I'm grateful to you, sir.
But I believe it's best to be completely naked!
Although, due to various reasons,
my wish hasn't been granted this time.
We shall still stick to good manners!
Attention!
I, Yamato Mikoto, upon this day,
shall teach you what those manners are!
Bell, should we go to all this trouble to just take a bath?
Goddess, learning a manner or two doesn't hurt, does it?
First, bow twice!
Clap twice!
Bow once!
Then offer some money.
Wait a second!
Why do I have to offer money?!
Silence!
This is what good manners are supposed to be!
Then, recite prayers,
and perform the San-san-kudo ritual.
Ka-shi-ko-mi! Ka-shi-ko-mi!
Ka-shi-ko-mi.
I can't hear you!
How's that supposed to be Ka-shi-ko-mi?
Is she always so passionate like now?
Recite again!
Pretty interesting, though.
Is this that Eastern culture of yours?
I'm afraid not.
That's her culture alone.
Up to now is what good manners require.
Finally, warm up your wrists and ankles...
And head for your hot spring!
She didn't even wash herself before entering.
We are so sorry...
This is great for a break.
And it'll remain perfect as long as Hermes doesn't make himself a nuisance.
Hot springs are the best!
What magic! My shoulders feel lighter than ever before!
That's not magic, I suppose...
I'll get you this time!
No, I'll get you!
So the battle is over.
Yeah, we survived.
I just realized, it's all your fault, isn't it? Big guy?
I know that.
And I won't regret it.
Bell!
This cave is huge, let's go to the recesses and see what's there!
Ah, certo, Deusa.
Sorry, I have to go.
That's called perquisite.
He's our Little Rookie.
Ouka...
Mikoto found the source desta fonte termal.
Maybe if you bathe there, you'll recover faster.
Quer vir comigo?
Ah, claro.
Cuidado onde pisa...
Ah, tudo bem.
Droga!
Ficar sozinho nem sempre é algo ruim.
There is a good side to solitude.
Te dá tempo pra refletir.
You mean looking back?
Why is she wearing bloomers?
Não está muito quente, Ouka?
If you think so, then get out.
C-Claro...
But I can't!
Me desculpem por antes.
I always lose my sanity when I spot a hot spring.
Don't sweat it.
Besides, it's an honor to converse com membros da Takemikazuchi Familia.
I'm afraid the honor is all ours.
I agree with Chigusa.
Te ver lutar me faz perceber que ainda tenho muito a aprender.
Hey!
Isn't the water too hot for your feet?
You may get burned if the water is too hot...
No problem!
It's cozy!
I feel... good.
I see...
It's fortunate that we bumped into this place.
And the hot spring is curative for Mr. Ouka.
Yeah.
Miss Chigusa, I respect your concern for Mr. Ouka.
That's because... he is our leader, so...
Your kindness is beyond reasoning, I really respect it.
Obrigada.
Ouka!
What a misfortune, Mr. Ouka!
Ouka is dead!
I didn't expect to find a place like this in the dungeon.
It's impressive!
Right?
It's only the two of us here.
No one can interfere.
You annoying, Valen-whatchamacall!
I'll make you comprehend that you're merely a outsider.
De novo?
Bell, it'd be bad if you catch a cold.
We could stay warm if we walked shoulder to shoulder...
Oh! Let's call Lili and others!
They'd be happy to join us!
Esp..., ei Bell-kun!
Eu volto logo.
Caramba, Bell-kun idiota!
Calm down... calm down...
What are you doing up there?
I wanna ask you the same!
This is a hot spring, you know?
Yes, I know.
Then what are you fishing?
I'm fishing precautions.
Precautions?
I'm yet to be convinced...
that this is a naturally formed hot spring.
What do you mean?!
It's only my intuition.
I also told Mr. Cranel about it.
Currently, my intuition is unverified.
Calm down... calm down... calm down...
Don't use me to calm your urge for her bloomers.
It's only bloomers, that's all...
Forget it! Forget it!
My plans are ruined once again!
What's that?
There wasn't anything twinkling a moment ago.
I want some water,
I'll go back for a while.
Sure.
Bell!
Deusa?
A fantastic scenery, don't you agree?
Sure... But what are they made of?
Those are trivial matters.
Só estamos nós dois aqui.
Bell-kun...
D-Deusa...
Pessoal! Saiam já da água!
Lion, como assim?
M-Meu biquíni!
Lili-dono...
Calm down! Calm...
Que delícia...
O que é isso?!
Ho! Ho! A luxury for my eyes!
So is this your doing again?
Nah. I have nothing to do with this.
I don't think our Divine Hermes did this either.
This means...
Cranel-san e a Deusa Hestia!
D-Deusa, tem algo estranho...
Nothing is wrong, I'm dead serious!
Ahn, não foi bem isso que eu quis dizer...
Bell-kun, eu... I... I was always...
Monstros!
Eu tenho que protegê-la!
Bell-kun...
Deusa, você está bem?
Forgive me, Goddess!
Bell-kun!
FIRE-
Ouch!
Ryuu-san!
Are you okay, Cranel-san?
Essa foi por pouco!
Thanks! Miss Asfi!
Hestia-sama, what are you doing naked in the arms of Master Bell.
Please take my cloak for now, Deusa Hestia.
Thank you, I shall borrow it.
Não pode ser...
Bell-kun?
Is it the master of this place?
Cuidado!
Bell-kun!
Don't worry!
Eu vou te proteger, Deusa!
Bell!
FIRE BOLT!
Bell-kun!
Você conseguiu, Bell-kun!
Sim, Deusa.
Ryuu-san e Asfi-san, obrigado pela ajuda.
I suggest you get dressed before expressing your gratitude.
Please avert your eyes, Goddess!
Come on Bell, não seja tímido!
You see, Valen-whatsoever?
You won't stand a chance against me!
What's wrong, Aizy-tan?
Você pegou um res...
Um resfriado?
I never expected this entire hot spring to be a trap set by monsters.
Perhaps all the adventurers who found it prior to us didn't manage to escape their jaws.
It would explain why it's uncharted.
Guess we should submit a report to the guild.
Eu sinto muito mesmo.
If I didn't lose my sanity to some sort of hot spring...
Não precisa se desculpar.
After all we all had a good time.
Sim.
Right, right, we are all fine...
Ouka, aguente firme!
Then, shall we go onward?
What's so funny, Deusa?
Não é nada.
Vamos voltar, Bell! Para o nosso lar!
Sim!
Fim