Yuppy
Elas chegaram.
Let's put in another good day's work, yo!
She said "yo."
The Personal Entertainment AI
that syncs up to you: HackaDolls!
O que você deseja de nós hoje?
I want you to get the perfect
present for this girl.
What a drag...
Oh?
Uau! Que bonita!
Ela é sua namorada?
Oh, he has a real life...
Ah! É a Yuppy!
Você conhece ela?
Ela é uma seiyuu.
Sua namorada é uma seiyuu?!
Não. Eu sou só um fã.
R-Right...
Episódio 11: "Polícia Seiyuu, Move Out!"
My heart is with Yuppy
Yuppy is holding a birthday solo live concert na próxima semana.
Whoa! First editions!
And even store exclusives!
Oh! So you want to give her
a present at the concert?
Exato. Por isso quero que ele seja perfeito.
He only has the DVDs that
include Yuppy's character songs!
I want you to research her
favorite thing for me.
Pode deixar!
Oh! This is the T-shirt that sold out
instantly at her concert! I'm so jealous!
I can't wait to see the smile on her face quando você entregar o presente a ela.
No, I'm not handing her the present directly.
Wow! He even has this!
Oh, really?
That's weird!
Vocês não sabem de nada!
There'll be a box for presents at the
concert hall! I'm putting it in there!
Sheesh! You really "Doesn't
Know Anything," do you?!
R-Right...
For crying out loud!
We, her fans,
risk our lives to choose the best
present, for that very reason!
We consider Yuppy's feelings!
We think, think, think, think...
Therefore, we risk our lives to figure out
what will make Yuppy the happiest!
Uh, I see...
Tem CDs aqui também!
Darn it!
*It's just water. Takeuchi-kun is undergoing special training.
Gurushan! Ele tem Gurushan!
*Gurushan: short for Gurume Shampoo (Edible Shampoo)
*É só agua.
Oh, then...
H-How about a brand-name bag?
Girls love those.
You really don't get it, do you?!
Please forgive #1. She's the straight-laced type.
Wait, are you...
Oh, that's right. #3-chan adora seiyuus.
Você é fã da Yuppy também?
Eu sou uma DD...
*DD: Short for "dare demo daisuki" (loves everyone)
But as a fellow VA fan, eu entendo como você se sente, Takeuchi!
#3...
You want us to find a gift that best
shows your support for her, right?
Yes! That's right!
Leave it to me.
Eu vou achar o presente perfeito
to show Yuppy your support!
Okay! Polícia Seiyuu, move out!
Y-Yeah...
Polícia
Seiyuu
The Otokonoko Inspector   HackaDoll #3
The Fujoshi Inspector   HackaDoll #2
The Piece of Junk Inspector   HackaDoll #1
Pessoal! Obrigada por
coming out me ver hoje!
No! Thank you!
Tem algo importante que eu
preciso contar a vocês hoje...
Eu...
I'm retiring from voice acting today!
I'm going to quit voice acting so I
can travel the world and find myself.
Mas...
Sh-She's retiring...
But I've been her fan since day one...
Takeuchi-san.
If it had to end this way,
I wish I'd been born as
a blade of grass or a tree.
I'm going to quit being her fan!
Yuppy...
You don't understand Yuppy, do you, Takeuchi?
#3...
It's hard for Yuppy to say
goodbye to her fans, too.
That's why you need to give her
this present and cheer her up!
That's what a true fan does!
That's right. You mustn't give up.
This is surely your one chance!
Now, here's my last song,
"Doesn't Know Anything."
Yuppy...
Okay.
I want to hand this to her!
Eu quero dar isso pessoalmente a ela!
Okay! Let's go!
Presents
Go Here
Yuppy
Present Box
-4-
Yuppy
Present Box
-3-
Staff only.
Não entre.
She's over there!
Saiam do caminho!
There's no end to them.
Deixe eles comigo, Takeuchi. Vá na frente!
#3... Está bem!
I won't let you guys stop my love for Yuppy!
O meu...
My love for Yuppy...
is much greater
than this!
*It's just water. Takeuchi-kun is undergoing special training.
Yuppy!
Thanks for all your support,
Takeuchi-san.
Estou tão feliz por você, Takeuch—
E-Ele está morto.