Hey...
What do I mean to you, Ikuo?
Am I just a girl you grew up with?
Hey... What do I mean to you, Ikuo?
1. "Yes. Just a girl I grew up with."
2. "No. You're my girlfriend."
3. "Nothing. I don't even know you."
4. "..."
I'm so happy!
So now we're boyfriend and girlfriend!
As if this would ever happen.
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come into your room?
Your parents aren't home today, right?
Unexpected plot twist!
Well, if this were reality,
I'd never even get to know any girls.
Well, I'd better be a gentleman.
Hey... What do I mean to you, Ikuo?
Am I just a girl you grew up with?
Huh?
What the heck?!
I was just getting to the good part.
We are the Personal Entertainment
AI that syncs to you: HackaDolls!
Wait, what?
Just me?
A girl...
I wonder what happened to the other two.
A girl suddenly appeared in my room...
Hm, that sure is strange...
Wh-What sort of eroge is this?
Well, whatever.
Is there anything you wish
for me to advance for you?
Whoa... What do I do now?!
Episode 4: "Take a Shower First"
Calm down, Ikuo.
I'm not sure how it happened, but this
is my chance to get to know a girl!
First impressions are key!
Excuse me...
Yes?!
Would you tell me your name?
1. "..."
2. "My name is Ikuo. Nice to meet you!"
3. "Call me Kokuryuuin Ikuo-sama."
4. "I can't give away personal information..."
What the hell am I doing?!
In a game, this'd be a piece of cake!
Excuse me...
What should I call you?
1. "Call me Ikuo."
2. "Call me Iku-chan!"
3. "Call me Master."
4. "What the hell is HackaDoll #2 anyway?"
This time for sure!
I-Ikyuo ish my name.
This isn't working! I thought
I chose my words perfectly, too!
Ikuo-san?
Nice to meet you.
So cute.
Still, what about him shall I advance?
Uh, wait...
Let me clean up this mess.
Oh, yes! Cleaning!
I can do that for you.
Huh?! No, you don't need to...
U-Um...
1. "S-Sorry!"
2. "You'd better do as I say."
3. "Damn, you're cute."
4. "Heh, look, a wall slam! Didn't see that trope coming!"
Ah... Never mind! Just sit there.
Um, here, read this!
Damn it, this isn't working
like it does in games!
It almost feels like he's the one advancing me.
But I need to advance him at least a bit...
Excuse me, Ikuo-san?
Huh? Yeah...
What shall I do after this?
I can advance anything for you.
Shall we both lie down and relax?
Just kidding!
I-I'll get some drinks!
Ikuo-san?
I can advance anything for you.
Shall we both lie down and relax?
That smile is totally unfair.
"Shall we both lie down?"
Oh, crap... I haven't even done anything,
and yet it's all going so smoothly,
even in reality... Is that possible?
Anyway, gotta be a gentleman...
I-I'm back...
Oh, thank you.
Oh, dear... Look what you did to me...
S-S-Sorry!
I'm all wet.
Oh, well...
Uh, you should take a shower first!
Huh? O-Okay...
I'm supposed to be advancing Ikuo-san.
Why am I taking a shower instead?
Wh-What should I do next?
And why was I even summoned
here in the first place?
You should take a shower first!
O-Okay...
Huh... Could it be...
Could it be that's what this is all about?!
Oh... Oh, no...
What should I do?
Oh, what should I do?
Am I supposed to do something like this?
Sorry that was all I had for you to wear.
It's okay...
Um...
Oh, you first.
No, uh...
L-Let's watch TV...
Stare...
Don't mind me. Please continue.
Sorry for the wait!
I'm sorry! Gosh, you're all wet... Um, um...
I'm sorry about what #1-chan did.
Oh, it's okay...
Change of clothes.
Oh, thanks.
No peeking!
No touching, either!
Ikuo, I bought some pork buns!
Wait...
What are you...?!
1. "I just wanted you to have grandchildren..."
2. "Don't worry, we showered first."
3. "Uh, well, um..."
4. "This isn't what you think! Really!"
Ikuo, listen here...
Just because you're legally an adult now
doesn't mean you can bring home girls
in the middle of the day on a weekend...
And to your parents' house...
I mean, I don't mind!
I really don't, but I'd be so
humiliated if the neighbors saw...
And wait, isn't this that "cosplay" thing?
Cosplay? I dunno, but if it were
at least something more normal...
Dad, say something to him!