We're back.
Welcome home, you two.
Aqui, os ganhos de hoje da dungeon.
Os custos equipment costs for our weapons and such já foi deduzido.
I appreciate your help.
Vocês duas have been an invaluable asset
to our Familia desde que se juntaram.
Que gentileza a sua.
A propósito, what are your plans for
the quest you mentioned earlier?
We can take care of it ourselves, if necessary.
Retrieving rare medicinal herbs from a deserted island...
Sounds interesting, to say the least.
Actually...
Miach-sama has proposed bypassing the Guild and
putting in a personal request with Bell and the others.
A Familia da Hestia?
How come?
A lot has happened recently,
and their Familia has grown...
Ele queria parabenizá-los.
Bom, nada contra, mas...
Herbs de uma ilha deserta would be made into a medicine of immense worth...
We're going to turn a profit, independente de qual Familia we ask to retrieve them.
But Miach-sama insists on doubling
the reward for Bell-kun e os outros para celebrar.
É o quê?
E ele quer pagar adiantado.
What?!
Essentially, it's an invitation for a relaxing vacation.
Estou começando a sacar por que esta Familia está sempre com dívidas...
That's Miach-sama, for you.
Algo errado, mocinhas?
Glittering sunlight!
Um oceano azul!
White, sandy beaches!
Welcome to Paradise Island!
Here we are... on a deserted island named "Paradise"...
Yes. When you invited me here, pensei que era alguma piada.
You helped us out big time
during the War Game, Miss Elf!
Inviting you along was the least
we could do to repay you!
What a load of bull...
Whose idea was it to rely on her for protection from
any weird monsters that might be lurking around?
Listen here, Miss Supporter...!
The topics discussed at our Familia meetings
are strictly confidential!
The entire island's supposed to be
a treasure trove of rare herbs, right?
Yup, according to Naaza-sama.
Rumor has it, a mysterious, potent herb called an "Everything Flower" lies at the center of the island.
What exactly does it do?
As its name suggests, the herb has
unbe-leaf-able capabilities.
Was that a pun?!
There are stories of people falling in love
and bathing in tubs of gold with the herb in their possession.
Wow, that's amazing!
Seems suspicious, if you ask me...
Regardless, we were called upon to complete this quest.
Our job is to collect a supply of herbs and return home.
Let's start by splitting up and searching the island.
Welf and I will head towards the forest.
Everyone else should stick to the shore.
The heck are you talking about, Bell?!
We came all this way to Paradise Island.
Before we get to work, I say we go for a dip in the ocean!
Yeah!
Y-Yeah...!
Oh, but I... didn't bring a swimsuit with me.
What?!
What on Earth were you thinking, Bell-kun?!
How could you disappoint us like this, Bell-sama?!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry! I don't know what
I did wrong, but I'm sorry!
Smart move. Apologize now and ask questions later.
Oh well!
The rest of you go ahead and swim.
Bell-kun and I are busy keeping
an eye on the bags together.
Weren't you the one who wanted to
go swimming in the first place?!
Please allow me to look after Bell-sama!
I thought you wanted to
go seashell hunting or something!
Excuse me...
I wouldn't mind looking after Bell-sama...
Get your grubby tail off of him!
Y-Yes!
Well then, we'll just have to
let Bell-kun decide, won't we?!
I propose a swimsuit contest!
Sounds good to me!
Winner gets to spend the entire day
hanging out alone with Bell-kun?
Exactly what I was thinking!
M-May I participate, too?
Our contestants are currently
preparing their change of clothes.
What sort of exciting swimsuits do
they have in store for us today?
Perhaps I should have mentioned this earlier,
but I'm surprised the Guild allowed you
to leave Orario, Hestia-sama.
Well, I might've asked Ganesha for a favor.
Off the record, you know?
Seriously? Again?
What about the incident with the Kingdom of Rakia?
Don't be such a party pooper!
I refuse to be the only one left behind, especially
when everyone else gets to go to Paradise Island!
This is becoming an awfully bad habit of yours...
Whatever, it doesn't matter.
In this swimsuit contest, I shall be the victor!
Hestia has moved to the private changing area.
Let's take a quick peek!
Sneak...
Her swimsuit...?
If they think they can beat me with boring swimsuits like that, they are sorely mistaken.
Besides, Bell-kun and I share memories together
that they don't even know about.
After I hang out with Bell for the entire day,
the two of us will finally...!
I... want to be with you, Goddess.
I feel the same way, Bell-kun.
You don't understand, Goddess.
I want to spend the whole night by your side.
Just the two of us.
Bell-kun!
I can't believe it's actually happening!
After all this time...!
Please refrain from punching
the cameraman with your panties!
Hestia-sama has been acting way
out of line towards Bell-sama lately.
Whenever I ask what happened at the village
in the mountains, she refuses to answer me...
Am I supposed to sit back and let her do whatever
she wants just because she's a Goddess?!
Bell-sama is going to pick Lili for sure.
And then...!
Too late!
Bell-sama...
Albeit small, Lili is a beautiful girl who hides
her trauma underneath a tough exterior,
and the only people she isn't afraid
to let see her cry are the ones closest to her...
Are you sure that's what you want?!
Of course. I love you exactly the way you are, Lili.
Bell-sama...!
Yes, yes! Perfect!
Although I've volunteered to participate,
Bell-sama would never grant
his affections upon one such as I...
But I would be grateful if his kindness
were to rub off on me!
Haruhime-dono...
When you say things like that,
you risk gaining a reputation as a closeted pervert.
If you wish to have Bell-dono,
confronting him directly would be the wisest option.
"Have" him...?
Mikoto, what are you implying...?
Bell-sama, why haven't
you brought a swimsuit with you?
I'm sorry, Haruhime-sama.
But I don't need one.
After all, we won't be wearing clothes for long.
Collarbones... A gentleman...!
It's the moment you've all been waiting for.
In honor of our visit to Paradise Island:
The Hestia Familia Swimsuit Competition!
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen.
My name is Welf, and I'll be
your host for today's festivities!
Make sure you rank 'em fairly.
Rank them? But-
Moving on!
In lieu of a practice round, let's kick off
the competition with an unofficial participant!
Incredible!
She may be ineligible to win,
but her swimsuit is hideously lame!
Has a mystery of the Far East emerged
from the recesses of an old lady's closet before our very eyes?!
The tacky style and form-fitting material work
in tandem to accentuate her figure.
Such an advanced approach is meant
to appeal to the male psyche.
Very impressive, Ryu-san!
I'm a lvl. 4.
Moving on!
We will now begin the judging round. Please welcome our first official contestant to the stage!
Huh?
That's not a swimsuit...
There she is! A Goddess, through and through!
True to its name, Paradise Island has blessed us
with a plump and bountiful harvest!
Well? What do you think, Bell-kun?
Tell me exactly how you feel. Don't hold back!
I-I think you look nice...
Her large chest and small body are
in stark contrast with one another.
The use of leaves in place of a swimsuit strikes
the perfect balance between flashy and lewd.
It's so well-crafted that I wouldn't mind wearing it myself.
What?
Please welcome our next contestant!
Incredible!
A key component of every good swimsuit competition!
Going so far as to bring her own cheesy prop from
home... The mark of a skilled tactician!
An exercise in supply and demand, to be sure.
Though childlike in some ways, there's
a certain erotic charm to her shapelier features.
Bell-sama!
Where did you even get that thing?
"Always be prepared" or whatever...
And now, please welcome our final contestant.
Amazing!
What a sight for sore eyes!
An ordinary swimsuit without any sort of gimmick in
sight!
How simplistic...
The epitome of innocence!
Posing as though forced to enter
the competition by her friends!
The more she shies away from the audience, the greater her appeal becomes.
Even Bell can't resist!
His eyes are glued to the spot, folks!
Could this be the end?!
Objection!
Talk about underhanded!
You're being totally unfair, Haruhime!
H-have I done something wrong...?
That attitude is exactly what we're talking about!
It wasn't my intention...
Y-You've got it wrong!
Haruhime-dono isn't nearly
the closeted pervert you think she is!
Come on, Bell-kun!
Time to decide the winner!
Huh? U-Uh...
I'm the obvious choice, right?
Why not pick Lili, Bell-sama?
If you don't mind one such as I...
Nope! He picks me!
W-Well...
U-Um, I think you all look nice...
Dodging the question by declaring everyone
a winner after all that effort would be...
insulting at best.
Huh?
Ladies and gentlemen, it's the moment of truth!
Which of our lucky contestants will get
to keep Bell all to herself for an entire day?!
Ais-san...?
What?!
I-Incredible! The Sword Princess swoops in for the kill!
An unexpected victory from a surprise opponent!
That's against the rules!
She isn't even wearing a swimsuit!
But Bell has the final say...
Me and my Familia arrived here earlier today...
Hi! My name is Ais Wallenstein!
Tee-hee!
"Tee-hee"...?
After a quick examination,
it appears the Sword Princess has lost all
of her memories outside of her own name.
She's got amnesia, eh?
That explains the completely uncharacteristic smile...
More than likely, she fell over and
hit her head on something.
Judging by the swelling, at least.
Surprised she managed a bump
that big in broad daylight...
Only on Paradise Island, I suppose...
Check it out! A sea cucumber!
Gross!
Come on, try it with me!
Wha-?
U-Um, Ais-san... You shouldn't
mess with living creatures...
Can't you do something about this, Miss Elf?
You dropped this...
If we don't bring the Sword Princess' memories back soon,
this could have a major effect on
the balance of power between Familias!
Tee-hee!
There is only one way to cure her:
The mysterious herb I mentioned earlier, the Everything Flower.
Having the herb in our possession
should treat any ailment.
Keeping watch sure is boring...
I'm quite used to waiting, myself...
Listen, Wallen-whatsit...
What is it?
This may come as a shock to you, but before losing
your memories, you were in love with someone.
Oh! With who?!
It was...
the boy who went to search for herbs, Welf!
Wow!
Now I understand...
Wait, what's she talking about?!
Why would she say that?!
That hunk in the swim trunks was my darling...?
There's no guarantee whether this will have
a lasting effect once her memories return...
What about the rabbit boy?
You ought to quit while you're ahead.
The two of you would be a disaster together!
Thank goodness you told me!
I'd never lie to you!
What a snake! A real goddess, through and through!
Sure isn't easy to find, is it?
Figured as much from this "mysterious" herb...
Let's take a break and check in with the others.
You're continuing on with the search, Ryu-dono?
Much appreciated.
Welcome back, honey!
Would you like a bath? How about dinner?
Or perhaps... you'd like me?
What?!
The hell are you talking about?!
Get away from me!
No!
Don't touch me!
I want to stay with my darling!
W-W-Welf...
Since when are you and Ais-san...?!
W-Wait, Bell!
Welf, you jerk!
You handsome, magic sword-hating blacksmith
with your hunky swim trunks...!
He's gone!
Bell!
It appears I've gotten myself hopelessly lost...
And I haven't located the Everything Flower, either.
Which direction leads back to the shore...?
This place...
Us Elves have an affinity for bathing in the forest,
and this lake looks to be empty...
Could it be...?
The Everything Flower!
I-I suppose I've got no choice.
In order to retrieve it, I must bathe in this lake.
Cranel-san isn't around to spy on me this time...
He wouldn't do that, would he?
Certainly not...
You definitely aren't here, are you?
We can use this to help the Sword Princess...
Cranel-san?!
Wasn't that Ryu-sama's voice?
Seriously?
What the heck is going on with this island?
Bell still hasn't woken up, and now Miss Elf...
I'll go check on her!
Let me come with you.
It's dangerous to go alone.
It should only take a moment.
If I run into trouble, I'll turn back.
Where on Earth has Ryu-dono gone?
This scent...
Impossible!
A secluded hot spring in the middle of the forest,
rife with health benefits?!
Could it be...?
The Everything Flower?!
I-I suppose I've got no choice.
In order to retrieve it, I must take a dip in this hot spring!
What a nice-
Wasn't that Mikoto's voice?!
Again?
No way... Mikoto-sama, too?
Hestia-sama... I'll go investigate.
Hold on, Welf. If something were to happen...
Don't worry.
If I sense any sort of danger, I'll come back.
That's exactly what Mikoto said...
Could this foreshadowing get any more obvious...?
What the...?
A glowing forge with the perfect setup
and no one else around...
I knew it!
Hello!
I am Ryu!
I am Mikoto!
And I am Ganesha!
Look... They've all got bumps on their heads!
Just like Wallen-whatsit...
"You gotta be kidding me!"
And now they're behaving just like her, too...
Check it out! A sea cucumber!
Gross!
The symptoms are exactly the same!
They must've fallen and hit
their heads like the Sword Princess...
We can't rely on them anymore...
There's only one thing left to do!
We have to search for the Everything Flower ourselves!
Track it down and save everyone's butts!
Failure is not an option! Bell is our top priority!
"You gotta be kidding me!"
Ais-san...?
Huh?
What?
What?!
N-No...
Goddess...
It can't be...
Everyone met the same fate as
Miss Ais while I was unconscious?!
Check it out! A sea cucumber!
Gross!
The symptoms are exactly the same!
Wh-Why is this happening?
Everyone must've hit their heads on something
and lost their memories like Miss Ais...
Throw a big ol' slab on the grill!
Cook 'em up nice 'n juicy!
It's as if they've turned into completely different people...
Time to toss the sea cucumbers!
Check it out! A sea cucumber!
Gross!
G-Goddess... Lili...
Ais-san!
Get ahold of yourself, Ais-san!
Bell? Is that you?
Her bump...
A mushroom?
Bell!
Ais-san?!
Bell-kun? Is that you, Bell-kun?
Bell-sama... Oh, how I've missed you...
Cranel-san?
There has to be some sort of mistake!
Ais-san can't turn into a mushroom! It's not possible!
Hey! Calm down, Bell!
Bell-dono!
Bell... That hurts.
I-I'm sorry...
Bell-san, it seems we're no longer gods nor humans.
Somehow, we've been turned into mushroom creatures!
Goddess...
We might be stuck in these bodies for
the rest of our lives...
But the thought of rotting away on this island
in the middle of nowhere is too agonizing to bear!
Please, Bell...
Bring us home. Let us see the sunshine in Orario!
I know we can count on you, Bell-dono!
I beg of you, Cranel-san...
Save us!
You're right...
My friends are my friends,
whether they're mushrooms or not!
I swear I'll bring you back to Orario safely!
And how do you plan on doing that, Bell Cranel?
Finn-san! What are you doing here?!
A mushroom is a mushroom,
regardless of the circumstances...
And I will destroy every last one!
Back off, you damn mushrooms!
Quit your shouting, lowly little mushrooms!
Ooh, these mushrooms seem a little wound up.
What do you think of that?!
I'm going to take your sweet mushrooms all for myself!
Let the mighty Kingdom of Rakia strike fear
into the hearts of Orario's mushrooms!
E-Everyone else, too?!
These mushrooms are mine!
I'm bringing them back home to Orario with me!
For what reason would we submit
to the whims of a child?
Onward!
Where did that mountain come from?!
It can't be...!
Another... vision?
Another vision?!
Oh Cassandra, what a strange child you are.
Come on, Daphne-san!
I really, really mean it this time!
Be that as it may,
Bell-kun and the others set out
to complete the quest several days ago.
What?
They're due to return soon.
What?!
Don't you remember?
Cassandra, you've been asleep for nearly a week.
Oh! Good to see you, Bell.
Welcome.
You must be exhausted from such a long journey.
Have a seat, Bell.
Tell us the riveting tale
of your visit to Paradise Island.