Bonus anime:
Seraph of the Endless!
Number 8
Major General Hiiragi Shinya of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
I will now present my report regarding the vampires' abnormal movements in the Kansai area.
Hey, Ichinose.
Ichinose Guren!
Is the long-ass meeting finally over?
Now, what's with that attitude?
Know your place, Ichinose.
My, if it isn't Hiiragi Tenri-sama. My apologies.
I was incredibly bored, you see.
Don't get too conceited.
Well, his attitude is nothing new.
I'll continue my report.
I'm outta here.
Just give me the important details later.
Come on, Guren.
Even I can't back you up if you act like that.
And who asked you to back me up?
Geez...
Besides, the Japanese Imperial Demon Army is all but run by the mighty Hiiragi family.
Someone from a branch family like me doesn't belong here.
Oh, I see you understand.
Hurry up and get the hell out of here then, scum.
That's what I'm trying to do.
Catch you later.
Geez.
Huh?
Welcome back.
Why...?
Just what the hell's going on?
Umm...
Forget something?
Or so you thought—!
Welcome to Shinya's problem counselling room!