Broken memories hurt, don't they?
itainda ne kowasareta omoide wa
I've been betrayed countless, countless times.
nandomo nandomo uragirareru
But since I'm alive, it's okay to trust...
kedo shinjiteitai yo ikiteitai nara
Even if it's futile to have faith.
shinjitatte muda demo
I learned there's nothing in this world more isolating than myself.
watashi ijou no kodoku wa kono yo ni nai tte wakatta
But despite that, I'm still holding on to hope...
soredemo kibou o motteru nowa
It's funny.
waracchau
It's like a habit. Maybe it's just for peace of mind?
shuukan mitai na mono kiyasume datte koto kana
Is this the end?
mohaya kore made
End, world.
sekai oware
I'm waiting... I can't wait... I've been waiting!
matteru... matteru... matteta na
I'm still sane, though, believe it or not. For now. Probably.
shouki dayo, kore demo ne tabun wa na
Who gets to decide?
matte yo, kimeru na
I'm waiting... I can't wait... I've been waiting!
matteru... matteru... mattetanda yo
I won't let it be called love.
fani da nante iwasenai
That would be too convenient.
zutto yo, suki
It's just a pure obsession.
tada no shuuchaku dayo
Whitewashing things is so much fun.
yume ni nattemo tanoshimi dane
It's fun to pretend I'm the only one who's pure.
jibunra kimaru kirai na furi tanoshimi dane