Hospital Geral Squid Black Light
Hey, glad you came.
You guys are the ones that can
advance anything, right?
Sim! Somos as Hackadolls!
Bem, the reason I summoned you is because...
We want you guys to fight monsters
for us while enquanto estamos aqui no hospital.
We got a little carried
away in the movie version.
The founder took it too seriously.
She blew away a building com as próprias mãos.
I can't hold a candle to her!
So that's why we need your help.
Por hoje, hang out at the embankment
on Third, and they'll show up.
Hum... Quem exatamente vai aparecer?
Praying for your speedy recovery.
Quem mais? The monsters!
-The Neighborhood Big Friend Association
We can sense that sort of thing.
Okay, get out there and be
Magical Girl Lovely Hurt!
Okay! We'll do our best!
Episódio 12: "Garota Mágica Lovely Hurt"
I can't believe we get
to help Lovely Hurt-san!
Um gorila, né?
That was a gorilla, wasn't it?
We're so lucky to get a big gig like
this in our second-to-last episode.
But... Will the monsters really show up here?
Aaaaaaah
What's that?!
Today, as any other day,
we stare for no reason at the
girls who walk down the street...
We wave at them.
We greet them with smiles.
And we create incidents!
Mama!
Don't look at them.
It's the evil monsters!
They really did show up...
We need to transform, you guys!
Yes!
Stop right there!
Who's there?!
A HackaD-rive in the blazing sunlight!
Lovely #1!
A HackaDo-rhythm, waving in the breeze.
Lovely #2!
HackaDo-romance with the scent the ocean.
Lovely #3!
Juntas, nós somos as...
Magical Girl Lovely Hurt!
Magical Girl
Whoa! It's Lovely Hurt!
Kick the bad guys' butts!
Vocês parecem um pouco diferentes,
but there you are, Lovely Hurt!
Victory to the swiftest! Here I come!
Bring it on!
Ouch!
Don't dodge it! Elbow him!
Quit slacking! Grab him
from behind and throw him!
Qual o problema?
Come at me with your usual
focus on physical blows!
Ow, ow, ow!
He doesn't fly away when punched,
like they do on TV!
O que você está fazendo?!
Use Lovely Folding Chair to
beat him to a bloody pulp!
Get out your Lovely Bar, morons!
#1-chan!
Você não vai se safar dessa!
Não!
Looks like you're having
an off-day, Lovely Hurt!
I'll defeat you swiftly so I'll have
time to stop by the cleaners after!
Hold it!
Nothing can be seen in a world of darkness.
However!
Se fechar seus olhos,
you can see a tiny bit of light.
I call that light "hope"!
Quem diabos é você?!
I need not tell the likes of you!
#4-chan, what are you doing?
I am a substitute for the heroes
who hurt themselves in the movie!
Manami
Akino
Saori
Last night was wonderful.
Heroes just keep coming to
thwart me, one after the next...
Nesse ritmo,
I'll never be able to make this a happy and healthy town!
Huh? You weren't going for world domination?
Stop your whining!
All right! I'll just have to crush you!
And now the final blow!
Idiota! O que você está fazendo?!
Look what you did to our town!
Put it back!
Huh? That's easier said than done...
Huh? This pattern again?
Something is seriously wrong here!
So this is the end... How regrettable.
Kaijin-san...
I wanted to clean up this town.
I wanted this town to be a safe place
for all the little children who live here.
Eu queria que todos aqui sorrissem.
However!
Those impetuous magical girls, those
transforming heroes, always attack me!
We were only trying to make
this town a better place!
Poor guy.
I understand!
Right!
Kaijin-san, estávamos erradas sobre você.
We thought you were bad guys.
We'll help you clean up this town!
You'll really help me?
Sim!
Pode deixar com as Hackadolls!
Começando hoje, we collaborate
with the evil monsters!
É o início de um novo grupo!
Novas fantasias!
Hacka...dolls!
New costumes to commemorate the founding of a new group. These new
wrestlers' motto is to make this town a clean and beautiful place.
Don't miss this battle of historic proportions!
Lovely Hurt vs. Captain Evil Monster