Bonus anime:
Seraph of the Endless!
Number 7
As a general rule, Annihilation Units always move in groups of 5.
If you encounter an armed vampire with fewer than 5 people,
there's a good chance you'll be killed.
Now that we're beyond the wall,
I won't allow any of you to split up or act on your own.
Got it?
So he says.
Are you okay with that, Mr. Reckless?
I can't promise anything.
If I happen to see a vampire in front of me, I might just—
What're ya doin'?
You've got terrible reactions.
One more try.
Alright.
So he says.
Are you okay with that, Mr. Reckless?
I can't promise anything.
If I happen to see a vampire in front of me, I might just—
A feint?!
Too careless.
One... One more try.
So he says.
Are you okay with that, Mr. Reckless?
I can't promise anything.
If I happen to see a vampire in front of me, I might just—
This time for sure!
Wha—
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle...
You're just too careless.