Bonus anime:
Seraph of the Endless!
Number 9
There's nothing in the past.
But what you have is the future!
Shut up.
Alrighty!
You've all got your Demonic Arms, and we've actually managed some teamwork.
Let's head over to the front lines, shall we?
The front lines?!
That's right.
The Kansai vampires are planning to recapture Shinjuku.
We'll be going over there to have a look.
So I'll get to kill some vampires, then?
Th-The front lines, all of a sudden?
Don't we get a break or something?
It sure is tough to raise kids.
Right?
It's hard work, getting children to grow and advance.
Where the hell did you come from?!
Where? From behind you, of course.
Don't be like that.
I'm always protecting you.
Huh?
I don't remember ever being protected.
Oh, come on.
I've always been covering your back through Byakkomaru's eyes.
Thanks to that, we've shared a lot of fond memories together.
Memories?
Would you like to... see them?
What the hell is that?
Now, now. Just look.
What a great smile, don't you think?
Oh, there's also this one.
A time-limited papaya-flavoured drink.
The aftertaste was terrible, wasn't it?
Oh, what's this?
How adorable.
Oh!
These are some very precious photos
of when you stubbed your little toe on a table right after coming out of the shower
and spilled your unfinished milk all around the room
as you fell to the ground crying in agony.
This one's a treasure for sure.
I'll always cherish this collection.
Huh?
Get back here, you little...!
I'm gonna kill you!