Don't go!
We'll miss you!
Yuppy!
Yuppy
They're here.
Let's put in another good day's work, yo!
She said "yo."
The Personal Entertainment AI
that syncs up to you: HackaDolls!
What do you wish of us today?
I want you to get the perfect
present for this girl.
What a drag...
Oh?
Wow! She's pretty!
Is she your girlfriend?
Oh, he has a real life...
Oh! It's Yuppy!
Do you know her?
She's a voice actress.
Your girlfriend is a voice actress?!
No. I'm just a fan.
R-Right...
Episode 11: "VA Police, Move Out!"
My heart is with Yuppy
Yuppy is holding a birthday
solo live concert next week.
Whoa! First editions!
And even store exclusives!
Oh! So you want to give her
a present at the concert?
Yes. That's why I want it to be perfect.
He only has the DVDs that
include Yuppy's character songs!
I want you to research her
favorite thing for me.
Very well!
Oh! This is the T-shirt that sold out
instantly at her concert! I'm so jealous!
I can't wait to see the smile on her face
when you hand her the present.
No, I'm not handing her the present directly.
Wow! He even has this!
Oh, really?
That's weird!
You know nothing!
There'll be a box for presents at the
concert hall! I'm putting it in there!
Sheesh! You really "Doesn't
Know Anything," do you?!
R-Right...
For crying out loud!
We, her fans,
risk our lives to choose the best
present, for that very reason!
We consider Yuppy's feelings!
We think, think, think, think...
Therefore, we risk our lives to figure out
what will make Yuppy the happiest!
Uh, I see...
There are CDs in here, too!
Darn it!
*It's just water. Takeuchi-kun is undergoing special training.
Gurushan! He has Gurushan!
*Gurushan: short for Gurume Shampoo (Edible Shampoo)
*It's just water.
Oh, then...
H-How about a brand-name bag?
Girls love those.
You really don't get it, do you?!
Please forgive #1. She's the straight-laced type.
Wait, are you...
Oh, that's right. #3-chan loves voice actors.
You're a Yuppy fan, too?
I'm a DD...
*DD: Short for "dare demo daisuki" (loves everyone)
But as a fellow VA fan, I understand
how you feel, Takeuchi!
#3...
You want us to find a gift that best
shows your support for her, right?
Yes! That's right!
Leave it to me.
I'll find the perfect present
to show Yuppy your support!
Okay! VA Police, move out!
Y-Yeah...
VA Police
The Otokonoko Inspector
HackaDoll #3
The Fujoshi Inspector
HackaDoll #2
The Piece of Junk Inspector
HackaDoll #1
Hey, guys! Thank you for
coming out to see me today!
No! Thank you!
There's something important
I need to tell you all today...
I...
I'm retiring from voice acting today!
I'm going to quit voice acting so I
can travel the world and find myself.
But...
Sh-She's retiring...
But I've been her fan since day one...
Takeuchi-san.
If it had to end this way,
I wish I'd been born as
a blade of grass or a tree.
I'm going to quit being her fan!
Yuppy...
You don't understand Yuppy, do you, Takeuchi?
#3...
It's hard for Yuppy to say
goodbye to her fans, too.
That's why you need to give her
this present and cheer her up!
That's what a true fan does!
That's right. You mustn't give up.
This is surely your one chance!
Now, here's my last song,
"Doesn't Know Anything."
Yuppy...
Okay.
I want to hand this to her!
I want to give it to her personally!
Okay! Let's go!
Presents
Go Here
Yuppy
Present Box
-4-
Yuppy
Present Box
-3-
Staff only.
Do not enter.
She's over there!
Out of the way!
There's no end to them.
Leave them to me, Takeuchi. You go ahead!
#3... Okay!
I won't let you guys stop my love for Yuppy!
My...
My love for Yuppy...
is much greater
than this!
*It's just water. Takeuchi-kun is undergoing special training.
Yuppy!
Thanks for all your support,
Takeuchi-san.
I'm so glad for you, Takeu—
H-He's dead.