Please, give me that.
If you say "that" I don't understand.
Airi, come on. Answer back. What do you want?
I want your life power.
It isn't a simple life power, right?
I want your precious and radiant life power.
I can't wait anymore.
This is your limit? It's a disappointment.
A dog would hold more.
Airi, what are you?
I'm Elina-sama's slave.
Without your life power, I can't live.
That's why I want your life power, please. Give to your dirty slave life power.
Start here.
Ok.
Let's go. Don't despair so much. You are dirty.
Elina-sama, if you like this, you can scream.
You sound very arrogant to be a slave.
Elina-sama...
Open your mouth.
Yes.
You're dirty.
When I met you three days ago, you were very arrogant.
But you already got used to being a slave.
Elina-sama... more please.
I don't have any other option.
Queen's Blade.
That is the name that the gods gave to the battles between beautiful girls.
The Bitoushi are chosen by angels, and they're responsible to fight for their desires.
The one who loses in that battle must fulfill the desire of the winner.
Elina.
Claudette-onee-sama.
So you'll go find her, huh?
Take it.
The spear of rumors?
The world is dangerous.
Didn't our father order you not to let me go out and look for her?
I'm weak to beer.
While I was drinking, you asked me if you could go, and I couldn't refuse the request.
Onee-sama...
Bring Leina back.
I'm counting on you, Elina.
Leina-onee-sama...
I can't believe that you escaped from the castle and have faced each other in a battle of Queen's Blade.
I must find you before you lose the battle and fulfill a strange promise.
Please wait.
I tell you to wait!
Why are you running away?
Obviously I'll run away if you persecute me.
Don't you listen when I talk to you?
T-This is...
So are the things.
There's no doubt what that light is.
Although it would be dangerous to approach me.
I want information. I heard that you have.
Oh yeah?
I heard that you were the one with information.
Further...
I'm a very dangerous person capable of killing, abducting and more.
Still, believing in you, I came to see you alone.
I want information.
You have guts.
Leina ended up involved with a person from a Bitoushi organization.
This organization only seeks victory.
It isn't a battle that she has chosen.
His opponent is a well-known Bitoushi.
From the Kouya clan, Listi.
What I know is that Listi was defeated by Leina.
Onee-sama is incredible.
There was no way he would lose with a low-grade Bitoushi.
I heard that Leina, after having beaten Listi, will goes to Maramax.
Maramax? The place of fairy tales?
It isn't a place of fairy tales.
So it exists.
This is all I know since I can remember.
Wait!
If you follow the road to Maramax, you'll have a better chance of finding Leina.
Maramax...
A place where many Bitoushi are found.
The demons use the Bitoushi as their harem, it's a place full of impurity and it's cursed.
If something like that existed, where would it be?
What the hell?
Where do you think you are putting your face?!
Sorry!
Excuse me!
What things.
Oh? He's pretty cute.
Isn't here! It's terrible!
That!
Don't do that!
What happens? You're making strange noises.
O-Onee-san... give me back that.
Huh?
Give it back to me quickly or she'll reach me.
What is that? A beast?
Is she chasing you?
That boy, Michael Rivalanshiel-sama, belongs to my mistress.
I'm nobody's.
So you still don't accept being to her.
I don't want to hear that.
I don't know where you are from. But if you want to live, you can leave.
A Queen's Blade will start!
Michael, what do you say?
Huh?
Do you want me to save you?
Save me!
Save me, Onee-san!
The duty of a noble is to protect the weak, those who flee.
Onee-san!
So you define it as a connection of nobility.
My name is Airi, I'm a maid.
I accept your challenge!
It's a shame!
Sorry, but I'm not a Bitoushi!
I can't fight with you!
Have a nice day, Airi!
Please wait!
If Michael-sama is taken by a Bitoushi, I would have to fight with her to perform the exchange.
Of course, the one who wins, would have the right to choose what she wants.
It was a perfect plan, but...
I can't believe that she isn't a Bitoushi.
Run to the port! It's a Queen's Blade!
Melpha against Nowa!
What a bad time!
Senal Pose!
Sokubako!
Repent!
There is nothing that I should repent!
It's delicious.
E-Eh... Thank you, Elina.
Tell me Elina-sama.
Yes! Elina-sama.
Do you think it's ok? I have many things to ask you.
First, why did she persecute you?
I don't remember it well.
When I woke up, I was in the woods and that girl was chasing me.
I don't remember anything else.
I saw everything half blurry.
Do you have amnesia?
Also, I heard a strange voice in my head.
It told me to find a strong Bitoushi to go to Maramax.
Maramax?
Melpha, the Senal Pose is very difficult.
Of course. It's something that can be done after a hard workout.
I see. I was lucky not to have fallen before it.
The Senal Pose is very shameful. I must practice more.
More.
It's easy to scare you, Melpha.
It's just a flute. Look.
What happens?
Nothing.
What is this? It's broken. It doesn't emit any sound.
Wonderful. That's something I can't do.
It was not my intention to do it.
Let's wash it and return it to its place.
I'll help you!
You have to do it gently.
Understood.
Maybe my encounter with this boy has been predestined.
If I go to Maramax, I will surely find Onee-sama.
I have to believe and follow.
Fine! I already decided. I'll be a Bitoushi and I will protect you.
Huh? Its aspect...
It's getting bigger.
It seems that it has a strange power.
Is it a bad power?
No. The master of this flute has a strong life power.
Calm down! Calm down, me!
This is nothing!
So it can become so big.
It's clean now.
Leave it in the highest basket.
Hey! Are you ok?
-Amazing!
-You can't see, Nowa-san!
Enough! Bring a towel!
What's up with this flute?
I don't know.
Why do you make strange moans?
I told you to stop!
Don't!
Do it again.
Dared.
Please. It seems that I'm going to remember something.
Play it.
That flute is Cathedral.
When it's played and my body is near, the key to Maramax is activated.
Cathedral should only be played when you want to go to Maramax.
I saw the road to Maramax!
What happens?
It was a life power with good flavor.
I'll return Michael and Mateki Cathedral to my mistress.
Well, have a nice night.
Turning your back on your enemy is a great oversight.
It must be a joke! Do you still have life power?
Yes of course. By the way, let's fix things.
What is this?
Fine! I'm sorry to interrupt you! I'm an elite angel, Nanael-sama! Here I introduce myself!
You're lucky.
One that wants to get something and another with the courage to defend it! They are apt to be Bitoushi!
Angel Nanael?
Elina-sama, take it.
Play it!
My power...
Hey, I'm talking seriously. Do you hear me?
Eh... Elina Vance, do you want to be a Bitoushi?
Understood! In the name of Nanael, I turn you into a Bitoushi!
Airi, now I'm proposing you a duel.
It's what I wanted!
I'll start the battle!
Putting your titles as Bitoushi into fight, say your wish!
Wish?
My wish is that Elina doesn't get involved with Michael again.
My wish...
Come on, decide fast.
I'll decide after winning.
Is that possible?!
I don't know. But I'm the one who decides!
That's why...!
Queen's Blade, start!
How reckless!
Michael, stay behind.
Let's go! Show me a good battle!
Bitoushi, show me everything without holding back, fight to get your wishes!
I don't plan on doing what you say!
You are very naive. You can't hurt me with that weapon.
This spear...
Coming from a powerful sanctuary, it's the weapon that carries a lot of feelings.
With Claudette's prayers, this spear possesses all of Elina's wrath inside.
Can you face the power of this spear?
I'll not let you do it again!
It's time to end with this!
Ability of the Vance legacy! Ougi!
Ryuusei!
Take this!
I can't believe that I'm losing...
Well, it's over!
Choose your wish, winner.
Fine...
Then, you are forbidden to receive life power from any other person than me.
The orders of the Queen's Blade winner are absolute.
And if I oppose the orders, I'll have to fight against Nanael.
I'll also stop being Bitoushi.
I agree.
Well done.
Then I'm leaving. Keep having good fights!
Bye bye!
Come, I'll give you life power.
Lift your face.
This is...
This is the proof of your loyalty to me.
Now you're my slave.
If you force to leave, it will hurt. And the chains weigh, so that's fine.
We'll go to Maramax.
You can also come with us.
Well, if you can live without my life power, you don't have to come.
Understood.
Before that, we should bathe again.
We sweat a lot.
I'll wash your back, Elina-sama.
You'll enter alone!
F-Fine.
It's very heavy...
There's no other option. I don't have a horse.
I had a good idea!
Elina-sama, don't you want to train?
If you do, you can travel even without these things.
Denied. To be able to make jokes you must wear the maid costume.