A Totally Live Request
Hi! Thanks for your call!
HackaDolls here!
O quê? Seu filho está jogando jogos
Yoshie         Masafumi
(Masako)                 Satoru
You
Tetsuya                  (Yuuto)                .
A hikikomori gamer.
Won't leave room.
[I want to eat least eat dinner as a family.]
no quarto dele and won't come out?
Never fear! Em horas como essa...
Você pode contar com as HackaDolls!
You who have inherited the
soul of the sealed dragon,
é hora de salvar o mundo!
Sword Quest Online: Royale!
Episódio 9: "Nada Pode Me Parar But Routine Tuesday Maintenance"
S-So this is SQO...
The latest games are amazing!
Os jogos da DeNA são os melhores do mundo!
So it's great that we're here, but...
How shall we procurar por ele?
Let's go to town and ask around!
Com licença...
Wahoo!! Wanna meet up IRL?
Woo-hoo!! You guys are cute! Wanna meet up IRL?
Uh...
Oh, there are also people over there.
Um...
Com licença...
Um... Can I
fap to you?
Er, um...
Hmm...
Been a while, has it?
Poor guy...
Hmm...
Been a while, has it?
Poor guy...
Okay.
Score!!
Acho que ele está ocupado...
Com licença!
Nós estamos procurando por alguém chamado Shimada Yuuto-san.
Yuuto?
Oh, eu acabei de ver ele in the back alley.
O-Obrigada.
You've got some pretty nice bewbs.
Bye.
Todo mundo aqui é tão estranho...
Você é o Yuuto-san?
Meu nome é Yuuto.
The dark knight clad in darkness, Yuuto!
Yeah, Shimada Yuuto-san, right?
Ele parece diferente da foto.
The discrepancy with my real appearance
is of no importance.
Yuuto-san, por favor saia do seu quarto.
Sua mãe está preocupada com você.
Eu não posso fazer isso.
I am fated to spend my days in
combat para proteger o mundo de SQO.
Eu não posso fugir da batalha.
A gaming otaku, huh?
Nada pode me parar but
routine Tuesday maintenance!
O-O que foi?
Pardon me. Banheiro.
Oh! So you can leave your room.
I'm going to use this item. Excuse me!
Uma garrafa?
Yuuto-san, let's have a proper talk now, okay?
Ué? Você é uma garota?
Meu avatar é. Pretty moe, right?
A verdade é que...
I am currently in Kazuya's evil
clutches and cannot quit SQO.
Kazuya-san?
O jogador mais forte de SQO.
He's the head da minha guilda.
Until I can defeat the dark dragon
in the dungeon and obtain
the rare Crimson Drop that he desires,
Don't log out without my permission.
New Year's? That means
fewer rivals. Vamos caçar.
Mundo real?                   This ain't child's play.
Sever your ties.
To be frank, if I give the word, I can get over
half the players in this server on my side.
Real life plans... No one has those.
Give me your email and cell number so I can slap you awake.
I quit high school.
That's how hardcore
you should be.
Stick to it until the traitors retreat.
I haven't logged out
once since launch.
Install this on your work PC.
We're putting our lives on the line here.
I'm going to talk to a GM I know about the problems.
I am unable to log out.
Kazuya chamando
Aceitar
Rejeitar
É o Kazuya-san!
'Sup?
Yes, yes...
Um, minha mãe está meio brava,
so may I log out for a moment?
Ah... Of course! No, I'm not messing with you.
SQO pode ser um jogo, but it's not child's play.
Uhn? Within the day? Right...
Okay. Bye...
It would seem my powers
alone are insufficient.
If only someone would
volunteer to join my fight,
I'd quit being a hikikomori
and go to the temp agency!
Nós vamos ajudar você!
Nós vamos te ajudar a ter sua vida real de volta, Yuuto-san!
Obrigado... I am grateful for your friendship.
Mas vocês vão ficar bem com esse equipamento?
Uh... No, we won't.
Please accept this token of my friendship!
Let us go forth! Para a dungeon do dragão negro!
Wooser Plains
Go! Go!
Keep going!
Wooser Plains
Anyone running away is an enemy!
Anyone not running away
is a well-trained enemy!
Wooser Plains
Dark Dragon's Dungeon
Certo! O dragão negro deve estar in here.
Everyone, charge!
Dark Dragon's Dungeon
Wait, just us?
Charge!
Dark Dragon's Dungeon
I got the coveted Crimson Drop!
#4-chan?
Por quê?
I got the treasure before you!
Isso não importa. Apenas devolva!
O Yuuto-san não pode voltar para o mundo real sem isso!
If you want it, then take it by force!
If that's how it is...
We'll just have to fight you!
Nope! Not even close!
I see an opening!
Agora, #1-chan!
Not even close!
Veneno, deadly poison
paralysis, sleep,
confusion, curse,
hit
That's a rare item for you.
Status effects on parade!
Agora, the final blow!
Eu sou o Yuuto!
The dark knight clad in darkness, Yuu—
Your atrocious behavior...
And your swordsmanship...
Não pode ser...
Kazuya?!
Took you long enough!
Isso mesmo, "Kazuya" is my sub-account!
Yuuto, você é tão inútil.
I've got tons of other chores for you.
No logging out or leaving your
room until you finish everything.
My beloved family... I am sorry.
You're so lazy, Yuuto!
Essa voz...
Just kill her already,
and let's all go eat dinner!
Nii-chan!
We're having your favorite
tonight: Hamburg steak!
Pai!
If you don't eat it before it gets
cold, your mom will be angry.
Grandpa?!
No matter how many small fry flock to you, vocês não podem me derrotar.
Is that really true?
Sensitive-to-cold sorcerer, Tetsuya!
Gout-suffering warrior, Satoru!
Dragon knight of stiff shoulders, Masafumi!
Together, these three timely
human sacrifices perform...
O ataque final da família Shimada!
Eternal Material Force!
Esse sou... eu?
Indeed. All for the sake of family harmony.
I'm rather impressed!
Yuuto-san, por favor use us!
Derrote a #4!
So fast!
I shall regain my real life with the help of
my family's love e o poder das HackaDolls!
Th-This is the "power of love" that I despise!
Have faith that Yuuto's love can save the world...
Thanks for reading!
Please look forward
to Geso Ikuo-sensei's
next work!!