Take that!
Little devil!
Episode 5: "#4 Isn't Just for Show!"
Remaining time
Oh, dear... Look what you did to me...
What are you...?!
They never do anything useful.
Overall
Rating
Looks like they need some shoring up.
The newest model, developed using
all of our technology to date...
Go forth, HackaDoll #4!
Find #s 1 through 3 and show them how it's done!
The network is vast.
But...
The real world is seriously vast, too!
Now, then, where are they?
Wait just a sec, Granny.
Now you can cross all you like!
Wow, I advanced so far!
For real?
Wow! Advancing things is super easy!
Okay, let's keep it up
and complete my mission!
Convenience Store
Your change is 141 yen.
Did I help advance you?
Huh? Isn't it supposed to be,
"thanks for your business"?
Uh, right...
My change.
Sorry!
I advanced you, didn't I?
Frankfurters
What happened?
Why do we have so many frankfurters?
Well, you ordered them, didn't you?
Oops! I think the number I ordered
was off by a couple of digits.
You're killing me here!
What if we can't sell all these?
Why don't you eat them?
Don't you giggle at me.
Let me have that.
Found you!
Welcome to our store.
High-spec Personal Entertainment
AI, HackaDoll #4!
HackaDoll #4?
You're #4-chan, the one said to
be able to advance anything?
Exactly!
So they finished you! Amazing!
So? What're you all doing?
The manager asked us to help
advance this convenience store.
It's a part-time job!
We get paid 890 yen per hour.
It's a very at-home work environment.
But we mess up so much,
we can't seem to advance anything.
But advancing things is super easy!
Oh, well. I guess I'll have
to show you how it's done!
Component Analysis!
Wow! Amazing!
Since you love smartphone
games, you need this!
Want to gaze at the sky from Aff with me?
Wow! So many ultra-super characters!
Pizza Roll
Since you are hungry...
Delivery for you!
There! All the money you can grab!
It's Super Car!!
Road Roll— I mean, Super Car!
Amazing! She's advancing left and right!
#4 isn't just for show.
Mom! I wanna see a shooting star!
Okay, when it gets dark, we'll look for one.
No! I wanna see it now!
F-F-F-Found you!
The satellite's orbit has
mysteriously changed!
Look! It's a shooting star!
How pretty!
What is that?
It's gonna fall on Earth!
Oh, no! This is bad!
What should we do?
We must run.
Sister 0!
Oh, I was just showing them how advancing is do—
You call that advancing?!
Satellite
#4
Oh. It's back to normal.
Ow, ow, ow...
Hey! Why is my phone bill so high?
How do you expect me to
eat 100 pizzas by myself?
I'm gonna get arrested!
You'd better take responsibility!
Whoa! Wh-Wh-Why?!
Now, then...
W-Welcome to our store.