Give me power!
Fine...
More! More!
Power, give me power.
What the hell is going on?
Who are these people?
Everyone, get inside!
Who is that girl?
I'm not really sure.
We're not making any progress.
If we could get rid
of just a few of them...
What's wrong?
I don't know.
I had no idea you'd
come over this quickly.
I thought you'd get permission
from the elders first.
Shizuku!
Narifumi.
Shizuku, come back with us.
It's not too late...
If you want to take me back,
you'll have to do it by force.
Shizuku...
But if you get in my way, I'll kill you.
Why?
You'll never understand.
Earthquake!
The gate...
The gate is out of control.
What should we do?
They are still in this realm.
Then...
Find them!
Certainly!
That young woman...
What the hell is going on?
Explain so I can understand it.
Sorry, we don't really know either.
What?
All we know is what we've gathered
from the old teachings we've been told.
Teachings? What are those?
What I want to know is...
Calm down, Hosokawa!
Ma'am.
We'll tell you what we know, but
we can't do any more than that.
We are guardians of the gate.
Guardians of the gate?
You saw the gate too.
That is called the Black Gate.
It connects the world we
were in before to this world.
Our world and this world?
Yes, this is a different
world than the one we live in.
That's ridiculous.
How can that be?
It's true.
In the past, this world had people living
in it, it had a culture, and a history.
But...
They accidentally discovered
an incredible power.
...strong enough to destroy themselves.
The few remaining people chose
our world as their new home.
...and so they built the Black Gate.
The Kadomori family are descendants
of those who came over from this side.
They have been protecting
the gate this whole time.
Protecting it?
From what?
The power that destroyed this world.
This power known as "The
Power to Rule the World"...
...can also destroy the
world that we live in.
So we've sealed that power on this
side and have guarded the gate...
...so that it would not be opened.
The power to rule the world?
Yes.
It is said that if you have that
power, you can control the world.
There are no teachings on
what those powers may be...
...so we're not really sure, but...
I had no idea.
It's hard to believe, isn't it?
I'm here on this side, but it
still doesn't seem real to me.
But if you think about what's going
on, there's no choice but to believe it.
So everyone here is a
guardian of the gate?
Yes.
Kasumi Kadomori...
...Mizuki Komiyama...
...and me, Nanami Ebizuka,
you know who we are.
This is Miharu Fujisaki.
She's the student body president
so I know what she looks like but...
Koyuki Hasegawa and Fuu Katsuragi.
They are both a year ahead of you.
And Amane Izumi.
She's one year below you.
The Kadomori power has been
passed down through the women.
The seven of us plus Shizuku makes
eight, and we are the guardians.
Shizuku...
Why did she do that?
She's trying to acquire
the power to rule the world.
For a guardian of the gate to try
something like this is the greatest sin.
But she's trying to get it, nonetheless.
What happened to her?
I don't understand why, either.
Miss Nanami, this girl,
what's wrong with her?
I don't know.
What's your name?
Sora.
Kasumi.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing...
I'm sorry to drag you into this.
Don't worry about it.
Shizuku...
...she liked you.
But I was the one going out with you.
I knew how she felt.
But she was happy for me, and I
believed that everything was okay.
But it wasn't okay.
That's why Shizuku...
That's not true...
Narifumi...
...if you had enough power to do
anything you wanted with this world...
...what would you do?
Don't say that.
You're saying that Shizuku's
trying to get back at you.
There's no way that's true.
You're twins.
You grew up together.
You know her better than anyone.
She wouldn't think anything like that.
Right?
Yeah.
Here goes.
Okay.
Did it hurt?
I'm okay.
You can move it.
Narifumi! Narifumi!
Wow!
I'm going to lose my mind.
Kasumi, I'm going to come.
Yes, come, Narifumi.
Narifumi...
I'm so happy.
How can you be so complacent?
You say it like it would be easy
to find someone in this big world.
Mizuki.
I can't deal with this.
I'm going back.
Wait.
Leave me alone.
Listen, the gate isn't stable right now.
It's not safe to go through it.
Yeah, well it's your fault for
breaking your concentration before.
And that's not it, this whole thing
is you and your sister's fault.
Why do I have to be put through this?
Calm down.
Don't touch me!
W-What!
There's no reason to cry...
Miss President...
What's wrong? This isn't like you.
Then what am I like?
Um...
I've held myself back...
...to be a top student, to
meet people's expectations.
I've had enough.
I've decided to be true to myself.
It's great to be true but...
Right?
So...
These are my true feelings.
Hey!
I like you.
I don't want Kasumi or Shizuku
or anyone else to have you.
Miss President.
Don't think of anyone other than me.
So? Has anyone ever done this for you?
Well...
I can't hold it anymore...
It's okay, come.
I'm sorry, Miss President, but...
I'm sorry!
Hosokawa!
Even if I'm true to myself...
It's not worth it.
Why are you here?
Well...
Now it's time for fun.
You look good, Mizuki.
Let's begin.
We wouldn't want anyone to catch us.
He's going to enter you.
Does it hurt?
I bet it hurts.
You don't seem like
you've played around much.
Does it make you mad?
There's nothing as demoralizing
as experiencing your powerlessness.
No matter what you say, no
matter how you justify it...
...unless you have the power to put it
in to action, it doesn't mean anything.
That's right, power is everything.
Say something.
Are you enjoying this?
You are a freak.
You're enjoying it
under these conditions...
I am not enjoying it.
Stop lying.
It's embarrassing.
Become more free, be more honest.
You decided to live
that way, didn't you?
There's no place for you there.
Not the way things are now.
Don't you wish you had the power
to create a place for yourself?
Miss President.
What pretty flowers.
Yeah.
There were a lot of them over there.
Wanna go pick some with me?
No.
No!
Miss President!
What are you doing?
Narifumi!
Get back!
What are you planning to do with Sora?
I don't have any interest in her.
Shizuku.
We're taking the girl.
Goodbye, Miss Nanami.
Not again.
Everyone, to the shrine.
Wait!
Thank you.
It's okay.
Can you give me some
time alone with Hosokawa?
Um, what is it?
I was born into a family of
guardians who handed down...
...all the knowledge of the
guardianship of the gate.
I'd like to hand this
knowledge over to you.
It will help you in
your battles to come.
Knowledge?
I don't have long.
Miss Ebizuka!
What are you going to do?
My everything...
I'm counting on you, Hosokawa.
You're the only one who
can keep the girls together.
I'm counting on you.
Miss Ebizuka!