Episódio 10: "Vamos Para Uma Fonte Termal!"
This is my first time at a hot spring!
I'm so excited!
Eu também.
Mal posso esperar!
We're getting into the hot spring
as a bonus from a job I did.
You better be grateful!
Estamos indo na frente, #3-chan.
See you there!
Hey... Hold up!
O que é isso?
Well, whatever.
The water's great!
And we have it all to ourselves!
They're floating...
So warm.
Get in more quietly, please!
This is Heaven...
Nothing beats a hot spring.
Indeed.
I can die happy.
Hey, #4-chan, don't say such ominous things.
It's so good, it's criminal. Like murder.
Now, don't say that, or it might really...
Tonight, at midnight,
one of you will die.
Wh-What is this?
"Tonight, at midnight"...
"One of you"...
"Will die."
Nobody move!
This is who I am.
This letter is an unmistakable
declaration of murder.
And...
The killer is among us!
This is silly.
I'm going back to my room.
Don't move!
Anyone who takes off on their
own in the midst of this...
will die!
M-Mr. Inspector, wh-what's this white outline?
Ah, yes, as you may have guessed...
It's just for effect.
I will begin interrogations now.
Okay, Mr. Inspector! We shall assist you!
Who are you girls?
Personal Entertainment AI, HackaDolls!
You mean the ones that can
advance a person in anything?
All right. You're my assistants.
O-Okay!
Wow, I've always wanted
to do something like this!
Well? Are you ready to confess yet?
If your poor mother saw you right now...
Don't play dumb with me!
Make yourself comfortable.
Spit it out! Now!
Here. Have some katsudon.
Yum!
Onde você estava no momento of the declaration?
I took a bath, then I drank some milk.
Leite? Isso é suspeito.
Chief. #4 has caused a lot
of trouble in the past, too.
So she has a record... Even more suspicious.
Wait, no, no, no! Não fui eu!
Come on, guys, you were all with me!
We were in the same bath!
Ah! Ela tem razão!
Então ela tem um alibi.
Todos têm um alibi...
Ou seja...
That means?
It's an unsolvable crime!
It is not!
It's almost time for the murder.
É o que parece.
Damn it! The killer won't strike while I'm alive!
Chief!
Hear me, killer! I see through your evil scheme!
Eu já vi esta faca em algum lugar antes.
Eu sei quem é o assassino!
Shut up, kid!
Quit trying to play detective.
Keep it down a bit, okay?
Fine. Vocês não me deixam escolha...
Shazam!
Tap, tap, tap, tap, and go!
Oh?
Ow!
I blew it!
#1-chan? Owner-san? Are you okay?
Whoa... Oh, all right.
Eu...
sei quem é o assassino.
O quê?!
The letter was pinned in place with a knife.
Which means...
The killer is someone with a knife.
So who is the killer, then?
O assassino é...
The one who hid a knife in the changing room.
In other words, me!
Wh-What?!
Look at what I found in #4-chan's bag!
#4-chan, I'm so disappointed!
At 11:58 pm...
Suspect apprehended!
It's over! Let's take another bath.
Oh, dear. When did I fall asleep?
And where is that knife I asked
#4-chan to get for me?
Faca?
Yes, the blade got nicked enquanto eu estava preparando o jantar,
então eu mandei a #4 pegar outra pra mim.
Wait, so that knife was...
Huh? O que está acontecendo?
#4, você tem o direito de permancer em silêncio.
O quê?!
Apparently, o verdadeiro culpado foi pego algum tempo depois,
from the fingerprints on the letter.
I'm really sorry.