Huh?
Huh? It's gone!
It's gone! It's gone! It's gone! It's gone!
Gone, gone, gone! My thing is gone!
Oh, #3-chan!
Oh, #1, this is terrible!
My arms turned into drills!
#3-chan!
#2... Wait, what?!
Are you okay?
I'm not okay!
Indeed. This is an emergency!
The HackaDoll system is full of bugs.
Thanks to this idiot!
Sorry, guys!
We must restore the system!
Damn it! A call at a time like this?
#3, since you're still okay,
go handle it by yourself.
Huh? But I'm not okay.
What's wrong? You look normal to me.
Mumble, mumble, mumble...
What?
What? What? What?
Your thing?!
There's nothing there!
What thing?!
Am I going to stay a girl forever?
It's definitely a thing of the past now!
Anyway! We must hold out
until the system is restored!
Now, go!
Episode 6: "A Thing of the Past"
Young master, I've brought you some new toys.
There we go.
Who're you?
Let's see, synchronizing to you,
uh... I'm HackaDoll #3.
Um, I came here to advance you... I guess.
Advance...
Um, I came here to help you
do whatever it is you want to do.
So you'll do anything I ask?
Yeah... Probably.
Then play with me!
Huh? That's all you want?
Oh, then I'm totally cool with that.
Butler, put her in normal clothes.
Right away.
Right away!
Now I'm totally a girl...
You look... pretty.
Shut up! I said you look pretty!
I think a flag just went up.
Shut up!
Oh, it looks like we'll be back to
normal by the end of the day.
So until then, be a convincing girl.
So, what're we going to do?
Anything! Anything that's fun!
Take that!
Remaining until recovery: 5%
Sushi
Honey, I'm home!
Welcome home.
Dinner isn't ready. Your bath
isn't ready. Nothing's ready.
What? What've you been doing all day?
Sleeping.
Um, I'm sorry, darling.
What a hopeless wife you are.
That's right. I'm a hopeless wife.
Today you're playing with
Mom and Dad all day!
#3, everything's restored here.
You should return to normal soon.
I guess I'll get going, then.
Young master, HackaDoll-san
needs to go home now.
No!
No arguing.
Don't go!
But I think I played enough.
But I'll be alone again!
Alone?
Mom and Dad are always gone,
and I don't have any friends at school.
Do you get lonely?
Of course I'm not lonely!
Hey, stay here longer.
But...
Isn't it fun playing with me?
It is fun, but...
Then live with me forever!
I know! You should marry me!
Huh?
I'll buy you anything you want!
So let's live together forever!
Young master...
Shut up!
Let's go!
We're eloping right now!
Young master!
Wait... Wait a minute.
I... I'm not...
Huh? What's wrong?
Your body is glowing.
I don't think I can stay with you.
Wh-Why not?
Because, well...
Do you hate me?
It's not that...
What, then?
You're gonna leave me all alone, too?
Huh? I'm back to normal.
You're...
Uh... Um...
Look, I'm... actually a...
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Hold on to it until we meet again!
Huh?
Okay.
You better not lose it.
Okay. I won't.
See you later.
Yeah.
It's a promise!