A Totally Live Request
Hi! Thanks for your call!
HackaDolls here!
What? Your son is playing games
Yoshie         Masafumi
(Masako)                 Satoru
You
Tetsuya                  (Yuuto)                .
A hikikomori gamer.
Won't leave room.
[I want to eat least eat dinner as a family.]
in his room and won't come out?
Never fear! At times like this...
You can count on HackaDolls!
You who have inherited the
soul of the sealed dragon,
it is time to save the world!
Sword Quest Online: Royale!
Episode 9: "Nothing Can Stop Me But Routine Tuesday Maintenance"
S-So this is SQO...
The latest games are amazing!
DeNA games are the best in the world!
So it's great that we're here, but...
How shall we search for him?
Let's go to town and ask around!
Excuse me...
Wahoo!! Wanna meet up IRL?
Woo-hoo!! You guys are cute! Wanna meet up IRL?
Uh...
Oh, there are also people over there.
Um...
Excuse me...
Um... Can I
fap to you?
Er, um...
Hmm...
Been a while, has it?
Poor guy...
Hmm...
Been a while, has it?
Poor guy...
Okay.
Score!!
I guess he's busy...
Excuse me!
We're looking for someone
named Shimada Yuuto-san.
Yuuto?
Oh, I just saw him in the back alley.
Th-Thank you.
You've got some pretty nice bewbs.
Bye.
Everyone here is so strange...
Are you Yuuto-san?
My name is Yuuto.
The dark knight clad in darkness, Yuuto!
Yeah, Shimada Yuuto-san, right?
He looks different from his picture.
The discrepancy with my real appearance
is of no importance.
Yuuto-san, please come out of your room.
Your mother is worried about you.
That I cannot do.
I am fated to spend my days in
combat to protect the world of SQO.
I cannot flee from the battle.
A gaming otaku, huh?
Nothing can stop me but
routine Tuesday maintenance!
Wh-What happened?
Pardon me. Bathroom.
Oh! So you can leave your room.
I'm going to use this item. Excuse me!
He uses a bottle?
Yuuto-san, let's have a proper talk now, okay?
Oh? You're a girl?
My avatar is. Pretty moe, right?
The truth is...
I am currently in Kazuya's evil
clutches and cannot quit SQO.
Kazuya-san?
The strongest player in SQO.
He's the head of my guild.
Until I can defeat the dark dragon
in the dungeon and obtain
the rare Crimson Drop that he desires,
Don't log out without my permission.
New Year's? That means
fewer rivals. Let's go hunting.
Real world?                   This ain't child's play.
Sever your ties.
To be frank, if I give the word, I can get over
half the players in this server on my side.
Real life plans... No one has those.
Give me your email and cell number so I can slap you awake.
I quit high school.
That's how hardcore
you should be.
Stick to it until the traitors retreat.
I haven't logged out
once since launch.
Install this on your work PC.
We're putting our lives on the line here.
I'm going to talk to a GM I know about the problems.
I am unable to log out.
Kazuya calling
Accept
Reject
It's Kazuya-san!
'Sup?
Yes, yes...
Um, my mom is kinda mad,
so may I log out for a moment?
Ah... Of course! No, I'm not messing with you.
SQO may be a game, but it's not child's play.
Huh? Within the day? Right...
Okay. Bye...
It would seem my powers
alone are insufficient.
If only someone would
volunteer to join my fight,
I'd quit being a hikikomori
and go to the temp agency!
We'll help you!
We'll help you get your
real life back, Yuuto-san!
Thank you... I am grateful
for your friendship.
But will you be okay with that equipment?
Uh... No, we won't.
Please accept this token of my friendship!
Let us go forth! To the dark dragon's dungeon!
Wooser Plains
Go! Go!
Keep going!
Wooser Plains
Anyone running away is an enemy!
Anyone not running away
is a well-trained enemy!
Wooser Plains
Dark Dragon's Dungeon
All right! The dark dragon should be in here.
Everyone, charge!
Dark Dragon's Dungeon
Wait, just us?
Charge!
Dark Dragon's Dungeon
I got the coveted Crimson Drop!
#4-chan?
Why?
I got the treasure before you!
That doesn't matter. Just give it back!
Yuuto-san can't return to
the real world without it!
If you want it, then take it by force!
If that's how it is...
We'll just have to fight you!
Nope! Not even close!
I see an opening!
Do it now, #1-chan!
Not even close!
Poison, deadly poison
paralysis, sleep,
confusion, curse,
hit
That's a rare item for you.
Status effects on parade!
Now, the final blow!
I am Yuuto!
The dark knight clad in darkness, Yuu—
Your atrocious behavior...
And your swordsmanship...
Are you...
Kazuya?!
Took you long enough!
That's right, "Kazuya" is my sub-account!
Yuuto, you're so useless.
I've got tons of other chores for you.
No logging out or leaving your
room until you finish everything.
My beloved family... I am sorry.
You're so lazy, Yuuto!
That voice...
Just kill her already,
and let's all go eat dinner!
Nii-chan!
We're having your favorite
tonight: Hamburg steak!
Dad!
If you don't eat it before it gets
cold, your mom will be angry.
Grandpa?!
No matter how many small fry
flock to you, you can't beat me.
Is that really true?
Sensitive-to-cold sorcerer, Tetsuya!
Gout-suffering warrior, Satoru!
Dragon knight of stiff shoulders, Masafumi!
Together, these three timely
human sacrifices perform...
The Shimada family's final attack!
Eternal Material Force!
Is this... me?
Indeed. All for the sake of family harmony.
I'm rather impressed!
Yuuto-san, please use us!
Defeat #4!
So fast!
I shall regain my real life with the help of
my family's love and the HackaDolls' power!
Th-This is the "power of love" that I despise!
Have faith that Yuuto's love can save the world...
Thanks for reading!
Please look forward
to Geso Ikuo-sensei's
next work!!