Queen's Blade:
A quadrennial competition that determines the queen who rules the continent.
The newest queen abolished the royalty and brought equality to the masses.
Cities thrived, civilization improved, and people gained wealth and knowledge.
However, this was the beginning of a very chaotic, anarchical world.
A Saint's Agony ~ The Door of Faith Reopens ~
This is the story of beautiful crusaders who fight for their beliefs.
This shit is great!
Goes down like water!
Hey, more beer and beef! Make it quick!
Dear Lord, I give thanks for tonight's generous bounty.
But God's a lazy-ass who can't be trusted, right?
Yeah, yeah. Like, no matter how much we pray, like, we're so normal.
If it would make me strong right now, maybe I should just pray to Satan.
Silence!
Huh?
I will not tolerate any blasphemy against God!
You wanna start something?!
We were enjoying our drinks 'til you came by.
Take responsibility, you bitch!
Stop this at once!
If you continue your trespasses against God, I shall condemn you as heretics!
You could burn at the stake for this.
Did you hear that? She's imitating the Inquisitor!
Hilarious. She's just another powerless nun.
I won't forgive you now. You shall see.
Sacred pose–
No... wait... what's going on?
What is she doing?
You mocking us?!
You guys are way too loud.
Let me eat my dinner in peace!
Sh-She was in the last Queen's Blade...
That's Steel Princess Ymir, without a doubt!
I heard she's amazing.
I've never seen her before.
They're so small.
Yeah, she's flat as a board.
Who's that running their mouth?!
St-Steel Princess Ymir?
Wh-Why is she here?
You! You said you want to be stronger?
Then your best bet is to buy one of my prized weapons.
What do you think? Aren't they beautiful?
For a limited time only, it's buy one, get one free!
We-We're sorry!
Please pardon me!
W-Wait! Buy the weapons! Now!
Wait, your check!
Put it on our tab!
Thank you very much for that.
I'm Shigi from the 16th monastery.
Our meeting here must be God's will.
You're such a reckless nun. To think you'd mess with those drunkards...
Punishing anyone who commits blasphemy against God is only natural.
Are you a fundamentalist? By the way, weren't you trying to use the sacred power?
Indeed.
But I mess up every time I rush it.
Even though I finally received God's power...
I'm ashamed of myself.
Those people should all burn at the stake.
You're overreacting.
No, a seed of heresy should be crushed while it is still small.
It would be bad for the believers if left alone.
Well, that's that. So... wanna buy some weapons?
If you had my weapons, you'd be looked upon favorably during your propagations!
He has proclaimed...
Huh?
There shall be love and happiness for all believers.
But for the followers of Satan, there shall be only merciful, cleansing fire.
Believe! Pray!
Faith shall save all.
Well, it looks like I've become involved with a real nutjob...
His power is eternal.
He is absolute.
Oh, God. God, please bless us!
What nice weather. If this keeps up, maybe I can get there today.
Oh, good morning.
So you're also headed to Gainos?
Yes, the Central Holy Dynasty has commanded me to worship in the Grand Cathedral.
How about you, Ymir?
A business venture! I was thinking of selling these weapons to Claudette.
That's wonderful!
Queen Claudette is a great ruler...
who generously protects the church and strengthens the power of the Holy Dynasty.
So these weapons will soon be used to spill the blood of heretics?
Well... Maybe, maybe not...
Thank you very much, Ymir! Let's exterminate the heretics together!
What's that?
What is going on?
A child was suddenly struck by illness. It looks bad.
Hold it together, Comse! Comse!
We sent for the town doctor, but I wonder if he'll make it in time.
Let's go. We can't do anything here.
Let us borrow His power.
What?
What are you going to do?
Please do not worry. He will be well shortly.
Sacred pose: Healing.
God... please... save... this... child...
Wow!
Mother?
Comse!
Thank goodness.
Thank you, Sister.
God be praised. His miracles are great.
Maybe what's great here isn't God, but...
your ass.
That "sacred pose"... You said last night that it doesn't work well,
but this time it worked just fine.
Yes, it is fine if I do not hurry, but I tend to fail at it when I do.
Yeah, if someone draws a sword in front of you, that's understandable.
To punish the heretics requires strength of mind as well as strength of body.
That is why I learned martial arts.
Wow! That's pretty smart.
It's getting late. I thought we could get to Gainos by tonight.
We decided to walk all night, but the road at night is kinda creepy.
Do not fear, Ymir. God is with us.
God might be with us, but snakes could be with us, too.
You sure seem happy, though.
Of course! With this, I can burn any heretics at the stake.
What's that noise?
I hear that there are bandits around here. Perhaps a traveler is being robbed.
Bandits?
To think that they would rob a genuine believer...
This is unforgivable.
Let's go, Ymir.
No way.
I don't wanna get involved in a skirmish.
Now that I think about it, if that traveler had my weapons,
he could have easily defeated the bandits.
Hey, wait! Don't take the fire with you!
S-Snakes might come!
Please forgive me. I have no money.
Well then, just leave your body.
I might just have to split you in half.
Stop this at once!
Who the hell are you?!
A servant of God.
What you are doing, ganging up on an innocent old man...
It is unforgivable!
Whew, I finally caught up.
Well, one, two, three... Wow, there's so many.
Hey, guys! I have some exciting news!
I'm sure that even bandits like you
have heard about the Steel Princess's rare weapons, right?
In that case...
Let's kill her first!
Those dumbasses.
I haven't even got to the meat of the story.
Well then, I'll just have to show them the power of my weapons.
Ymir, I will fight, too. I must punish these insolent men.
All right. Let's go!
Don't get ahead of yourself!
Use this!
What?!
You guys are new to this.
Shut up!
Hold on there. You can't fight with those, can you?
Don't you wanna buy these?
How the hell...
Time for your punishment!
The sword... I want the sword.
This is for the ax.
Give me a shield, too!
Let's do this like gentlemen. Line up, everyone!
Thanks!
Wait, let me have the sword instead!
Oh, all right.
Don't forget my shield.
Yes, sir.
Such wealthy bandits.
I haven't made a profit like this in a long time.
It was a good idea to give her that.
This sword is different.
Oh yeah, I like that face.
This will FINISH you!
Do not underestimate God's power.
His protection...
That looks painful!
I'm out!
I'm next.
No, let me!
B-Boss!
Please forgive me, Boss!
Why are you guys having such a hard time against a lone nun?
How pathetic.
You're the leader of these ruffians?
That's right.
Pray. Beg for forgiveness.
Even though you became a bandit,
if you change your ways and promise to follow God, He shall forgive you.
Don't underestimate me.
The only people that benefit from a god are people like you.
God is absolute. If you do not obey, you will be regarded as a heretic.
A heretic? Whatever.
Now that I think about it, I actually feel closer to Satan than God.
Such heretical words...
You shall know your place. Sacred pose:
Re... morse.
No, not like this...
What are you doing?
Close my eyes...
Sacred pose: Remorse!
It's not working...
Cut it out.
I was thinking of sparing your life if you stripped yourself naked,
but I don't feel like it anymore.
God will never desert a believer.
We'll see if you still feel that way after this.
How are you going to fight against this many men?
Pray if you want.
But you will die all the same.
Well, well. This is excellent.
Who are you?
So this is the true strength of the bandits' leader.
But I don't know about that sword.
This?
I'll give you the best of the best:
The sword that the champion of the last Queen's Blade,
Leina, also used: the Ewindel Sword!
Wow! The wandering warrior's sword? Amazing!
If you wanna deliver the final blow, you should at least use a sword of this caliber.
Well, it's sorta expensive...
I don't care about the price. I'll buy it!
It's a deal!
I bought you some time.
The rest is up to you. Brace yourself.
Have you finished your final prayer?
God is absolute. Believers always achieve victory.
Then pray and die where you stand!
Believe in God.
Entrust Him with everything.
Sacred pose: Worship.
Thank you! Thank you, Lord!
Did you think I'd change...
from something like this?!
It's all right.
I lost...
Phew, we've finally arrived.
So this is Gainos.
You were pretty harsh back there.
I thought you had forgiven them...
But you still burned them all.
Well, they were heretics.
Burning heretics is His love; His way of purifying them.
Is that so?
Well, I guess this is goodbye.
It was a pretty fun journey.
Same here. Thank you for your support.
All right, I'm off!
I almost forgot!
Payment for that weapon I gave you.
You're... charging me for that?
Obviously. I'm Steel Princess Ymir, don't ya know?
You seem to be prepared, Shigi.
Of course.
Then, in the name of God and the Central Holy Dynasty,
I hereby designate you as the Inquisitor.
I accept.
As the Inquisitor, I proclaim:
All heretics and sinners shall be burned at the stake.
Sacred pose:
Fear!
Who will the goddess of victory favor?
Whose beliefs will prevail?
Only battles will determine the winner.