Queen's Blade.
This was a tournament held once every four years to decide
the queen who would rule over the continent.
The new queen abolished the nobility and brought equality to the commoners.
Cities flourished, and civilization progressed.
The people enjoyed their newfound prosperity under the new regime.
However, this also marked the beginning of a ruthless rule under an iron fist.
Queen's Blade
A sister's agony – The door of faith opens once more
And thus begins the prelude to the battle
between the beautiful warriors who fight for their beliefs.
This really hits the spot!
You're holding your liquor well.
Hey, bring more ale and meat!
Dear Lord, thank you for the food tonight.
Seriously, God is so lame! He never does anything!
Yup.
We even tried that praying crap.
But nothing happened!
You know what? Worshipping Satan might not be a bad idea,
especially if it makes me stronger!
Enough!
I won't tolerate such blasphemy!
You trying to pick a fight?
Can't you see that we're enjoying our drinks?
How are you gonna make it up to us?!
Cease this immediately.
Otherwise, I'll have to brand you as heretics.
You'll be judged guilty,
and burned at the stake!
Get a load of that.
She thinks she's an inquisitor or something.
What a joke.
She's obviously still in training!
That does it! You're going to regret that!
Divine Pose!
Wait, what's going on?
What the hell is she doing?
Now I'm mad!
You're making a racket.
Let me eat my dinner in peace!
Hey! She was in the last Queen's Blade tournament...
The Steel Princess Ymir!
I'm sure of it!
I heard she's really strong.
This is the first time I've seen her in person.
She's so small too.
Completely flat.
All right, who said that?!
The Steel Princess Ymir!
What's she doing here?
Did somebody say she wants to become stronger?
In that case, the fastest way is to buy my fine weapons from Steel Mountain!
What do you think?
Quite the beauties, aren't they?
If you buy one now, you'll get another one for free!
Please excuse me!
Sorry!
Hey, wait! Buy my weapons!
Hey, the bill!
Put it on my tab!
Thank you for saving me.
I am Siggy of the 19th Holy Order.
Our meeting must be part of God's plan.
You're certainly one rash sister.
It's not wise to start trouble with that unruly lot.
It is my duty to admonish those who speak ill of God.
Are you a fundamentalist?
That reminds me. You were going to use holy powers, weren't you?
Yes,
but that always happens when I panic.
I couldn't do anything even with God's help.
I wish they would all die in a fire.
That's a bit too much.
No, the seeds of heresy should not be allowed to take root.
To overlook them is to betray those who have placed their trust in God.
Well, anyway...
How about some weapons?
Owning a weapon from Steel Mountain might give you an edge in your missionary work-
God hath decreed,
"Those who believe in me shall be blessed with love and happiness."
"Those who worship demons shall be granted mercy and purified with fire."
"Pray to me. Believe in me."
"Faith is the only way to salvation."
Sheesh, it looks like I've run into a nutcase.
The power of God is for eternity!
God is absolute!
Oh, dear Lord!
Please shower me with your hot, passionate blessings!
The clouds have cleared.
At this rate, I'll make it to Gainos by the end of the day.
Good morning.
Are you also headed for Gainos?
That's right.
I've received orders from the Holy See to pray at the cathedral.
What about you?
Business!
I'm planning to sell these weapons from Steel Mountain to Claudette.
That's splendid!
Queen Claudette is an esteemed figure who favors the church
and has given greater authority to the church.
These weapons shall someday be used
to hack those demon worshippers into bloody chunks!
Well, perhaps. It really depends-
Ymir, thank you.
Let's destroy the heretics together!
What's that?
What happened?
This child is sick.
It looks pretty serious.
Hold yourself together!
Coms! Coms!
Someone has gone to the village to look for a doctor.
But he might not make it in time.
Let's keep going.
There's nothing we can do.
Let us borrow the power of God.
What?
Hey, what are you...
There's no need to worry.
He'll be right as rain soon.
Holy Pose.
Healing.
Lord...
Please save this boy!
Mother?
Coms!
Thank goodness.
Thank you so much,
Sister!
Thank goodness. God's power is wonderful.
No, God's power is nothing compared to your...
...butt.
You said you couldn't use your holy power last night,
but you managed to do it this time.
Yes, because I kept my calm.
But if I get flustered, I...
Well, it's hard not to panic with a sword pointed at you.
Power is needed as well to punish the heretics.
In order to do so, I've learned some martial arts...
Wow, that's quite impressive!
It's getting late.
I'd thought we'd be able to reach Gainos before the day ended.
It's good to aim to reach there before dark,
but mountain paths are creepy at night.
Don't feel dispirited.
God is always with us!
Even if God is with us, snakes will still appear.
You seem to be enjoying yourself.
Yes!
With this torch, I can set afire any heretics that may cross our path!
Help!
What could that be?
I heard that mountain bandits appear around here.
Some traveler probably got attacked.
Mountain bandits?
Attacking a righteous follower of God is unforgivable!
Let's go, Ymir!
Nope. I don't want to get involved.
Honestly, if those travelers had Steel Mountain weapons with them,
they wouldn't need to be afraid of bandits.
Hey, stop!
Don't take the torch with you!
The snakes will come!
Please, spare me!
I don't have any money!
Then leave your possessions and get lost!
Or should I cut you in half?
Cease this at once!
Who the hell are you?!
A servant of God.
It's unbecoming to gang up on a frail old man.
You shall be punished!
I finally caught up!
One, two, three...
Wow, there are so many of them!
Great!
You lot! I have some good news for you!
Even bandits such as you
should have heard of the fine weapons from Steel Mountain, right?
I'm going to-
Start with her!
How foolish. I haven't even gotten to the good part yet.
There's only one thing left to do.
I'll let them have a taste of my Steel Mountain weapons!
Ymir, I shall fight as well.
I have to teach the insolent fools a lesson.
As you wish.
Go!
You shut your whore mouth!
Use this!
What?!
This is your first time, isn't it?
You can't fight without a weapon.
So, wanna buy some?
No way!
Here's your punishment.
Here! Give me a sword!
I want an axe!
Give me a shield as well!
Don't rush!
Line up!
All right!
Forget that! Give me a sword!
Okay!
Don't forget my shield!
These bandits are rich!
I haven't made such a killing in a while!
I did the right thing giving her that weapon.
This sword isn't like the last one.
That's a nice expression you have.
This is it!
Don't belittle God's power!
May the Lord be with you.
I can't take this anymore!
Me too!
I'll fight you next!
No, I'll go first!
Boss!
Forgive me, boss!
Having trouble with one sister?
You're pathetic.
You're their leader, are you not?
Something like that.
Pray to God.
Beg for his forgiveness.
God will forgive even a brigand such as you,
as long as you vow to turn over a new leaf and serve God.
I wish you wouldn't look down on me.
Unlike you people of the church,
we can't put food on the table with faith alone.
God is absolute!
If you do not submit, I'll take you as heretics!
Heretics?
Fine.
Besides, all of us feel more at home with Satan than God.
Wicked heretics, just you wait.
Holy Pose.
Remorse...
Wait, that's not right.
What are you doing?
Close your eyes.
Holy Pose!
Remorse!
It's not working!
Enough.
I'd planned to spare your life if you'd just give up your belongings.
But I'm no longer in the mood for that.
God does not abandon his believers!
Oh? Perhaps this will change your mind.
How do you plan to fight so many at once?
Go on, pray to your god.
Either way, you're dead. I hope you're ready.
Wow, you're great!
Who are you?
I'd expect nothing less of the woman who rules over the bandits.
But that sword won't do.
This?
You'd do well to buy one of the finest weapons of Steel Mountain!
Especially the one used by Reina, the winner of the previous Queen's Blade tournament!
Behold, the Evindil Sword!
What? The sword of the Wandering Warrior Leina?!
This is good stuff!
When dealing the final blow,
you have to use a sword like this,
or else you won't look cool!
Well, it's going to cost you.
I don't care about the price.
Just sell it to me!
Deal!
I've helped you to stall for time.
The rest depends on you.
Are you prepared?
Have you said your last prayers?
God is absolute.
Those who believe in God
cannot possibly be defeated.
Very well. Then die as you pray!
Stay calm.
Have faith in God.
Place your trust in him.
Holy Pose.
Worship.
Thank you!
Thank you, God!
I won't fall like this.
I won't let you touch me!
It's all right.
I've lost.
We finally made it!
So this is Gainos!
You know, you really lack mercy.
I thought you were going to forgive them.
In the end, you torched all of them.
Well, they were heretics.
Purifying them with fire is another display of God's affection.
Is that so?
Well then, time to part ways.
It was fun traveling with you.
I thank you for your help.
All right! Stay well!
I almost forgot!
The money for the weapon I gave you!
You want money for it?
Of course!
I'm the Steel Princess Ymir!
You seem to have made up your mind, Siggy.
Yes.
In that case...
By the name of our Lord and the Holy See,
I hereby decree you an inquisitor!
As you command.
I order you as an inquisitor.
Burn every heretic, pagan, and disobedient follower!
Holy Pose!
Will!
Who will the Goddess of Victory cast her smile upon?
Who will blaze a path to achieve her heart's desires?
Until they cross swords, only God knows.