Let me tell you about my abilities.
Apollo!
In addition to possessing an Accelerator,
the veil of heat surrounding
my body is 3,000 degrees.
I can emit a heat blast
of 6,000 degrees from my palms...
and an 8,000 degree laser
from my fingertip.
Now it's your turn.
You can't only have an Accelerator.
What other powers do you have?
009...
What other powers do I have...?
Nothing but courage!
Akira! Akira!
Sachiko! You're alive?
Sachiko!
I died. I'm dead.
When you gain powers beyond a human's,
you either become a god or a demon.
And me, I'm going to become a god.
One befitting of this body!
You're wrong!
See? I knew you would go against me.
That's why we have no choice but to fight.
009... Apollo...
I died.
I can't go back and live with
Mommy or Daddy again.
Sachiko...
It hurts...
The accursed voices of the damned...
Voices from hell!
Jinmen?
How do you like my shell? That's right...
Take a good look!
You can see the sorrow I've eaten
and the malice I've devoured
displayed right on my shell!
Akira!
I've never hated you demons
more than I do now!
You'll pay for this, Jinmen!
How long do we have to keep up this fight?
There is an end to it.
We need simply continue until
there is a victor and he becomes a god.
Humanity has always needed gods.
The world cannot escape
from its history of war.
Black Ghost is proof of that.
If you're neither human
nor aiming to become a god,
then you're merely trash!
Too slow!
Isn't the smell of burning meat
just wonderful?
I'll add your face to my collection.
You can't even do a thing to stop me.
It's not that I can't.
I'm just choosing not to.
If I don't experience
even a thousandth of her pain,
I won't be able to forgive myself!
These people are no different
than the living.
They're still conscious of everything.
Bastard...
Whatever's wrong?
Don't want to fight?
If I have to fight...
then I'll...
I'll become a monster to put an end
to fighting once and for all.
Then I'll send you to hell!
Helen!
Helen, let me go. Helen, you're on fire...
Apollo, even if we survive,
people will still fight.
But 009 might one day...
Helen...
What are you saying?
We'll become gods and change this world...
Apollo, you should already understand...
Helen...
Helen!
Take this, Devilman!
Akira, you have to kill him.
I'm dead. I'm already dead!
No! Stop, don't do it!
If you remove my shell, they'll all die.
Is that what you want?
But you'll die too.
Everything looks to be fine.
Hey, come get some exercise with me.
Let's go.
I've got another one almost ready to go.
Yeah, it smells good in here.
These all look great.
I'll carry them out.
I'll help.
Even if Black Ghost starts something,
they won't be stupid enough
to get it picked up by the news.
Keep it down. Can't you just
quietly read the newspaper?
Newspapers only publish articles
to help those in power.
Are you communing with spirits?
It's time to eat.
Okay.
What's wrong?
The spirits of the wind
and earth are trying to warn me.
Well, that's a little alarming.
Ivan?
Hm? He shouldn't be up yet.
Warning, warning!
Demons are coming!
Demons?
I'll take that!
Thief!
A purse snatcher? Let's go get him, Akira.
Come on, Miki. Just leave it be.
Take this!
What the hell?
You want some of this?
Give back what you stole!
Just because you're a girl, don't think...
Oh, you've made a big mistake.
Oh, boy.
Hey, you're actually pretty hot.
I'll show you a good time.
Yeah.
Up we go.
Oh, no, I'm losing my grip.
Whoa, stop, you idiot!
Whoops.
Sorry, I couldn't hang on to it!
Screw you! We'll get you for this!
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Take care.
Sheesh. Why do you keep sticking
your neck out like that?
Nothing's really popped up yet.
In any case,
Ivan woke up from
his 15-day slumber to warn us.
It's unlikely to be a normal threat.
Yeah, the spirits warned us, too.
Right.
Albert and his team
are investigating, too.
We should gather
as much information as we can.
Agreed.
I'm Eva Maria Parallels.
Whoa, she's beautiful.
So cute.
My life just got so much better.
Your seat is next to Ms. Makimura.
Over here!
I'm Miki Makimura. Nice to meet you.
Got your textbooks yet?
Yes, thank you.
Not that one. Your seat is by the window.
Oh, okay.
That one's the idiot's desk.
His name is Akira.
Don't worry about him.
He always skips class.
That idiot.
He's planning on
skipping class again today!
Sorry, I didn't mean to weird you out.
I did it again.
"Demons" is the only thing
we have to go on...
If they try to make their move in Japan,
there will be movement in their
multinational corporation's front office.
If they plan on inciting another incident,
they'll probably target somewhere
with crowds.
Françoise and I have narrowed it down
to a few locations.
Start with those.
Yes, sir.
Black Ghost, where are you hiding?
From an economic standpoint,
it's definitely a demon's tower.
SHIBUYA CENTER
Pretty awesome, right?
Hey, I did pretty good too.
I looked it up and everything.
Like Gilles de Rais' Bluebeard legend
or the legend of Vlad the Impaler.
Yeah, all the urban legends forums
are lighting up right now.
People saying they saw demons
or beast men.
Would you mind telling me
a bit more about that?
Hey, man, how you been doing?
If you hear any hot tips
about shady foreign investors or anything,
do me a solid and let me know!
That's about all we have at present.
It might be fake.
Pretty much the same here.
Copy that. Keep up the good work.
Great?
Yes, do not fret, my young friend.
The kind Pyunma will surely
lend a helping hand.
I won't be going.
Urban legends of demons, is it?
Françoise, let's check that
with the other information.
Okay.
I've cross-referenced the information
provided with the web search history.
The key is the use of the term "demon."
It's concentrated in this area.
I'll access the police database
and overlay it with reports
on demon-like monster sightings.
That many?
That's not all.
It's as if the number
of sightings correlates
with the increase in number
of people missing.
Françoise.
Can we look at the security footage
around this region?
Yes.
There sure are a lot of them.
I'll start with the areas and times
mentioned in the witness reports.
There.
-One more time.
-Okay.
Stop!
Zoom in.
Okay.
That's a demon.
This is the real deal.
First Olympian gods, now demons.
This area is located in close proximity
to some dense woodlands.
Black Ghost might be experimenting
with a new type of cyborg.
I'll look into it.
I'll go too.
I should be able to track it.
Okay!
The demon is hiding out in the woods
while spreading his influence.
Which means that this forest
will be our hunting ground.
Hunting grounds, huh?
That's him. That's Akira.
Who's that with you?
This is Eva. She's a new student
who just transferred to our class.
So be nice to her, Akira.
I'm Eva. Nice to meet you.
What do you say?
Okay, fine.
Oh, I'm spending the night
at Ryo's place, so I don't need dinner.
Again?
He always seems so cold.
I don't know how to deal with him.
Wh-- What?
How suspicious...
What are you talking about?
I'm just kidding.
Ouch, that hurts, Miki.
I won't make you lunch
if you skip class again.
Aw, come on.
Ow, ow! Stop!
Joe and Françoise are tracking down
a new lead?
Apparently.
What about Great?
-I left him behind.
-Whoo!
The devil's drink, so tempting and smooth.
You were tailed, too?
Three versus three...
Well, it's time to face our demons.
The sun is setting.
It's time for the hunt to begin.
Found you.
Just perfect...
Your banquet shall be for our Sabbat.
Your bodies shall be sacrificed to us.
It's a monster!
Joe!
Françoise?
Screams... I hear a crowd screaming.
Let's go.
Pazuzu, he's coming.
It may not be as much as Atun's, but
I still have history of my own with him.
I'm thankful to you for this opportunity.
Everyone else
head to Lord Atun's location.
Amon, you've come.
I'm not Amon.
I'm Devilman, and I hunt demons like you!
Demons? Devilman?
Is this the demon Ivan mentioned?
Follow me!
Let's end this game of hide and seek.
You followed us for a reason, didn't you?
Let me guess.
You're assassins sent by Black Ghost.
They never give up, do they?
You have guts.
I must credit you for destroying
the Mythos Cyborgs.
There you are!
009.
I'm reading three signals.
Two seem to be enhanced warriors,
but neither match our database.
The third one is human.
Perhaps it's a Black Ghost scientist.
He could be here to record
the combat data from their battle.
Got it.
They look exactly like
what you'd imagine a demon to be!
What's wrong? You besmirch the name
of Amon, demonkind's greatest hero?
You're still on about that?
I'm not Amon! I'm Devilman!
Akira!
He's not hurt?
Black Ghost scum!
Crap...
I see, he's a demon
that's fused with machine.
It's not as if we hadn't considered
that possibility.
What are you planning?
Demon...
Activate Accelerator!
How did he match my speed?
Is it by pure instinct?
I've got you now.
My super gun...
009 is in combat...!
Dammit. My limiter...
What this? Your punch's
grown pathetic all of a sudden.
What are you planning, Black Ghost?
Huh? He's not a demon?
Well, even if he's not a demon,
with that amount power
he will eventually become an equal threat.
We're simply taking him out
while we can as a precaution.
009!
Akira!
Joe...
Joe!