Kamikui
Kamikui.
They're monsters that broke Goddess Amaterasu's seal and plunged down to Earth to bring about chaos.
They are enemies of all that is living!
chimimouryou abare moyou
Monsters are going on a rampage!
Let's get going!
kono machi ni hime ga kuru
The princess is coming to town!
tachisugata amakumite
Don't sell her short,
Ibaraki-douji
koukaija girigiri out
or you'll regret it.
Yoshitsune
kiryuu kiryuu mau wa hanafubuki
Cherry blossoms rain down upon her as the wind blows.
doo-bee-doo masani iryu-jonisuto illusionist
Doo-bee-doo, she's a born illusionist!
Shizuka Gozen
you kiryuu hime wa rankiryuu
If you're a breeze, then she's the storm!
Kaguya
goikkou-sama goshuushousama
I feel sorry for you, my dear Goikkou.
Amaterasu
Sakura
Zin
This is the story of the Kamikui,
and the brave girls who fight them!
Shizuka Gozen
Born April 8th, Blood Type O
150 cm, B85, W56, H83
Naive and Innocent
Main Technique:
Heavenly Arrow Death Penalty
Shizuka Gozen
Born April 8th, Blood Type O
150 cm, B85, W56, H83
Naive and Innocent
Main Technique:
Heavenly Arrow Death Penalty
Yoshitsune
Born September 18th, Blood Type A
156 cm, B77, W55, H79
Serious, Quietly Love Struck,
Main Technique:
Mountain Green Explosive Crash
Yoshitsune
Born September 18th, Blood Type A
156 cm, B77, W55, H79
Serious, Quietly Love Struck
Main Technique:
Mountain Green Explosive Crash
Zin
Born December 18th
Blood Type AB, 174cm
Blunt
Main Technique:
Frozen Heaven Ice Flash
Zin
Born December 18th
Blood Type AB, 174cm
Blunt
Main Technique:
Frozen Heaven Ice Flash
Sakura
Born December 12th, Blood Type O,
157 cm, B84, W55, H83
Normal
Main Technique:
Crimson Lotus Explosive
Blaze Execution
Sakura
Born December 12th, Blood Type O
157 cm, B84, W55, H83
Normal
Main Technique:
Crimson Lotus Explosive
Blaze Execution
Kaguya
Born August 15th, Blood Type AB
160 cm, B90, W57, H80, 2channeler, Delusional
Main Technique: Ruinous Beam of Light
Kaguya
Born August 15th, Blood Type AB
160 cm, B90, W57, H80, 2channeler, Delusional
Main Technique: Ruinous Beam of Light
Amaterasu
Born January 1st
Blood Type A
142 cm, BXX, W52, HXX ,
Scheming Little Girl, Plays Innocent
Main Technique:
Bewitching Narrow Fallen Light
Amaterasu
Born January 1st
Blood Type A
142 cm, BXX, W52, HXX ,
Scheming Little Girl, Plays Innocent
Main Technique:
Bewitching Narrow Fallen Light
Ibaraki Doji
Born February 3rd
Blood Type B
177 cm, B98, W62, H91
Good-Natured, but Crude
Main Technique: Inferno Grave
Ibaraki Doji
Born February 3rd
Blood Type B
177 cm, B98, W62, H91
Good-Natured, but Crude
Main Technique: Inferno Grave
The Curtain Rises on Onigiri
Shizuka, finish off that Kamikui!
On it!
I wanna do it!
I'm way too close to leveling up to pass this one up!
Then, I shall do it!
This is Shizuka's moment!
But I want EXP, too!
And EXP's being tripled right now!
Um...
This isn't the right time to argue.
Zin
"Oh, dear..."
Only the girls are voiced in Onigiri.
Let's not fight among ourselves!
Zin
"What?!"
Shizuka!
Yoshitsune-chan!
This year's Sakurajima radish looks so good!
I didn't except to land all the way in Satsuma.
Fall damage could've killed us.
Don't say "fall damage"!
What should we do now, Yoshitsune-chan?
Yoshitsune-chan, look!
So this country is also overrun by Kamikui?!
Please save us!
And why are there so many?!
It's all because those Kamikui bastards broke the seal!
Let's save them, Shizuka!
Of course!
Instant Flash!
Bang, bang! Bang, bang, bang!
Pulsing Radiant Slash!
Boom! Boom!
Ultimate technique:
Hectic Exposure Wave Earth Destroyer!
We have detected a faulty tool and have paused all activity.
To investigate this issue,
your accounts shall be suspended for a week.
Oh, okay.
We're sorry.
This is the story
of harbingers of chaos, the Kamikui,
and the brave girls who fight them, supposedly!
Next episode: Pandora's Box.
Next
Episode
Pandora's Box
You'll learn the truth from behind the flames!