Bonus anime:
Seraph of the Endless!
Number 3
What's up, Mika?
Something on your mind again?
Oh, Yuu-chan.
Geez, I keep telling you not to keep it all in.
But... I'm not sure if I can talk to you about this.
Don't worry, just tell me!
Well...
I was just thinking that I've got more charm than you when it comes to the main characters.
Whatever, just go get killed!
Main characters need charm, Yuu-chan!
You need charm like me, you know, for the story!
Like me!
S-Saying all that crap...
But you're the one who said to tell you.
I see. You do have a point.
If I were to make an entrance as a magical girl,
there'd be no doubting the sales!
No, no, no! Now you're just changing the whole story!
Who needs main characters when you have me?
You're already a main character in the novels!
Dammit, you guys!